What are the most popular questions
最热门的问题有哪些？
people come to you with as a sleep
人们带着睡意来找你
doctor?
医生？
&gt;&gt; There's three biggies. Number one is,
有三大件大事。第一点是，
"What do I do if I fall asleep, okay,
“如果我睡着了怎么办，好吗？”
and I wake up in the middle of the night
我半夜醒来
and I can't fall back asleep?"
我睡不着了？
&gt;&gt; And you can help people with that.
你也可以在这方面帮助别人。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. The second question is,
绝对地。第二个问题是：
"What pillow should I buy?" And I'm
我应该买哪种枕头？而我是
going to walk you through which pillows
接下来我会带你了解哪些枕头比较好。
make sense for which people. And then
对哪些人来说有意义？进而
another one that people ask me all the
另一个人们经常问我的问题。
time is, "What's the best time to have
时间就是，“什么时候才是拥有的最佳时机”
sex?"
性别？”
&gt;&gt; That's a strange thing for somebody of
对于一个……来说，这真是一件奇怪的事。
your profession to be
你的职业是
&gt;&gt; about. Well, let me explain why. So,
关于。让我来解释一下原因。所以，
I've been an actively practicing sleep
我一直在积极练习睡眠
specialist for 26 years. I take care of
从事该领域工作26年。我负责照顾
people's sleep problems like apnea,
人们的睡眠问题，例如睡眠呼吸暂停症，
insomnia, and I'm really interested in
失眠，我对这个很感兴趣
the things that you might be doing right
你可能正在做对的事情
now that are messing up your sleep that
现在这些正在扰乱你的睡眠。
are easy to fix. So, for example, most
很容易修复。例如，大多数
people don't know that they have a
人们不知道他们拥有
genetic sleep code inside them called
它们体内的遗传睡眠密码被称为
their chronoype, which decides when your
他们的计时器决定了你的时间
brain releases things like melatonin,
大脑会释放褪黑激素等物质，
cortisol, adrenaline, and dopamine. And
皮质醇、肾上腺素和多巴胺。和
so I can show you based on your
这样我就可以根据你的情况向你展示。
chronotype when it's bedtime, but also
就寝时间的生物钟类型，以及
the perfect time of day to do almost any
一天中做几乎任何事情的最佳时间
activity, including the perfect time to
活动，包括最佳时间
have coffee and alcohol. Crazy. There's
喝咖啡和酒。疯狂的。有
even data to show that your ability to
甚至有数据表明你的能力
understand complicated concepts improves
理解复杂概念的能力会提高
when you're more in line with your
当你更符合你的预期时
chronoype. Now, there are three known
chronoype。现在已知有三个
chronotypes, but what I'm famous for is
睡眠类型，但我出名的是……
discovering a fourth one, which I think
发现了第四个，我认为
might be you. So, we're going to talk a
可能就是你。所以，我们要谈谈……
lot about that. We're also going to talk
关于这方面有很多话要说。我们还要谈谈
about dreams because dreams can tell you
关于梦境，因为梦境可以告诉你答案。
things about yourself that you may not
关于你自己的一些你可能不知道的事情
want to know. And then there's how to
想知道。然后是如何……
fix jet lag, whether you should sleep
如何缓解时差反应，你是否应该睡觉
with a TV on, the truth about melatonin
电视开着，关于褪黑素的真相
supplementation, and my favorite way to
补充营养，以及我最喜欢的补充方式
get magnesium.
补充镁。
&gt;&gt; Before we get into all of that, shall we
在我们深入探讨所有这些之前，我们先……
go and look at the best possible sleep
去看看最好的睡眠方式
position?
位置？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, let's check it out.
好，我们去看看。
&gt;&gt; Guys, I've got a quick favor to ask you.
各位，我有个小忙想请你们帮。
We're approaching a significant
我们即将迎来一个重要的时刻。
subscriber milestone on this show and
本节目订阅用户里程碑
roughly 69% of you that listen and love
大约有 69% 的听众和喜爱者
this show haven't yet subscribed for
我还没有订阅这个节目。
whatever reason. If there was ever a
无论出于什么原因。如果曾经有过……
time for you to do us a favor, if we've
如果我们已经……是时候请你帮我们一个忙了。
ever done anything for you, given you
曾经为你做过什么吗，考虑到你
value in any way, it is simply hitting
无论从哪个角度来看，它的价值就在于此。
that subscribe button. And it means so
那个订阅按钮。而这正是它的含义。
much to myself, but also to my team cuz
这对我自己很重要，对我的团队也很重要，因为
when we hit these milestones, we go away
当我们达到这些里程碑时，我们就离开了。
as a team and celebrate. And it's the
团队合作，共同庆祝。而这正是
thing, the simple, free, easy thing you
这件事，这件简单、免费、容易的事，你
can do to help make this show a little
可以做些什么来帮助让这个节目变得更好？
bit better every single week. So that's
每周都进步一点点。就是这样。
a favor I would ask you. And um if you
我想请你帮个忙。嗯，如果你
do hit the subscribe button, I won't let
请点击订阅按钮，我不会让你失望的。
you down. And we'll continue to find
你倒下了。我们将继续寻找
small ways to make this whole production
制作这部作品的一些小方法
better. Thank you so much for being part
更好的。非常感谢您的参与。
of this journey. Means the world. And uh
这段旅程。意义非凡。呃
yeah, let's do this.
好，我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Dr. Bruce, yes. What is it you do? Why
是的，布鲁斯博士。你是做什么的？为什么
does it matter so much now? And what
现在这件事还这么重要吗？还有什么
perspective do you take on what you do
你对你所做的事情持何种态度？
that is atypical versus other people I
这与其他人不同。
might have spoken to about this subject?
或许可以就此话题进行一些讨论？
&gt;&gt; I'm a sleep doctor. Um I take care of
我是一名睡眠医生。嗯，我负责照顾
people's sleep problems like apnea,
人们的睡眠问题，例如睡眠呼吸暂停症，
narcolepsy, insomnia, things like that.
嗜睡症、失眠症等等。
I've dedicated a good portion of my
我投入了相当一部分时间
career not just to understanding how to
职业生涯不仅仅是了解如何发展。
treat those disorders which are sleep
治疗睡眠障碍
disorders, but what I also I call
疾病，但我也称之为
disordered sleep. I'm really interested
睡眠紊乱。我对此很感兴趣。
in behavioral habits. What's going on?
在行为习惯方面。这是怎么回事？
what are the things that you might be
你可能会遇到哪些事情？
doing right now that are kind of messing
我现在做的这些事有点儿乱套了
up your sleep that are easy to fix um
改善睡眠，有些问题很容易解决。
and be able to maybe change how things
或许还能改变事情的走向。
are going forward? You know, I I didn't
你们打算继续前进吗？你知道，我没有
start out thinking I was going to become
一开始我以为自己会成为
a sleep doctor if I'm going to be honest
说实话，我建议你去看睡眠医生。
with you. Like that that was not on the
与你。就像那件事不在清单上一样
on the path. Um I was actually going in
在路上。嗯，我当时其实正要进去。
a completely different direction. And
完全不同的方向。和
one of the things I really discovered
我真正发现的一件事
was when you change someone's sleep,
就是当你改变某人的睡眠时，
dude, you change their life. Like it is
兄弟，你改变了他们的人生。就像这样
fundamental to who they are. And it's
对他们而言，这是至关重要的。而且是
important for me to be a sleep educator
对我来说，成为一名睡眠教育者非常重要。
in a way, shape, and form that's
以某种方式、形状和形式来说，是
practical so that people can actually
实用，以便人们能够真正做到
get something from what I'm talking
从我的话里听出点什么吧。
about and apply it right then and there.
立刻就去做，然后立即应用。
&gt;&gt; And there's probably a couple of million
可能还有几百万个。
people that have clicked onto this
点击过这个链接的人
conversation to listen.
值得倾听的对话。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Who is this conversation for?
这段对话是说给谁听的？
&gt;&gt; I think it's for anybody out there who's
我认为这适合所有……
either curious about sleep or wants to
要么是对睡眠感到好奇，要么是想……
try to improve their sleep or maybe
尝试改善他们的睡眠，或者
suspicious that they could have a
怀疑他们可能拥有
problem with their sleep. I think any
他们睡眠有问题。我认为任何
one of those three types of people would
这三种人中的一种会
find tremendous value here. And what are
这里蕴藏着巨大的价值。以及什么是
we going to be able to do for those
我们将能够为那些人做些什么
people today specifically?
特指当今的人们？
&gt;&gt; So, I'm going to give people um several
所以，我要给人们几个……
different like plans, if you will, uh
不同的方案，如果你愿意这么说的话，嗯
maybe even a five-step plan of things
或许还可以制定一个五步计划。
that they can absolutely learn how to
他们绝对可以学会如何做
do. They're also going to learn about a
做。他们还将学习有关……
genetic sleep code that they have inside
他们体内拥有的基因睡眠密码
them called their chronoype. A lot of
他们称他们为 chronoype。很多
people don't even know that they have a
人们甚至不知道他们拥有
chronoype or maybe they've heard of the
时间机器，或者他们可能听说过
of the idea, but they haven't ever heard
他们了解这个想法，但他们从未听说过。
of the term. We're going to learn a lot
该术语。我们将学到很多东西。
about that. We're also going to talk
关于那件事。我们还要谈谈
about dreams a little bit. Um I'm
稍微谈谈梦境。嗯，我是
excited to have the opportunity to do
很高兴有机会做这件事
that. I've spent the last year and a
那。过去一年多以来，我一直致力于此。
half learning more about how to use
一半人正在学习如何使用
dreams in my clinical work as a
我在临床工作中做的梦
psychologist, which is very interesting
心理学家，这很有意思。
stuff. So, I'm excited to share some of
东西。所以，我很兴奋地想和大家分享一些……
that. So, I think people are going to
那。所以，我认为人们会……
learn a whole bunch.
学到很多东西。
&gt;&gt; And dreams matter.
梦想很重要。
&gt;&gt; Oh, yeah. They absolutely matter. I'm I
哦，是的。它们至关重要。我是我
call dreams emotional metabolism, right?
把梦境称为情绪代谢，对吧？
And so, when you're dreaming, what is
所以，当你做梦的时候，什么是……
you what is the function? What is the
请问这个功能是什么？什么是
purpose? What are you doing? You're
目的？你在干什么？你是
actually working through your emotional
实际上，你需要努力克服自己的情绪
states that you had during the daytime.
你白天所经历的状态。
Um this is why we have nightmares,
嗯，这就是我们为什么会做噩梦的原因。
right? And so in a nightmare, it's a
正确的？所以在噩梦中，它是一种
scary scene and all a sudden it gets so
恐怖的场景，突然间就变得如此
emotional, you wake up. That is
情绪波动，你醒来了。那是
officially called a nightmare. That
官方称之为噩梦。那
awakening, but you stop processing. And
觉醒了，但你停止了思考。和
when you go back to sleep, you go back
当你再次入睡时，你就回去了。
to the dream and you get to that scary
梦境开始，你就会遇到那个可怕的地方。
point, you wake up again and you get
关键是，你再次醒来，然后你就会
caught in this loop, right? And so
陷入这个循环了吗？所以
dreams matter because they can be
梦想之所以重要，是因为它们可以……
incredibly disruptive. Also, they can
极具破坏性。此外，他们还可以
tell you things about yourself that you
告诉你一些关于你自己的事情
may not want to know or may not have in
可能不想知道，或者可能没有
the front of your mind at all times.
时刻牢记于心。
Right? Sometimes people have very
正确的？有时人们非常
interesting dreams like dreams of being
有趣的梦，比如梦见自己
chased or dreams of their teeth falling
追逐或梦见牙齿脱落
out or all these different things and
以及所有这些不同的事物
they can mean a whole host of different
它们可以指代各种各样的不同含义。
things. But I want to be super clear.
事物。但我想要说得非常清楚。
There's no guide book that says, "Hey,
没有哪本指南会说：“嘿，
you know, if you're if you're dreaming
你知道，如果你在做梦
of that you're in water, you hate your
如果你身处水中，你会讨厌你的
mother." Like, it doesn't really work
母亲。” 好像这根本行不通。
that way. Dreams mean something to the
那样做。梦对……来说是有意义的
dreamer. And so the goal is to
梦想家。因此，目标是
understand the context within that. So
理解其中的背景。所以
who is the dreamer? What is the dream?
谁是做梦者？梦想是什么？
And then how do those two work together?
那么，这两者是如何协同工作的呢？
And what is the experience that you're
你的体验是什么？
drawing from academically but also
借鉴学术界，但也
professionally? Give me a view of how
专业上？请给我展示一下如何
many people you've worked with and
你曾共事过的许多人以及
the range of things people come to you
人们来找你的范围很广
with.
和。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So I've been an actively
是的。所以我一直积极参与
practicing sleep specialist for 26
从事睡眠专科工作26年
years. So I work in offices with medical
年。所以我在有医疗人员的办公室工作。
doctors cuz I'm not a medical doctor. I
医生们，因为我不是医生。我
have a PhD and I work with them on their
我拥有博士学位，我与他们一起从事他们的工作。
patients. lot of insomnia patients but
患者。很多失眠患者，但是
also the apneas, the restless legs, the
还有睡眠呼吸暂停、不宁腿综合征、
narcolepsies of the world because I have
因为我患有世界上所有的嗜睡症，所以我患有嗜睡症。
kind of a unique distinction in that I'm
这是一种独特的区别，因为我
one of 168 people in the world who took
世界上有168人参加了这项活动，他是其中之一。
the medical boards without going to
无需前往医疗委员会
medical school and passed. So I can work
医学院毕业了。这样我就可以工作了
within that framework and really
在这个框架内，而且真的
understand a lot of what's going on. I
了解很多正在发生的事情。我
don't prescribe medication, but if I'm
不要给我开药，但如果我
honest with you, most people don't need
说实话，大多数人不需要
sleep medication as far as I'm
就我而言，睡眠药物
concerned. I can get them to sleep
担心的。我可以哄他们睡觉
usually without any medication at all.
通常完全不需要任何药物。
&gt;&gt; And you're a psychologist as well?
你也是一名心理学家吗？
&gt;&gt; I am. I'm a clinical psychologist. And
我是。我是一名临床心理学家。和
how does those two worlds make 1 plus 1
这两个世界如何等于 1 加 1 呢？
equal three?
等于三？
&gt;&gt; Sure. So when you talk about sleep,
当然。所以，当谈到睡眠时，
psychology is all over the place. I
心理学真是五花八门。我
would argue 75% of the reason people
有人认为这是人们75%的理由。
don't sleep is anxiety or fear. That
失眠是因为焦虑或恐惧。那
really falls well within the range of
确实完全符合以下范围：
psychology for sure. Um, and it's
当然是心理学方面的问题。嗯，而且是
different kinds of fears. It's fears
不同类型的恐惧。这是恐惧。
that you know about that are right in
你知道的那些事情是对的
your face, like something that's going
你的脸，就像有什么事要发生了一样
on in your daytime, but it could be
白天可以，但也有可能
other fears. It could be fears of your
其他的担忧。这可能是你对……的恐惧。
relationship. It could be financial
关系。可能是财务方面的问题。
fears. It could be a whole host of
恐惧。这可能是一系列
different things. So, I think there's a
不同的事情。所以，我认为存在一个
lot of psychology that gets to be played
很多心理因素都可以加以利用。
in all of this kind of thing.
在所有这些事情中。
&gt;&gt; I got two more questions before we
在我们开始之前，我还有两个问题。
really get into the details and
真正深入了解细节，
specifics and start really helping the
具体细节并开始真正提供帮助
audience with whatever they're dealing
观众会关注他们正在处理的任何事情。
with.
和。
&gt;&gt; The first is we have lots of props here.
首先，我们这里有很多道具。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Give me a a topline view of the types of
请给我简要介绍一下以下几种类型：
things you're going to show me and why
你要给我展示的东西以及原因
you've brought all of these wonderful
你带来了所有这些美好的事物
props.
道具。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. So, I get asked a lot of
绝对地。所以，我经常被问到这个问题。
questions as you might imagine and um
正如你可能想象的那样，问题有很多，嗯。
one of the big questions that I get
我经常被问到的一个大问题
asked is what bed and pillow should I
问我应该选择什么样的床和枕头。
buy? So, sitting next to you is a large
买？所以，坐在你旁边的是一个大……
stack of pillows, all different types,
一堆枕头，各种类型都有。
actually. And I want to be able to show
实际上。我想能够展示
some of your viewers how you look at
你的一些观众如何看待你
pillows and which pillows make sense for
枕头以及哪些枕头适合
which people. Believe it or not, there's
哪些人？信不信由你，确实有
like a fitting process. We're going to
就像一个试穿过程。我们将要
go through that. This device right here
经历一下。这个设备就在这里
is a sleep test, believe it or not. So,
信不信由你，这是一项睡眠测试。所以，
it used to be we'd have to send you to
以前我们必须派你去
the hospital. Yeah, you can unwind it.
医院。是的，你可以把它解开。
Uh, you have to send you to the
呃，你得把你送到
hospital. We'd put 27 electrodes all
医院。我们总共放置了27个电极。
over your body, respiratory belts across
呼吸带横跨全身
your chest. We'd have cameras zoomed in
你的胸部。我们会架设摄像机，拉近镜头。
on you. And then, by the way, you're
在你身上。顺便说一句，你是
supposed to be able to go to sleep,
应该能够入睡，
right? And we're supposed to be able to
正确的？我们应该能够
monitor you. Now, historically, we were
监视你。从历史上看，我们曾经是
able to do that pretty well. But once
他能很好地做到这一点。但曾经
COVID hit, nobody wanted to sleep in the
新冠疫情爆发后，没人愿意睡在……
same bed that somebody else had been
同一张床，之前有人睡过。
sleeping in the day before. So, now we
前一天睡懒觉。所以，现在我们
have what are called HSTS or home sleep
有所谓的HSTS或家庭睡眠
tests.
测试。
&gt;&gt; Wow.
哇。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. We'll talk about how to use it and
是的。我们将讨论如何使用它，
and what it can tell you.
以及它能告诉你什么。
&gt;&gt; My last question before we get into the
在我们正式开始之前，我的最后一个问题是……
details is what are the most popular
细节是最受欢迎的。
questions that people come to you with
人们向你提出的问题
as a sleep doctor?
作为一名睡眠医生？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, I'd say there's probably three
是的。所以，我觉得大概有三个。
biggies, right? Number one is, "Hey, Dr.
都是大事，对吧？第一个例子是，“嘿，博士。”
Bruce, I fall asleep just fine, but I
布鲁斯，我入睡没问题，但是……
wake up somewhere between 1 and 3:00 in
在凌晨1点到3点之间醒来
the morning, and it either takes me 20
早上，要么需要我20分钟。
minutes or 3 hours to fall back asleep.
几分钟或3小时才能再次入睡。
What the heck is going on there?"
那里到底发生了什么事？
&gt;&gt; And you can help people with that.
你也可以在这方面帮助别人。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. I'm going to give everybody
绝对地。我要给每个人
a exactly what I do in clinic. Like, I'm
这正是我在诊所里所做的。比如，我是
going to explain to everybody exactly
我会向所有人详细解释。
what I say to my patients and how to go
我跟病人说什么以及如何去做
about getting through that particular
关于如何度过那段时期
problem because it's it's so flagrant.
问题在于它太明目张胆了。
Everybody needs to know how to how to
每个人都需要知道如何做
work with that. The second question
就按这个来做。第二个问题
would be um what bed should I buy or
我会问：我应该买哪种床？
what pillow should I buy? I think we're
我应该买哪种枕头？我认为我们是
going to address that over here. Um and
我打算在这里解决这个问题。嗯，还有
then another one that people ask me all
然后还有另一个问题，人们总是问我。
the time is, you know,
你知道，时间就是这样。
is there some kind of timing? Is there
是否存在某种时间安排？有没有
some like I feel like my body is off.
有些人感觉我的身体不太对劲。
They say this all the time. They're
他们总是这么说。他们是
like, if I just lived in a different
比如，如果我住在另一个地方
time zone, I feel like everything would
时区，我觉得一切都会
work out well. So the very basics of
效果很好。所以，最基本的是……
sleep.
睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Uhhuh.
嗯哼。
&gt;&gt; What do I need to know about what sleep
我需要了解哪些关于睡眠的知识
is, the role it solves for us to even
是，它为我们解决的作用甚至
understand the context of the things
理解事物的背景。
we're going to talk about today?
我们今天要谈什么？
&gt;&gt; Yep. There's only a few things that are
是的。只有少数几件事是
truly important to understand about
真正重要的是要了解
sleep. One is how does sleep work in the
睡觉。其中一个问题是睡眠是如何运作的？
brain. It turns out that there's two
脑。原来有两个。
separate systems in the brain. One is
大脑中不同的系统。一是
called your sleep drive. The other is
我称之为睡眠驱动力。另一个是
called your sleep rhythm. And they both
叫做你的睡眠节律。他们俩
work uh in an interesting way. They're
以一种有趣的方式工作。他们是
both a little bit like hunger, right? So
两者都有点像饥饿，对吧？所以
sleep drive is like hunger because right
睡眠驱动力就像饥饿一样，因为……
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I
我饿了。我饿了。我饿了。我
eat something. that hunger begins to
吃点东西。饥饿感开始出现
dissipate. Same holds true with sleep.
消散。睡眠也是如此。
The longer you stay awake, the more the
你熬夜的时间越长，就越……
more sleepy that you get. When you look
你越困越困。当你看
at it from a biology standpoint, it's
从生物学的角度来看，它是
kind of interesting. So, when a cell
挺有意思的。所以，当一个细胞
eats a piece of glucose, something comes
吃了一块葡萄糖，然后有东西来了
out the back end. One of those things is
从后端出来。其中一件事是
called a denisonin. It works its way
称为丹尼森宁。它会按部就班地进行。
through your system and goes to a very
通过你的系统，并进入一个非常
specific receptor area, as a denisonin
特定受体区域，如丹尼森宁
accumulates, you get sleepier and
累积起来，你会越来越困，
sleepier and sleepier. Now, why am I
越来越困。那么，我为什么会这样？
going into so much detail? Turns out
要讲这么多细节吗？原来如此
when you look at a denisonin and you
当你看着丹尼森宁的时候
look at caffeine, they're off by one
看看咖啡因，他们算错了一个。
molecule. So, here's a little tip or
分子。所以，这里有个小提示或
trick early in the pod for everyone. I
在游戏初期就给所有人使了个小伎俩。我
call it the nappa latte. So, what you do
就叫它纳帕拿铁吧。所以，你做什么？
is you take a cup of drip black coffee,
你喝了一杯滴滤黑咖啡，
just throw in a couple of ice cubes,
只需放入几块冰块即可。
right? Merely to cool it down, drink it
正确的？只是为了降降温，喝掉它
as fast as you can, and immediately take
尽快，并立即服用
a 25minute nap. The adenosin that's
午睡25分钟。腺苷就是
built up in your brain will burn through
大脑中积累的毒素会燃烧殆尽。
while you're napping. Caffeine, since
当你午睡的时候。咖啡因，因为
it's so close in molecular structure,
它们的分子结构非常相似，
can fit into that receptor site. It
可以与该受体位点匹配。它
blocks any new adenosin. You're good for
阻断任何新的腺苷生成。你很适合
four hours, guaranteed. I use it with
保证四个小时。我把它和
every CEO that I work with. So, let's
我合作过的每一位CEO。那么，我们开始吧
say you only got three hours of sleep
假设你只睡了三个小时
the other night and you've got a big
那天晚上，你有一个很大的
presentation to do or an awards ceremony
演讲或颁奖典礼
or something like that. You can do a
或者类似的事情。你可以这样做
nappa latte for about 25 minutes or so
制作纳帕拿铁大约需要25分钟左右。
and you will feel much better. That's
你会感觉好多了。那是
sleep drive.
睡眠驱动。
&gt;&gt; Let me just
让我先说明一下
&gt;&gt; Sure.
当然。
&gt;&gt; I want to make sure I really understand
我想确保我真正理解
this. Can you explain this to me again
这。你能再给我解释一遍吗？
as if I'm a 16-year-old? by having a
就好像我是个16岁的孩子一样？通过拥有
coffee and then taking a nap would make
喝杯咖啡，然后睡个午觉。
me feel energetic because one would
我感觉精力充沛，因为一个人会
think that having a coffee and taking a
想想喝杯咖啡，然后……
nap are like
午睡就像
&gt;&gt; would be almost impossible, right? So,
几乎不可能，对吧？所以，
number one, the caffeine doesn't kick in
第一，咖啡因根本不起作用。
before the end of the nap. So, a lot of
在午睡结束之前。所以，很多
people think when I drink coffee, boom,
人们以为我喝咖啡的时候，砰！
it just kind of spins up and all a
它就这么开始旋转起来，然后就……
sudden I'm able to, you know, I get a
突然间，我能够，你知道，我得到一个
lot of energy from it. That's really not
它蕴含着巨大的能量。那真的不是
actually how caffeine works. It has to
实际上，咖啡因就是通过这种方式起作用的。它必须
go down, has to get absorbed, has to be
下降，必须被吸收，必须
digested. And so while all that's going
已消化。所以，就在这一切发生的同时
on, which takes approximately 25 to 30
开启，大约需要 25 到 30 分钟
minutes, you're actually taking a nap to
几分钟后，你其实是在打盹儿。
lower the amount of adenosin that has
降低腺苷的含量
built up in your brain. Let's say it's 2
在你的大脑中积累起来。假设它是 2
o'clock in the afternoon and you only
下午几点了，你只有
slept for 4 hours and you are dragging,
睡了4个小时就感觉昏昏沉沉的，
right? All that adenosine that's built
正确的？所有这些构建的腺苷
up when you take that 25minute nap,
当你小睡25分钟后醒来，
you'll burn through a lot of it and then
你会消耗掉很多，然后
caffeine fits in and blocks any
咖啡因恰好能起到阻断作用。
additional adenosin from coming in. So
阻止更多腺苷进入细胞。
that way you're actually adding caffeine
那样做实际上就相当于补充了咖啡因。
to the situation and boom, your energy
适应了这种情况，然后砰的一声，你的能量
goes straight. Okay. So adenosine is
直走。好的。所以腺苷是
makes me tired when it's docked in my
它停靠在我的……时让我感到疲倦
brain.
脑。
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
确切地。
&gt;&gt; So I have 4 hours sleep which means
所以我只睡了4个小时，这意味着
there's lots of adenosine and sleep get
有很多腺苷，而且容易入睡
clears the adenosine.
清除腺苷。
&gt;&gt; Correct. And then caffeine comes in
正确的。然后咖啡因就来了。
because it fits so perfectly into that
因为它与此完美契合。
receptor site
受体位点
&gt;&gt; and off you go. That's sleep drive.
然后你就走了。那是睡眠驱动力。
Sleep rhythm has to do with your
睡眠节律与你的
circadian rhythm. Right. And so lots of
昼夜节律。正确的。所以有很多
lots of information about that. But
有很多相关信息。但
basically your circadian rhythm is also
基本上，你的昼夜节律也是
a lot like hunger. Right? You ever
很像饥饿。正确的？你曾经
notice you're hungry around breakfast
注意到早餐前后你会感到饥饿。
time, around lunchtime, around dinner
时间，大约在午餐时间，晚餐时间
time, right? That's your circadian
时间到了，对吧？这就是你的昼夜节律
rhythm for hunger. For sleep, most
饥饿的节奏。对于睡眠而言，大多数
people, at least here in North America,
至少在北美，人们
have a tendency to fall asleep somewhere
有随时随地睡着的倾向
between 10:30 and 11:00, 11:30 at night.
上午 10:30 至 11:00，晚上 11:30。
So, that's kind of the circadian rhythm
这就是昼夜节律的由来
there. So, when your circadian rhythm is
那里。所以，当你的昼夜节律是
high and your drive is high, you sleep.
情绪高涨，动力十足，你却睡着了。
But if either one of them is off, that's
但如果他们中任何一个缺席，那就糟了。
when you have a sleep disorder or
当你患有睡眠障碍时
disordered sleep.
睡眠紊乱。
&gt;&gt; My circadian rhythm is high.
我的生物钟很紊乱。
&gt;&gt; When your circadian rhythm is on point,
当你的昼夜节律正常时，
high is probably not the right word. On
“高”这个词可能不太合适。在
point. So meaning you are abiding by
观点。所以意思是，你遵守了……
your circadian rhythm. Now another
你的昼夜节律。现在又来了
question you might say to me is well how
你可能会问我的问题是：如何
do I know what my circadian rhythm is?
我知道我的昼夜节律是什么吗？
And we're going to talk a lot about
我们将深入探讨……
chronotypes cuz that's what your
昼夜节律类型，因为这就是你的
circadian rhythm is.
昼夜节律是。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So let's do chronotypes then.
好的。那么我们就来聊聊昼夜节律类型吧。
You've got some cards in front of you.
你面前有一些牌。
&gt;&gt; I do. I kind of like these cards. So
我愿意。我挺喜欢这些卡片的。所以
when we talk about chronotypes, a lot of
当我们谈论生物钟类型时，很多
people may have heard of the idea but
人们可能听说过这个想法，但
not actually heard the term chronoype
我之前没听说过chronoype这个词。
before. So if anybody out there has ever
前。所以，如果有人曾经有过这样的经历的话……
been called an early bird or a night
有人称他为早起的鸟儿，也有人称他为夜猫子。
owl, those are chronoypes. So, we've got
猫头鹰，那些是时间鸟。所以，我们有了
early birds. These are people who, by
早起的鸟儿有虫吃。这些人，通过
the way, this is genetic. You don't you
从某种意义上说，这是基因决定的。你不
don't actually get to choose this.
实际上你没有选择权。
There's a special area on your genome
你的基因组上有一个特殊区域。
called the PER3 area. And when you have
称为 PER3 区域。当你拥有
something called a single nucleotide
一种叫做单核苷酸的东西
polymorphism or a snip. If it's flipped
多态性或剪切。如果它翻转了
one way, you're an early bird. If it's
从某种意义上说，你是个早起的鸟儿。如果是
flipped another way, you're a night owl.
换句话说，你就是个夜猫子。
If it's not flipped, you're in the
如果它没有翻转，你就在……
middle. Okay? So, so far, I haven't told
中间。好的？所以，到目前为止，我还没有告诉过别人。
anybody anything new. Like, this is this
有没有人知道什么新鲜事？比如，这就是这个
is all stuff that we've already learned.
这些都是我们已经学过的东西。
The new part is this irregularity that
新的部分是这种不规则性。
seems to happen for people during for
似乎在人们……期间会发生这种情况
their sleep schedule. Specifically, an
他们的睡眠时间表。具体来说，
irregularity in their melatonin and
褪黑激素分泌不规律
cortisol production. So, all of this is
皮质醇生成。所以，这一切都是
predicated on when does your body make
取决于你的身体何时产生
melatonin. So, if you're an early bird,
褪黑素。所以，如果你是早起的鸟儿，
your body makes melatonin earlier in the
你的身体会在更早的时候开始分泌褪黑激素。
night starting at around 8:00 in the
晚上大约从8点开始
evening. Makes you want to go to bed
晚上。让人只想睡觉
around 9:30. You have a question.
大约9点30分。你有一个问题。
&gt;&gt; So, melatonin is a hormone
所以，褪黑激素是一种激素。
&gt;&gt; it is
这是
&gt;&gt; that
那
&gt;&gt; you produce inside of your body that
你体内会产生那种物质
actually helps you sleep. It guides, it
实际上有助于睡眠。它指引着，它
tells your body when it's bedtime, which
它会告诉你的身体什么时候该睡觉了，
is a little bit different than the
与……略有不同
adenosine, which makes you feel sleepy.
腺苷，它会让你感到困倦。
&gt;&gt; I guess people listening now would be
我想现在正在收听的人应该是
asking themselves, why does it matter to
他们不禁自问，这为什么重要？
know my chronotype? Like, as it relates
知道我的生物钟类型吗？就像它所关联的
to my productivity, the way I live my
对我的生产力而言，我的生活方式
life, my relationships, whatever matters
生活、我的人际关系、所有重要的事情
to me, why does it matter?
对我来说，这有什么关系呢？
&gt;&gt; Because I can show you based on your
因为我可以根据你的情况向你展示。
chronoype the perfect time of day to do
找出一天中做这件事的最佳时间
almost any activity. So if you f if you
几乎任何活动。所以如果你f如果你
know when your body is doing certain
了解你的身体何时在做某些事情
things, when it has melatonin or when it
东西，当它含有褪黑素或当它
has cortisol or adrenaline or all these
是否含有皮质醇或肾上腺素，或两者都含有
other things, if you know the schedule,
其他事情，如果你知道日程安排的话，
you can actually just change your
你其实可以简单地改变你的
activity to when your body is naturally
当你的身体自然活动时
producing the hormone and then you do
产生激素，然后你……
the hormone better.
这种激素更好。
&gt;&gt; Okay,
好的，
&gt;&gt; so let's talk about the easy one, which
那么，我们来谈谈最简单的那个，
is sex, right? So a lot of people want
性就是性，对吧？所以很多人都想要
to know, "Hey, Michael, what's the best
想知道，“嘿，迈克尔，最好的是什么？”
time to have sex?" By the way, I think
该做爱了吗？顺便说一句，我觉得
that might be the third question that I
那可能是我要问的第三个问题。
get asked most um often other than uh
除了……之外，最常被问到的问题是……
the insomnia one and the mattress one I
失眠症和床垫的问题
think is what's the best time for sex
想想什么时候才是性爱的最佳时间
might be the the other question that I
这可能是我要问的另一个问题。
get asked more than anything.
被问到最多的问题。
&gt;&gt; Must be tricky if you the time you want
如果你想在某个特定时间做这件事，那肯定很棘手。
to have sex and the time your partner
和伴侣发生性关系的时间
wants to have sex are off.
想做爱的人都拒绝了。
&gt;&gt; Well, think about it like this. What if
不妨这样想。如果什么
your partner's an early bird and you're
你的伴侣是个早起的人，而你
a night owl?
你是夜猫子吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I think that's me.
是的，我想那就是我。
&gt;&gt; Don't worry, we're we're going to be
别担心，我们会……
able to fix you. So, first of all,
能够治好你。首先，
there's a couple of different answers to
这个问题有几种不同的答案。
this question. So, number one is you
这个问题。所以，第一名是你。
want to have a time. So, first of all,
想找个时间。首先，
most people are intimate between 10:30
大多数人在晚上10:30之间有性生活。
and 11:30 at night. That's just a survey
晚上 11:30。那只是一份调查问卷。
that we did. So, it makes kind of a lot
我们确实做到了。所以，它产生了很多。
of sense. But here's what's interesting
有道理的。但有趣的是……
is your hormone profile doesn't look too
你的激素水平看起来不太好
good at 11:30 at night for having sex.
晚上11点半适合做爱。
In order to have successful sex, you
为了获得成功的性生活，你
want to have estrogen, testosterone,
想要雌激素、睾酮，
progesterone, adrenaline, and cortisol
孕酮、肾上腺素和皮质醇
all to be high and melatonin to be low.
所有指标都升高，褪黑激素水平降低。
What do you think your hormone profile
你觉得你的激素水平如何？
looks like at 10:30 at night?
看起来像是晚上10点半？
&gt;&gt; It's literally the opposite, right?
事实恰恰相反，对吧？
Melatonin is high and all those other
褪黑激素水平高，以及其他所有因素。
things are low. That's hint number one
情况很糟糕。这是第一条提示。
as to when would probably be the best
至于什么时候可能是最佳时机
time to have sex. Hint number two, if
该做爱了。提示二，如果
you happen to be having sex with
你碰巧正在和……发生性关系
somebody who was born biologically male,
生理性别为男性的人
what do most men wake up with in the
大多数男人醒来时身上有什么？
morning? An erection. If that's not
早晨？勃起。如果那不是
mother nature telling you when to use
大自然会告诉你何时使用
that thing, I don't know what is. Right?
那东西，我不知道那是什么。正确的？
So, when you start to look at it, and we
所以，当你开始审视它的时候，我们
actually did the surveys, we discovered
我们发现，实际上我们已经做了调查。
that people actually have greater
人们实际上拥有更大的
connection and greater performance in
连接和更佳性能
their sex when they have sex in the
他们在性交时的性行为
morning time. Now, do you have to brush
早晨。现在，你需要刷牙吗？
your teeth and throw in a little
把你的牙齿也放进去一点
mouthwash first? Yes, of course you do.
先漱口？当然，你肯定想。
Like, let's be fair to your partner
比如，让我们公平对待你的伴侣。
here. But you end up learning quite a
这里。但最终你会学到很多东西
bit. Again, your body is telling you
少量。你的身体再次告诉你
this is actually the perfect time to do
这实际上是做这件事的最佳时机
something like this. Did you know
类似这样的。你可知道
there's like a perfect time to have
似乎总有一个最佳时机……
coffee?
咖啡？
&gt;&gt; I didn't.
我没有。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, there's absolutely a perfect time
是的，绝对存在一个完美时机。
based on your chronoype, too. One of the
也取决于你的时间记录。中的一个
first things that I ask people all the
我问人们的第一件事
time, I'll ask you, um, is the first
时间，我会问你，嗯，是第一个
liquid that crosses over your lips in
流过你嘴唇的液体
the morning caffeinated?
早上喝咖啡了吗？
&gt;&gt; Yes. So, let's talk about why that's
是的。那么，我们来谈谈为什么会这样。
probably not the best idea. So, most
这可能不是个好主意。所以，大多数
people don't know, sorry, most people
抱歉，大多数人都不知道。
don't know, but uh sleep in and of
不知道，但是呃，睡个懒觉什么的
itself is a dehydrative event. You lose
本身就是一种脱水事件。你输了
almost a full liter of water just from
光是这些水就几乎取了一升
the humidity in your breath by by
你呼吸中的湿度
breathing all night long. Caffeine is a
整夜都在呼吸。咖啡因是一种
diuretic, which mean it makes you have
利尿剂，这意味着它会让你……
to go pee. So, when you're already lost
去小便。所以，当你已经迷失方向的时候
a liter, now you add a couple of cups of
一升，现在你再加入几杯
caffeine, which makes you have to pee,
咖啡因会让你想小便，
you're going to turn into a raisin
你会变成一颗葡萄干
before this whole thing is through.
在这一切结束之前。
Okay? So, we need to get some water
好的？所以，我们需要弄些水。
inside of you. And so, one of the big
你内心深处。因此，其中一项重大举措是……
recommendations that I give all of my
我给所有人的建议
patients is don't have caffeine for the
病人不能摄入咖啡因
first 90 minutes you're awake. Now,
前90分钟你保持清醒。现在，
you're going to sit here and say, "9
你会坐在这里说，“9
minutes? That's a Michael? That's a long
分钟？那是迈克尔吗？那可真是一段漫长的时光。
time not to have any caffeine." Like,
是时候戒掉咖啡因了。
how am I going to do that? Like, I've
我该怎么做呢？比如，我已经
got my morning routine. I can smell the
我的晨间例行程序开始了。我能闻到……
coffee in the morning. It smells so
早晨的咖啡。闻起来好臭
good. Everything's going. How's how's
好的。一切进展顺利。怎么样？
this going to work? Let me explain the
这行得通吗？让我解释一下
biology. In order to exit a state of
生物学。为了退出某种状态
unconsciousness, you need two hormones,
失去意识需要两种激素。
and you need a lot of them. You need
而且你需要很多。你需要
adrenaline and cortisol and they both
肾上腺素和皮质醇，它们两者
wake you up. When you have a brain
叫醒你。当你拥有大脑
that's full of adrenaline and cortisol
里面充满了肾上腺素和皮质醇
and you add caffeine to it, it's like
再加上咖啡因，就好像
it's like adding weak tea to somebody
这就像给某人倒淡茶一样。
who's taking cocaine. Okay? It's not a
谁在吸食可卡因？好的？它不是
very powerful stimulant compared to the
与……相比，它是一种非常强效的兴奋剂。
hormones that are in your brain that are
大脑中存在的激素
a powerful stimulant. But if you just
一种强效兴奋剂。但如果你只是
wait 90 minutes, cortisol and adrenaline
等待90分钟，皮质醇和肾上腺素
naturally drop. If you have your
自然下降。如果你有你的
caffeine, then it actually boosts the
咖啡因实际上会增强……
cortisol and gives you a bigger bang for
皮质醇，并给你带来更大的好处
your buck. M
你的钱。 M
&gt;&gt; so you hydrate before you caffeinate and
所以你要先补充水分再摄入咖啡因。
about the amount somewhere between 15
金额大约在 15 到 15 之间
and 20 ounces of water if you can get
如果可以的话，再喝20盎司的水。
that down in the first hour and a half
在前一个半小时内就结束了。
that you're awake.
你已经醒了。
&gt;&gt; What's that in English terms?
用英语怎么说？
&gt;&gt; Oh, I don't know what that we'll have to
哦，我不知道我们得怎么办……
look it up.
查一下。
&gt;&gt; Is it one cup? Is it two cups?
是一杯吗？是两杯吗？
&gt;&gt; Oh, I would say it's probably 3 to four
哦，我估计大概是三到四个吧。
cups of water.
几杯水。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Well, that's a lot.
好的。嗯，那可真不少。
&gt;&gt; Well, don't forget you've lost a lot of
别忘了你已经失去了很多
water while you're sleeping and you
睡觉时喝水，你
might have lost it the previous day
可能前一天弄丢了
because let's say you worked out or
因为假设你锻炼了或者
things like that.
诸如此类的事情。
&gt;&gt; So, let's get into these chronotypes
那么，让我们来深入了解一下这些睡眠类型吧。
then.
然后。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, let's start off with the lion.
是的。那么，我们就从狮子开始吧。
So, lions are my early birds. Um, you
所以，狮子是我的早起鸟。嗯，你
know you've got a lion in your midst
要知道你身边有头狮子。
when you get an email at 6:00 a.m.,
当你早上6点收到一封电子邮件时，
right? That's somebody who's been up for
正确的？那是个一直很积极的人。
a while and who's got their brain kind
过了一会儿，谁的脑子比较发达呢？
of cooking. Um, lions like to make a
烹饪。嗯，狮子喜欢制造
list and go from step one to step two to
列出步骤并从第一步到第二步进行操作。
step three every single day. They get a
每天执行第三步。他们得到一个
lot of confidence and they get a lot of
他们信心十足，而且获得了很多……
pleasure following uh this list. But, if
很高兴能关注这份清单。但是，如果
I'm honest with you, being a lion isn't
说实话，当狮子并不
all it's cracked up to be because dinner
晚餐果然名不虚传
and a movie is out for a line. They've
一部电影正在热映。他们有
been up since like 4:30, 5 o'clock in
大概四点半到五点就醒了。
the morning, right? They don't want to
早上吧？他们不想
go see a concert late at night. They
深夜去看一场音乐会。他们
want to go to bed at like 8:30, nine
想在晚上八点半或九点睡觉。
o'clock. So, when you're looking at
点钟。所以，当你在看……
lions or what I early birds, what I call
狮子，或者我称之为早起的鸟儿，我称之为
lions, they've got some very interesting
狮子，它们有一些非常有趣的东西。
characteristics. They make up between 10
特征。它们占10%到10%。
and 15% of the population from a
以及来自以下地区的15%的人口
biological characteristic standpoint,
从生物学特性角度来看，
their melatonin stops early and their
他们的褪黑激素分泌很早就停止了，而且他们的
cortisol starts early. So, their
皮质醇分泌开始得早。所以，他们的
melatonin stops at about 4:30, 5:00 in
褪黑激素分泌大约在凌晨 4:30 到 5:00 之间停止。
the morning, and that's when cortisol
早上，也就是皮质醇分泌最旺盛的时候。
starts. And that's the reason why they
开始。这就是他们的原因
wake up so early.
起得好早。
&gt;&gt; What sort of window do the lions wake up
狮子们是通过什么样的窗户醒来的？
in?
在？
&gt;&gt; So, it's interesting because I've got
所以，这很有意思，因为我有
some lions who are kind of extreme, like
有些狮子性格比较极端，比如
they're getting up at 4:30 in the
他们早上4:30起床。
morning, which is not really probably
早上，这可能不太现实。
the best idea. But generally speaking,
最好的主意。但总的来说，
my lions get up right around 5 5:15 up
我的狮子们大约5点5分起床。
until about 6:00 6:30, but they are
直到大约6点到6点半，但他们是
definitely my early risers. They have a
绝对是我的早起者们。他们有一个
small breakfast. They don't like to eat
早餐很简单。他们不喜欢吃
a lot of food early in the in the
早期有很多食物
morning time because a lot of these
早上，因为很多这些
people like to go work out fairly
人们喜欢去锻炼身体。
quickly after they've uh after they've
在他们……之后很快
woken up. um which is very different
醒了。嗯，这非常不同。
than some of my other chronotypes. My
比我其他一些睡眠类型要好。我的
night owls don't like to work out in the
夜猫子不喜欢在白天锻炼。
morning. They don't like to do anything
早晨。他们什么都不喜欢做。
in the morning. So, my lions like to
在早晨。所以，我的狮子们喜欢
work out early in the morning. A light
清晨早起锻炼。一盏灯
breakfast. And also, their best work
早餐。而且，他们最好的作品
window is usually somewhere between like
窗口通常介于两者之间，例如
9:30 and 11:30. Like, that's when all
9:30 和 11:30。就像，就在那时所有
the good stuff gets done. Like when they
好事都办成了。就像他们
have if they have to get details or if
如果需要了解详情，或者如果
they have to do brainstorming or things
他们需要进行头脑风暴或其他活动。
like that, that's really kind of where a
就像那样，那才是真正的症结所在。
lot of the magic happens for them. By
很多奇迹都会发生在他们身上。经过
about two o'clock in the afternoon,
大约下午两点钟，
there's not a lot of stuff left inside
里面剩下的东西不多了。
the lion to be able to do do a lot of
狮子能够做很多事情
good things. That's when I have lions do
好事。那时我就​​会和狮子们一起行动。
more physical activities that don't
更多不
require a lot of cognition. So maybe you
需要大量的认知能力。所以也许你
go for an afternoon walk or maybe you
下午出去散散步，或者……
have uh you know you're you're meeting
你知道，你正在开会
with your folks that may not be really
和你的家人在一起，这可能并不完全是
detail oriented but more processoriented
注重细节，但更注重流程
in the afternoon
下午
&gt;&gt; admin and stuff.
行政和其他事务。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, absolutely. I actually had one uh
是的，绝对的。我其实有一个……呃
fellow chronotype his entire company and
他整个公司都是同一种时间类型。
then move meetings based on who was
然后根据参会人员的情况安排会议。
going to be in the meeting. Like it like
我会参加会议。喜欢它
he had all the early birds and he had
他拥有所有早起的鸟儿，而且他有
meeting at 8:00 in the morning and then
早上8点开会，然后
all the night owls he had a meeting at
他与所有夜猫子开了一个会。
4:00 in the afternoon. He said it was
下午4点。他说那是
amazing. He said it worked out really
惊人的。他说结果真的不错。
really well.
非常好。
&gt;&gt; Wow. What's the next one?
哇。下一个是什么？
&gt;&gt; So the next one is the bear. So bears
接下来是熊。所以熊
are representative of people that are in
代表了处于以下状态的人们
between early birds and night owls,
介于早起鸟和夜猫子之间，
right? So bears are the best. Honestly,
正确的？所以熊是最棒的。诚实地，
dude, I wish I was a bear because the
老兄，我真希望自己是只熊，因为……
whole schedule of life works on a bear
熊的整个生活日程安排
schedule. 9 to5 is perfect for a bear.
日程。朝九晚五对熊来说简直完美。
And they make up between 50 and 55% of
它们占50%到55%
the population. So, literally one out of
人口。所以，字面上来说，只有十分之一
two people is a bear.
两个人就是一头熊。
&gt;&gt; And when's their peak work time?
他们的工作高峰期是什么时候？
&gt;&gt; So, their peak work time has a tendency
因此，他们的工作高峰期往往具有某种规律。
to be sort of in the noon to 2:00 range.
大概在中午到下午两点之间。
Um, they're a little bit later than what
嗯，他们比预期晚了一点。
you would see the line. Some of them, I
你会看到那条线。他们中的一些人，我
think, can actually be better at 11.
想想，其实11岁的时候可能会更好。
It's kind of interesting. And we've had
挺有意思的。我们已经拥有
almost 3 million people take the quiz
近300万人参加了这项测试
and we've discovered that inside of
我们发现，在……内部
bears, there appear to be early bears
熊，似乎有早起的熊。
and later bears. So there are people who
后来又出现了熊。所以有些人
fall into that category but like to get
属于这一类，但喜欢获得
up a little bit early. So for them their
起得稍微早了一点。所以对他们来说，他们的
productivity window is probably 10:30,
最佳工作时间段可能是上午 10:30。
11. But for the later bears, it's more
11. 但对于后期出现的熊来说，情况则更为复杂。
like 11:30, 12, and then it's about a
比如11:30、12点，然后就差不多是……
2hour window after that.
此后两小时的窗口期。
&gt;&gt; For the people listening, um on screen
对于正在收听的观众，嗯，还有屏幕上的观众们。
at the moment is a grid showing you the
目前显示的是一个网格，它向您展示了
different chronotypes, the weight times,
不同的生物钟类型，体重时间，
the peak work window, and the sort of
高峰工作窗口，以及那种
afternoon slump time. What's the next
午后倦怠期。接下来是什么？
chronotype?
你的生物钟类型是什么？
&gt;&gt; So, the next chronotype is me, the wolf.
所以，下一个时间类型就是我，狼。
&gt;&gt; I think I'm a wolf.
我觉得我是一匹狼。
&gt;&gt; You might be a wolf.
你可能是一匹狼。
&gt;&gt; I love lions. I get it. I get a wolf.
我喜欢狮子。我得到它。我得到了一只狼。
&gt;&gt; Well, you might be. Hey, look, join me.
嗯，你或许是。嘿，看，加入我。
It'd be great. So, wolves represent the
那太好了。所以，狼代表了
night owls, right? And so, wolves are my
都是夜猫子，对吧？所以，狼是我的
artists, my actors, my creatives. If you
艺术家们，我的演员们，我的创意人员们。如果你
know a creative, when do they get their
认识一个有创造力的人，他们什么时候会获得……
biggest idea? It's not 2 o'clock in the
最大的想法？现在还不是下午两点。
afternoon, it's 2 o'clock in the
下午，现在是两点钟。
morning. Wolves are my highest
早晨。狼是我最崇拜的动物
risktakers. I know that that probably
冒险者。我知道那很可能
you fall into that category as well.
你也属于这一类。
Wolves are the folks that show up at the
狼群就是那些出现在……的人
party at 11 o'clock at night, but they
晚上11点开派对，但是他们
stay till 2 o'clock in the morning and
待到凌晨两点
they help you clean up and they hate
他们会帮你打扫卫生，他们讨厌
mornings more than anything.
尤其是早晨。
&gt;&gt; So, should we talk about dolphins?
那么，我们应该聊聊海豚吗？
&gt;&gt; What's the next one? Yeah,
下一个是什么？是的，
&gt;&gt; dolphins. This is the category that you
海豚。这是你所属的类别
fell into. So, let's talk about who are
陷入其中。那么，我们来谈谈他们是谁吧。
the dolphins and and what does this
海豚，还有这是什么意思？
actually represent? So, dolphins are
实际代表什么？所以，海豚是
usually highly intelligent. They're
通常智商很高。他们是
usually people who are fast-talking,
通常是那些语速很快的人，
well- read. These are people who are a
博览群书。这些人是
lot like a lion in terms of they like to
很像狮子，它们喜欢……
get up. They crave longer bouts of
起床。他们渴望更长时间的……
sleep, but unfortunately their body just
睡眠，但不幸的是，他们的身体只是
doesn't have a long sleep drive and so
它没有很长的睡眠驱动期，所以
they get really frustrated a lot of
他们经常感到非常沮丧
times. Um, also I think they have just a
次数。嗯，我觉得他们也只有一个
teeny bit of anxiety behind them. So a
他们背后隐藏着一丝焦虑。所以
lot of them, for example, the details
例如，很多细节
really matter to a dolphin, right?
对海豚来说，这真的很重要，对吧？
Versus other people where details might
与其他人相比，细节可能有所不同
not matter nearly as much. I think a lot
没那么重要。我思考了很多。
of my dolphins have got just a little
我的海豚们只有一点点
bit of obsessivecompulsive disorder. So
有点强迫症。所以
they're kind of focused in on the on the
他们似乎更关注……
different things. Like if I ask a
不同的事情。比如，如果我问一个
dolphin to do a project, generally
海豚通常要完成一个项目
speaking, they're never finished with it
说起来，他们永远没完没了。
until I say, "Can you just give me the
直到我说，“你能给我……”
project back now because they're always
现在就回头看吧，因为他们总是
working on a little detail here or
正在处理一些细节，或者
working on a detail there." Um, but
正在处理那边的一个细节。”嗯，但是……
dolphins are my favorite. They're the
海豚是我最喜欢的动物。他们是
people that I actually wrote the book
我实际上写这本书的人
for. Um, they're the ones that I I enjoy
为了。嗯，它们是我喜欢的那些。
working with the most. Um, because
与最多的人一起工作。嗯，因为
they're actually the easiest to work
实际上，它们最容易操作。
with because we can once I explain to
因为一旦我解释清楚，我们就可以了。
them how their hormones can be up and
他们告诉他们，他们的荷尔蒙水平可能会升高。
down and sideways, it can it starts to
向下和向侧面，它开始……
make a lot more sense for them. And for
对他们来说更有意义。而对于
anyone trying to figure out which one of
有人试图弄清楚是哪一个
these they are, where do they go to do
这些都是他们，他们要去哪里？
the test and how long does it take?
测试内容和所需时间？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you can go to my website. It's
是的，你可以访问我的网站。它是
called chronoquiz.com.
名为chronoquiz.com。
Uh, and uh, it takes about 3 4 minutes.
嗯，大概需要 3 到 4 分钟。
It's not very long at all. It's going to
其实并不长。它将
ask you a bunch of questions about your
问你一堆关于你的问题
sleep, about timing, things like that.
睡眠、作息时间等等。
&gt;&gt; Okay, I'll put that in the description.
好的，我会把这个写进描述里。
So, after you finish listening, you can
所以，听完之后，你可以……
all go take it and let me know your
都去拿吧，然后告诉我你们的情况。
thoughts in the comments section as
请在评论区发表您的想法。
well. So, once you figure out what your
出色地。所以，一旦你弄清楚了你的
chronosype is, come back to the episode
时间线是，回到这一集
and and let me know below,
请在下方留言告诉我。
&gt;&gt; please.
请。
&gt;&gt; And does my sleep change with age,
我的睡眠会随着年龄增长而改变吗？
Michael? It does. Absolutely.
迈克尔？确实如此。绝对地。
&gt;&gt; So, do my do my chronotypes change with
所以，我的生物钟类型会随着时间改变吗？
age?
年龄？
&gt;&gt; They do, actually. So, believe it or
事实上，他们确实如此。所以，信不信由你
not, you've gone through all the
不，你已经经历过所有这些了
chronotypes already. When you're an itty
已经有了昼夜节律类型。当你还是个小不点儿的时候
bitty baby, you're a lion. You go to bed
小宝贝，你是一头狮子。你上床睡觉
really early. You wake up really early,
很早。你起得很早，
right? Then you're a toddler, right? And
正确的？那你还是个蹒跚学步的孩子，对吧？和
in in like grammar school, you're a
就像在小学一样，你是一个
bear. You're going to bed around 7:30.
熊。你大概7点半睡觉。
You're waking up around 7:30. Then
你大约在7:30醒来。然后
adolescence hits, right? What do you
青春期来了，对吧？你是什​​么
want to do? Stay up until midnight and
想做什么？熬夜到午夜
sleep until 2, right? You become a wolf.
睡到两点，对吧？你变成了一匹狼。
Then at about 23 24 your chronotype has
然后，大约在23、24岁时，你的生物钟类型发生了变化。
a tendency to set into one of those
倾向于成为其中之一
three or four things and then you stay
三四件事，然后你就留下来
there for an extended period of time
在那里待了很长一段时间
like 25 30 years until you hit my age.
大概还有25到30年就到我这个年纪了。
So I'm going to be 58 soon and right
我很快就要58岁了，对吧？
when you hit in the mid-50s what we see
当你到了50多岁的时候，我们看到
is melatonin production can either slow
褪黑激素的分泌可能会减缓。
down or get earlier. So as an example if
要么早点到，要么早点到。举个例子来说，如果
your parents are still alive and you
你的父母还健在，而你
said hey mom dad I want to go for
我说，嘿，爸爸妈妈，我想去……
dinner. What time would they want to go
晚餐。他们想几点出发
for dinner?
晚餐吃什么？
&gt;&gt; Early.
早期的。
&gt;&gt; Right? four o'clock in the afternoon,
正确的？下午四点
4:30 in the afternoon, you're like,
下午4点30分，你会想：
"What is wrong with you, mom? What's
“妈妈，你怎么了？怎么了？”
going on?" That's her chronoype is going
发生了什么事？那是她的时间线。
backwards and your sleep changes over
倒过来，你的睡眠就会发生变化
the course of time. To be clear, at once
时间的流逝。说清楚点，立刻
you hit like age probably 50, 45 or 50,
你大概到了50岁、45岁或50岁左右，
we start to see a slowdown in production
我们开始看到生产放缓的迹象。
of melatonin. We also see an increase in
褪黑素。我们还看到……的增加
what are called EEG arousals. So things
即所谓的脑电图唤醒。所以事情
that break up your sleep and make it so
这会打断你的睡眠，使你……
it's not so continuous. That can be
它并非连续不断。那可能是
problematic as well. So there's a lot of
这也存在问题。所以有很多
things that can happen as you age.
随着年龄增长可能会发生的事情。
&gt;&gt; So do I start sleeping less as I get
所以，随着年龄增长，我应该开始减少睡眠时间吗？
older? You start sleeping poorer
年纪大些吗？你的睡眠质量开始下降
quality. I'm not convinced that it's
质量。我并不确信这一点。
always less.
总是更少。
&gt;&gt; And is that going to make me grumpy?
这会让我生气吗？
&gt;&gt; Yes, it is.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Really?
真的吗？
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. Poor quality sleep is, I
绝对地。睡眠质量差是，
would argue, is much worse than poor
可以说，这比贫穷还要糟糕得多。
quantity sleep. I I would rather I've
睡眠量。我宁愿我
got somebody who got 5 hours of really
找到一个花了五个小时真正……的人
great sleep versus seven hours of really
优质睡眠与七小时真正睡眠相比
light crappy sleep every time.
每次睡眠都很浅，而且睡眠质量很差。
&gt;&gt; Does that mean that as I get older, I'm
那是不是意味着随着我年龄的增长，我会……
going to be more grumpy?
会变得更暴躁吗？
&gt;&gt; It depends on the quality of your sleep.
这取决于你的睡眠质量。
So, what I can teach you is how to not
所以，我能教你的是如何不这样做。
get poor quality sleep as you age.
随着年龄增长，睡眠质量会下降。
Perfect example, a lot of folks who are
一个绝佳的例子，很多人都是这样。
a little bit on the older side are used
稍微老一些的也用。
to drinking coffee late in the day.
傍晚时分喝咖啡。
Well, if you change that habit, then you
如果你改变这个习惯，那么你
don't have as many sleep problems.
睡眠问题不多。
&gt;&gt; And I shouldn't I shouldn't be having
我不应该，我不应该有这种想法。
coffee late in the day at all.
一天中这么晚喝咖啡，真是太可惜了。
&gt;&gt; Probably you want to stop by about 2
你可能想在两点左右过来一下。
p.m., right? So, if you stop around 2
下午，对吧？所以，如果你在2左右停下来。
p.m., the halfife of caffeine is between
下午，咖啡因的半衰期在
6 and 8 hours. So, 8 hours later is
6小时和8小时。所以，8 小时后是
roughly 10, which is roughly when people
大约10岁，这大约是人们
are kind of wanting to go to sleep. So,
有点想睡觉了。所以，
I would say that that would probably be
我觉得那很可能是
the the time to do it. I think about my
是时候去做这件事了。我想到我的
siblings and us all being woken up for
兄弟姐妹们，还有我们所有人，都被吵醒了
school and I think about my performance
学校里，我会思考我的表现。
in school
在学校
&gt;&gt; and of all my siblings, there's four of
在我的所有兄弟姐妹中，有四个
us.
我们。
&gt;&gt; I was the one that always struggled with
我一直都是那个在以下方面感到挣扎的人：
being woken up in the morning in part
早上被叫醒的部分
because I'd gone to bed later.
因为我睡得比较晚。
&gt;&gt; But then I was also the one that
但后来我也是那个人
struggled with school the most.
在学校里最挣扎。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. That characteristic of a wolf
是的。狼的那种特性
characteristic of this night person. If
这是夜猫子的特征。如果
I'm honest with you, dude, like most
兄弟，我跟你说实话，就像大多数人一样。
kids should not be waking up at the time
孩子们不应该在这个时候醒来。
they're waking up to go to school,
他们起床准备去上学。
right? I mean so many kids are waking up
正确的？我的意思是，很多孩子都醒了。
at real like you know 5:30 6:00 in the
就像你知道的，大概在5:30到6:00之间
morning they have an hourong bus ride
早上他们要坐一个小时的巴士。
then they get there and if you're an
然后他们到了那里，如果你是一个
adolescent I don't think anything could
青少年时期，我觉得什么事都可能发生。
be worse
更糟
&gt;&gt; right
正确的
&gt;&gt; so we have to really start to try to be
所以我们必须真正开始努力成为
a little bit more thoughtful and look at
再仔细想想，看看……
like what are some of the activities
例如，有哪些活动？
that kids are doing how can we get them
孩子们正在做什么，我们该如何了解他们
to maybe take naps during the day if
或许可以在白天小睡一会儿
they need them um athletic performance
他们需要它们，嗯，运动表现
can depend on sleep academic performance
睡眠质量可能影响学业成绩
can depend on sleep it's it's
取决于睡眠，这是……
unbelievable all the different things
难以置信，竟然有这么多不同的东西。
yes
是的
&gt;&gt; has there ever been any research done
之前是否有人做过相关研究？
&gt;&gt; there has on different chronotypes
存在不同的生物钟类型
academic performance.
学业成绩。
&gt;&gt; There has been actually they haven't
实际上，他们并没有
they labeled it directly as chronotypes
他们直接将其标记为时间类型
but they've looked at it based on age
但他们是根据年龄来考虑的。
range and we know that for example here
范围，我们知道例如这里
in the United States there's a big push
在美国，这股推动力非常强劲。
for to change school start times so that
为了改变学校上课时间，以便
way high schoolers aren't starting at
高中生们现在的情况并非如此。
7:00 in the morning because high schools
早上7点，因为高中
shouldn't be starting at 7 o'clock in
不应该从7点钟开始
the morning. Preschoolers should be
早上。学龄前儿童应该
starting at 7 o'clock in the morning
从早上7点开始
because their body naturally wakes up at
因为他们的身体自然醒来的时间是
that time. So, we've actually seen there
那段时间。所以，我们实际上已经在那里看到了。
was a great study um that was done at
一项很棒的研究，嗯，是在……完成的。
the University of Minnesota that
明尼苏达大学
discovered that um when they just had
发现他们当时刚刚……
people come in 1 hour later from their
人们一小时后才从……
first period, they improved by one full
第一阶段，他们进步了一个整。
letter grade, meaning they went from
字母等级，意味着他们从
being C students to being B students or
从C级学生变成B级学生
from B students to A students merely by
仅仅通过从B级学生到A级学生
changing the timing of their first
改变他们第一次的时间
class. So that should give you pretty
班级。所以这应该能给你带来相当不错的结果。
good insight as to sort of these big
对这些大问题有很好的见解。
area like and and all children are
类似这样的区域，所有孩子都是
vulnerable to this. Like this is not
容易受到这种影响。好像这不是
like I'm not telling you anything that's
就好像我什么都没告诉你一样
new. This is these are studies that have
新的。这些研究已经
been going on for quite a while. And
已经持续相当长一段时间了。和
there's actually a whole movement trying
实际上，有一整个运动正在尝试
to get school start times to to slow
让学校开始时间放慢
down now.
现在宕机了。
&gt;&gt; Looking at some of the research here, it
从这里的一些研究来看，
says research consistently shows that
研究一致表明
morning types, which is the
早起型的人，也就是
&gt;&gt; lion,
狮子，
&gt;&gt; the lion, earn higher grades not due to
狮子，获得更高的分数并非因为
higher IQ, but because exams are
智商更高，但因为考试
scheduled during their peak alertness
安排在他们警觉性最高的时候
windows. You got it.
视窗。答对了。
&gt;&gt; That's crazy.
太疯狂了。
&gt;&gt; Sometimes wolves turn out to be much
有时候，狼会表现出远超常人的一面。
smarter, but because they're they can't
更聪明，但因为他们是……所以他们不能
perform at those early times, nobody
在那些早期时期，没有人表演过
knows. Remember, wolves are my
知道。记住，狼是我的
creatives. Like, where do you think some
创意人士。比如，你觉得有些
of these create great creative
这些都能创造伟大的创意。
innovations and ideas come from in the
创新和想法源于……
tech world, right? Like, these are the
科技界，对吧？比如，这些是
wolves that are out there that are up
外面那些狼已经起来了
late at night coding and trying to
深夜还在写代码，努力尝试
figure out what's going on.
弄清楚发生了什么事。
&gt;&gt; It's pretty cool when you think about
仔细想想，这真是太酷了。
it. And I just there's this thing called
它。我只是觉得有这么个东西叫
the synchronous synchrony effect from a
来自a的同步效应
study in 2020 where nearly 800 students
2020年，近800名学生参与了这项研究。
found a clear synchrony effect. Students
发现了明显的同步效应。学生
performed significantly better when
表现明显更好
their class schedule matched their
他们的课程表与他们
chronotype.
生物钟类型。
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
确切地。
&gt;&gt; Those morning people dominated in
那些早起的人占据了主导地位
morning classes and and the owls um or
早晨的课程，还有猫头鹰，嗯，或者
the wolves often caught up and
狼群经常追上猎物，
outperformed the morning people when
比早起的人表现更好
tested in the afternoon or evening.
下午或晚上进行测试。
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
确切地。
&gt;&gt; It's pretty fascinating. Now think about
这真是太有趣了。现在想想
it like this. Could you imagine a school
就是这样。你能想象一所学校吗？
system where if we identified children's
系统，如果我们识别出儿童的
chronotypes during their particular age
特定年龄段的生物钟类型
range and then we changed the testing so
然后我们改变了测试范围，所以
that they got tested when they're at
他们在……的时候接受了检测
their peak hours?
他们的高峰时段？
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; They'd actually do better.
他们实际上会做得更好。
&gt;&gt; People don't know this, but I never do p
人们不知道这一点，但我从来不做p
podcasts in the morning.
早上听播客。
&gt;&gt; I don't blame you ever.
我从来不怪你。
&gt;&gt; You shouldn't. Yeah.
你不应该这样做。是的。
&gt;&gt; It's it's not your time. Yeah.
现在还不是你的时间。是的。
&gt;&gt; Right. Like you have a very specific
正确的。就像你有一个非常具体的
subscribed time that I think works well
我觉得订阅时间效果不错。
for you. So I think you should abide by
为你。所以我认为你应该遵守
that.
那。
&gt;&gt; Duration of sleep. There's lots of
睡眠时长。有很多
conversation around how long you're
围绕你多久的对话
supposed to sleep for. What what's the
应该睡觉。什么？
truth? Yeah.
真相？是的。
&gt;&gt; 8 hours is a myth. Let's be fair. Like
8小时工作制是个神话。公平地说。喜欢
we came up with that from like the 30s.
那是我们大概在 30 年代想到的。
There was a great study at Stanford that
斯坦福大学曾进行过一项很棒的研究，
came up with 8 hours and 13 minutes plus
计算结果为 8 小时 13 分钟加
or minus. And that's kind of where we
或减去。而这大概就是我们……
came up with that as an idea. The truth
这是我想到的主意。真相
of the matter is somewhere between 7 and
这件事的严重程度介于7和
9 hours really is kind of the amount
9个小时确实差不多够了。
that people should be looking for. But
人们应该关注的。但
some people don't have that luxury. Some
有些人就没有这种条件了。一些
people don't have that much time that
人们没有那么多时间。
they can put towards sleep and so they
它们可以用于睡眠，所以它们
get a little bit less sleep. But for the
少睡一会儿。但是对于
lower level limit, I don't like anybody
等级限制较低，我不喜欢任何人
getting less than 6 hours. When somebody
获得的时间不足6小时。当某人
gets less than 6 hours sleep, their
睡眠时间不足6小时，他们的
driving is off. And so you can't operate
驾驶功能已关闭。所以你无法操作
machinery. So if you're driving to work
机械。所以如果你开车上班的话
or god forbid, carpooling your kids to
或者，天哪，拼车送孩子去
school and you're only you only got, you
学校，而你只有你，你只有你
know, less than 6 hours of sleep on on
知道吗，每天睡眠时间不足6小时
board, it's probably not going to go
董事会，它可能不会去。
well.
出色地。
&gt;&gt; We we do have to stop here and talk
我们必须在这里停下来谈谈。
about parents because listen, you're
关于父母，因为听着，你是
either a parent now, you might be
要么你现在是父母，要么你
someday. Absolutely.
总有一天。绝对地。
&gt;&gt; Maybe you won't be. But for those I've
也许你不会。但对于那些我……
just got a huge amount of respect for
我对……肃然起敬
parents because you know I've gone I'm
父母们，因为你们知道我已经走了，我是
not a parent yet. I hope I will become
还没当父母。我希望我能成为
one. But when I see what my brother who
一。但是当我看到我哥哥的所作所为时，我……
has three kids under the age of what
有三个孩子，年龄都在几岁以内？
seven now um
现在七点了，嗯
&gt;&gt; how much sleep has he lost?
他究竟错过了多少睡眠？
&gt;&gt; A lot and and and his wife as well. But
很多，还有他的妻子。但
um you must get parents coming to you
嗯，你必须让家长们来找你。
all the time being like what the hell do
一直都在想，这到底是怎么回事？
I do? Like I've got the I've got to wake
我愿意？就像我必须醒来一样
up when the kids wake up and but I'm
孩子们醒来的时候我也醒了，但我
it's destroying my my relationship, my
它正在摧毁我的感情，我的
marriage, my sex, whatever it might be.
婚姻、我的性生活，无论是什么。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So parenting children and sleep
是的。所以，养育孩子和睡眠
are difficult to coexist, but they're
它们很难共存，但它们
not impossible. It really has to do with
并非不可能。这确实与……有关
discipline and kind of thinking through
自律和思考方式
some ideas for yourself. When my So I
给你一些建议。当我的 So I
have a 23-year-old son and a 22-year-old
我有一个23岁的儿子和一个22岁的儿子。
daughter, so I'm a little bit out of the
女儿，所以我有点不在状态
the realm of having to deal with them
必须与他们打交道的领域
every day. Um, but I was, like I said
每天。嗯，但我当时就像我刚才说的那样。
before, I was in charge of mornings uh
之前，我负责早上的工作。
at our house waking them up. And it's a
在我们家把他们叫醒。而且它
lot, right? And so the very first thing
很多，对吧？所以，第一件事
that I try to explain to parents,
我试着向家长们解释，
especially if they have a child who has
尤其是如果他们有一个孩子的话
an irregular sleep pattern and is really
睡眠模式不规律，而且确实如此。
causing chaos for the rest, like one
给其他人带来混乱，就像一个人一样
child who won't go to sleep and it's
孩子不肯睡觉，而且
keeping every the whole house up. First
保持整栋房子的整洁。第一的
thing you want to do, educate the kid,
你想做的事，就是教育孩子。
right? A lot of kids don't know what
正确的？很多孩子不知道什么
they're doing is causing a lot of
他们的做法造成了很多问题
problems. They they're just kids.
问题。他们只是孩子。
They're just hanging out having fun. You
他们只是聚在一起玩玩而已。你
know, they're they've got energy. They
要知道，他们精力充沛。他们
want to be awake. So that you want to
想保持清醒。所以你想
educate them and say, "Hey, now is a
教育他们，并告诉他们：“嘿，现在是……”
particular time to wind down. This is
特别适合放松身心。这是
where your body recovers. this is how
身体在此恢复。就是这样
you get to do sports the next day or
第二天你可以参加体育运动，或者
theater the next day or ac whatever your
第二天去剧院或者其他什么地方
computers whatever your thing is you can
无论你擅长什么，你都可以使用电脑。
tie it to sleep and performance pretty
把它和睡眠和表现联系起来
easily and so getting them to understand
容易理解，这样才能让他们明白
that becomes very very critical number
那将成为一个非常非常关键的数字
two is have some guidelines right have
第二点是要有一些指导原则。
bedtimes have wake up times and follow
就寝时间有起床时间，并且遵循
them as quick as closely as you can for
尽可能快地、尽可能近地观察它们。
parents oftentimes what I try to tell
父母常常会告诉我我试图告诉他们的事情
them to do is like look after your child
他们要做的就是照顾你的孩子
goes to bed if you've got a child that
如果你家有孩子，就去睡觉吧
has problems for sleeping
睡眠有问题
take turns. Do what I call the on call
轮流。做我所说的随叫随到工作。
method. So, as a doctor, sometimes, you
方法。所以，作为一名医生，有时，你
know, you get a call in the middle of
你知道，当你正在打电话的时候……
the night because you you're covering
因为你在掩护，所以夜晚才这样。
patients at the hospital for your buddy
你朋友在医院看病
or something like that. You're on call.
或者类似的事情。你处于待命状态。
So, when you've got two people who are
所以，当有两个人……
managing one child, one person handles
管理一个孩子，由一个人负责。
Monday night, Wednesday night, Friday
星期一晚上、星期三晚上、星期五
night, the other one handles Tuesday,
晚上，另一个负责周二，
Thursday, Saturday. You flip a coin for
星期四，星期六。你抛硬币决定
Sunday. So, if the kid wakes up at 2
星期日。所以，如果孩子凌晨2点醒来。
o'clock in the morning, both parents
凌晨一点，父母双方
aren't awake. One parent has that
还没醒。其中一位家长有
responsibility. the other one can keep
责任。另一个可以保留
their eyes closed and go to sleep.
他们闭上眼睛，睡着了。
Interesting study was done looking at
一项有趣的研究着眼于……
men and women in bed when a child cries.
孩子哭闹时，床上的男人和女人。
So women take care of the child whereas
所以女性负责照顾孩子，而
men lie there and fake sleeping in order
男人们躺在那里假装睡觉
to be able to stay asleep, right? That's
为了能够保持睡眠状态，对吧？那是
problematic. Um in a lot of
有问题。嗯，在很多方面
&gt;&gt; they know in the study that they were
他们在研究中知道他们是
fake sleeping
假睡
&gt;&gt; because they asked the men afterwards
因为他们事后问了那些男人。
what were you doing and they all said
你们当时在做什么？他们都这么说。
they woke up and they were faking it.
他们醒来后发现是在装睡。
It's pretty crazy when you think about
仔细想想，这真是太疯狂了。
it. But this is a big this is a big deal
它。但这可是件大事。
for parents, right? A lot of parents
对父母来说，对吧？很多父母
turn to me and they're like, "This is
他们转过头来对我说：“这是
killing our marriage." Like, "We haven't
“扼杀我们的婚姻。” 就像，“我们没有……”
had sex in, you know, three years
三年没性生活了
because we've got a child who maybe the
因为我们有个孩子，他可能
child has special needs or maybe the
孩子有特殊需要，或者可能是
child doesn't have special needs, but
孩子没有特殊需求，但是
has other things going on or maybe it's
他还有其他事情要处理，或者也许是……
just normal development and and you
只是正常的发育过程，而你
know, they're worried about it." And so,
我知道，他们很担心这件事。”所以，
what I like to sit down with parents and
我喜欢和父母坐下来谈谈。
do is number one, let's figure out when
做是第一要务，我们来弄清楚何时做
your kid needs to sleep and let's set
你的孩子需要睡觉了，我们开始吧
some guidelines and rules. But number
一些指导原则和规则。但数字
two, let's do the same for you.
第二，我们也为你做同样的事。
&gt;&gt; Right? A lot of parents when they're
正确的？很多父母在……的时候
super stressed out, one of the first
压力巨大，这是最早一批。
things they do, grab a glass of wine,
他们做的事情，比如喝杯酒，
right? Wine's about the worst thing you
正确的？葡萄酒是你最糟糕的东西之一
could possibly do for sleep to be fair.
公平地说，这或许对睡眠有益。
Now, I'm going to teach people how you
现在，我要教大家如何……
can still have a glass or two of alcohol
仍然可以喝一两杯酒
and not completely destroy your sleep.
而且不会完全破坏你的睡眠。
But I want to be very clear about
但我想要非常明确地说明一点：
something. If you're using alcohol as a
某物。如果你把酒精当作一种
stress relief tool at night before bed,
睡前使用的压力缓解工具
it's messing up your sleep probably
这可能影响你的睡眠。
pretty bad.
很糟糕。
&gt;&gt; You might be asleep, but the quality of
你可能睡着了，但质量……
your sleep is
你的睡眠是
&gt;&gt; is [__] It's awful, right? And
真烂。太糟糕了，对吧？和
interestingly enough, during the one
有趣的是，在一次
stage of sleep that alcohol knocks out,
酒精会使人进入睡眠的某个阶段，这种睡眠状态会让人失去意识。
which is stage three and four sleep,
即睡眠的第三阶段和第四阶段。
what's the most interesting is that dur
最有趣的是，dur
during that particular stage of sleep,
在睡眠的那个特定阶段，
there's something called the
有一种东西叫做
glimpmphatic system that comes in and
一闪而过的系统进入并
scoops out these proteins that have a
舀出这些含有蛋白质的
tendency to accumulate in your brain.
容易在大脑中积累。
And when proteins accumulate in your
当蛋白质在你的体内积累时
brain, they wrap around the nerves and
大脑中，它们包裹着神经，
that's called Alzheimer's disease.
那叫做阿尔茨海默病。
&gt;&gt; So stage four sleep is imperative to
因此，第四阶段睡眠对于……至关重要
avoid Alzheimer's disease. And when you
预防阿尔茨海默病。当你
drink alcohol, you destroy stage four
喝酒，你会毁掉第四阶段。
sleep. H.
睡觉。 H.
&gt;&gt; So, it would be great if nobody drank
所以，如果没人喝酒就太好了。
alcohol, but I'm not so stupid as to
喝酒，但我没那么傻。
think that. Plus, I like bourbon. I like
想想看。另外，我喜欢波本威士忌。我喜欢
whiskey. I enjoy a glass of champagne
威士忌酒。我喜欢喝一杯香槟。
every once in a while. So, how can you
偶尔。那么，你该如何做呢？
successfully still drink alcohol and
仍然成功地饮酒
still get a decent night's sleep? I'm
还能睡个好觉吗？我是
going to give you a quick one, right?
我给你快速解答一个问题，对吧？
Let's say you're having dinner at 6:30,
假设你晚上6点半吃晚饭，
have your first glass of wine, then have
先喝第一杯葡萄酒，然后……
a glass of water, right? Then your
一杯水，对吧？然后你的
second glass of wine starts at, let's
第二杯酒从……开始
say, almost 7:00, right? Then you have
大概快7点了吧？然后你就有
your second glass of water. Then you
你的第二杯水。然后你
stop everything by 7:30. You wait 3
7点30分之前停止一切活动。你等3
hours, which would be 10:30, and then
时间是10:30，然后
you can go to bed.
你可以去睡觉了。
&gt;&gt; Why the water? Why the weight?
为什么是水？为什么是这个重量？
&gt;&gt; So, the water helps wash it through the
所以，水有助于将其冲刷干净。
system. Also fills your stomach up so
系统。它还能填饱你的肚子
you don't have too much. So, you you've
你拥有的并不多。所以，你已经
got more fluid in there so that way you
里面灌满了液体，这样你
don't drink extra wine. Um, and it makes
不要多喝酒。嗯，而且这使得
you have to pee, which flushes the
你想小便，这会冲走……
system out as well. The 3 hours.
系统也宕机了。 3 小时。
&gt;&gt; And it hydrates you.
它还能补充水分。
&gt;&gt; It does. Okay.
确实如此。好的。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. Because remember, wine pulls
绝对地。因为记住，葡萄酒会吸引
uh both magnesium and uh most water out
镁和大部分水都出来了
of your system because it makes you have
你的系统会让你拥有
to go pee.
去小便。
&gt;&gt; Helps with the hangover. So, there's a
有助于缓解宿醉。所以，这里有一个
couple of different things that I would
有几件事我想说……
say. Number one, this definitely helps
说。第一，这绝对有帮助。
with the hangover because you've got
因为宿醉，你……
water going in. For a lot of my
水流入。对于我的很多时候
patients, what I tell them is the very
我告诉病人的就是
last thing that you could do is have a
你最后能做的就是……
little bit of coconut water. So, coconut
少许椰子水。所以，椰子
water is loaded with zinc, magnesium,
水中含有丰富的锌、镁等矿物质。
and vitamin B. And those are some of the
还有维生素B。这些只是其中的一些。
things that get pulled out of your
从你身上掏出来的东西
system uh when you're drinking. By the
系统呃，当你喝酒的时候。由
way, did you know that there are happy
你知道吗，还有快乐的人。
hours specific to your chronoype?
与您的计时器具体时间一致吗？
&gt;&gt; Didn't know that. No.
我不知道。不。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, it's kind of interesting. So
是的。所以，这挺有意思的。所以
here's what's cool about it is your body
最酷的是你的身体
produces something called alcohol
会产生一种叫做酒精的物质。
dehydrogenase which is how you
脱氢酶，这就是你
metabolize alcohol but it does it at a
它能代谢酒精，但代谢速度很慢。
particular time and the time is
特定时间，时间是
different for each chronotype.
因人而异，取决于不同的生物钟类型。
&gt;&gt; So your body is most efficient at
所以你的身体在以下情况下效率最高：
drinking between basically the hours of
饮酒时间基本上在以下时间段：
4 and 8 happy hour as a lot of people
4点和8点是欢乐时光，很多人都会去。
know it.
我知道。
&gt;&gt; And how do you think about what time you
你觉得什么时候合适？
eat at night time?
晚上吃东西吗？
&gt;&gt; Such a great question. So 3 hours before
这个问题问得好。所以提前3小时
bed, you want to stop fluids including
卧床休息，你想停止输液，包括
alcohol um and food. You want to just
酒精和食物。你只想
stop it all 3 hours before bed. So it
睡前3小时停止服用。所以它
takes your body about that level of time
身体需要大约那个时间才能达到那个水平。
to number one digest, clear all the
进入第一摘要，清除所有内容
food, and then have all the mechanisms
食物，然后具备所有机制
that are working towards digestion now
现在正致力于消化
be able to be refocused onto the
能够重新专注于
recovery process of sleep. However, I I
睡眠恢复过程。然而，我
will tell you that there's this uh I've
我会告诉你，还有这个，呃，我已经
seen a couple people and there are
看到几个人，还有
people out there that are claiming that
有些人声称
if they stop eating at 11:00 in the
如果他们11点停止进食
morning that it helps their sleep
早上起来，这有助于他们的睡眠
dramatically at night. And it turns out
夜幕降临，景象壮观。结果表明
it has to do with your heart rate. So,
这和你的心率有关。所以，
one of the big metrics that is very
其中一个非常重要的指标是
important that all of our viewers and
重要的是，我们所有的观众和
listeners want to know is you need a
听众想知道你是否需要一个
heart rate of 60 or below in order to
心率低于60次/分
enter into a state of unconsciousness.
进入无意识状态。
And when you've got food in your
当你的食物在你的
stomach,
胃，
&gt;&gt; your heart rate is up.
你的心率加快了。
&gt;&gt; That's right.
这是正确的。
&gt;&gt; So, right. So if the longer you can
没错。所以，如果你能坚持的时间越长的话……
wait, the lower your heart rate is, the
等等，心率越低，
easier it gets into sleep. And so when
这样更容易入睡。所以当
we're talking about So a great example,
我们正在讨论的是一个很好的例子，
let's get back to parents for a second,
我们再回到父母这个话题上来吧。
right? You feed your kids at an earlier
正确的？你更早给孩子喂饭。
time and then what do you do? Oh, then
然后你会做什么？哦，那
you go back and have dinner with your
你回去和你的家人一起吃晚饭
spouse, right? Maybe that's not the best
配偶，对吧？或许那不是最好的选择。
idea because you're having dinner so
因为你正在吃晚饭，所以就有了这个想法。
late. Maybe you should have dinner with
晚的。或许你应该和……一起吃顿饭
your kids, right? And and enjoy that
你的孩子，对吧？并且享受这一切。
time with them and eat earlier because
花时间陪伴他们，早点吃饭，因为
that gives you more space later on to be
这样以后你就有更多空间了。
able to relax and go to bed. I said that
能够放松下来，安心入睡。我说过
tracks because I remember I've told this
因为我记得我说过这件事，所以就跟着做了。
story once or twice before. I remember
之前发生过一两次。我记得
when I was doing some podcasts over here
我之前在这里做一些播客节目的时候
in LA, we had Seth Rogan on.
在洛杉矶，我们请来了塞斯·罗根。
&gt;&gt; Sure.
当然。
&gt;&gt; And the day before in the hotel before I
前一天在酒店，我
lived here, I had a cookie from the mini
我曾住在这里，我从迷你店里拿过一块饼干。
bar. I'm going to admit it. I had the
酒吧。我承认。我曾有过
cookie and
饼干和
&gt;&gt; they're so good.
它们太棒了。
&gt;&gt; It was And then I went to bed pretty
然后我就上床睡觉了。
quickly.
迅速地。
&gt;&gt; Oh god,
我的天啊，
&gt;&gt; we were just terrible. And I was looking
我们当时表现糟透了。我当时正在看
at my whoop the next day ad
第二天我的广告
&gt;&gt; and it my heart rate
我的心率
&gt;&gt; was like 75 or 80 for the first 2 to 3
前两到三节课大概是75或80节课。
hours after I got into bed.
我上床睡觉几个小时后。
&gt;&gt; Isn't that crazy?
这岂不是很疯狂吗？
&gt;&gt; And I woke up feeling like hell.
我醒来时感觉糟透了。
&gt;&gt; Yep.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Terrible day the next day. I was
第二天糟透了。我当时
terrible during the conversation
谈话过程中很糟糕
&gt;&gt; and I looked at my go, "Oh my god, it
我看着我的……“哦，我的天哪，它
was that cookie. It put my heart rate
是那块饼干吗？它提高了我的心率
high."
高的。”
&gt;&gt; So also on top of that is sugar.
所以，除此之外，还有糖。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I mean, [__] me. Yeah.
是的。我的天啊。是的。
&gt;&gt; Right. So sugar turn so sugar actually
正确的。所以糖会变成糖实际上
slows production of melatonin. Remember
减缓褪黑激素的分泌。记住
melatonin is kind of the key that starts
褪黑激素就像是启动的关键。
the Yeah. The key that starts the engine
是的。启动引擎的钥匙
for sleep.
为了睡觉。
&gt;&gt; So is there anything else that I can do
那么我还能做些什么呢？
to make sure my heart rate is low as I
为了确保我的心率保持较低水平，我
get into bed?
上床睡觉？
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. Meditate.
绝对地。幽思。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; Breath work. All kinds of brings my
呼吸练习。各种各样的事情都让我感到快乐
heart rate down.
心率下降。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Absolutely. So what a lot of
是的。绝对地。所以，很多
people don't realize is just because
人们没有意识到，这仅仅是因为
we're breathing doesn't mean we're
我们呼吸并不意味着我们
actually breathing in a way, shape, and
实际上，呼吸的方式、形状和
form that can be helpful for us for
对我们有帮助的表格
sleep. So, in my most recent book,
睡觉。所以，在我最近出版的书中，
Sleep, Drink, Breathe, I talk a lot
睡觉、喝水、呼吸，我话很多
about breath work and what is it and how
关于呼吸练习，它是什么，以及如何进行呼吸练习。
does it work for you. But I'd love to
它对你有用吗？但我很想
teach you my favorite form of breath
教你我最喜欢的呼吸方式。
work and meditation. Um, that I think
工作和冥想。嗯，我觉得
you'll you'll get a lot out of. So,
你会从中受益匪浅。所以，
&gt;&gt; and I do this before bed.
我会在睡前这样做。
&gt;&gt; Exactly.
确切地。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; And you can, by the way, you can do it
顺便说一句，你也可以做到。
in the middle of the night if you wake
半夜醒来
up as well. Right. So, let's talk about
也向上。正确的。那么，我们来谈谈……
how to get how to fall asleep and do
如何入睡以及如何做
some relaxation exercises for that. And
一些放松练习可以帮到你。和
then I'm gonna give you some different
然后我会给你一些不同的建议。
ones for in the middle of the night. So,
那些适合在半夜使用的东西。所以，
let's talk beginning of the night. So,
让我们从晚上开始聊起。所以，
number one, you need runway to land the
第一，你需要跑道才能降落。
plane. Okay? So many people think
飞机。好的？很多人认为
they're just waiting for their head to
他们只是在等着自己的头……
be bobbing in front of the TV and then
在电视机前晃来晃去，然后
they go brush their teeth and they get
他们去刷牙，然后他们……
in bed and then all of a sudden they're
躺在床上，然后突然间他们……
wide awake and they don't know what's
他们清醒着，却不知道发生了什么。
going on, right? So, you need time for
正在进行中，对吧？所以你需要时间
your system to shut down. It's not an
您的系统将关闭。它不是一个
onoff switch. It's more like slowly
开关。更像是缓慢地
pulling your foot off the gas and slowly
松开油门，慢慢地
putting your foot on the brake. There's
把脚放在刹车上。有
a process. It should take you about 12
一个过程。大约需要12分钟
to 15 minutes to actually fall asleep.
实际入睡需要15分钟。
Okay? So number one, what I ask people
好的？所以第一点，我问人们什么
to do is take the last hour before bed
具体做法是在睡前最后一个小时进行。
and chop it up into three 20 minute
切成三份，每份20分钟
segments, right? So let's say you're
分段，对吧？假设你是
going to bed at 11, starting at 10:00.
从晚上10点开始，晚上11点睡觉。
And by the way, set an alarm on your
对了，记得设置闹钟。
phone to to tell you that it's 10:00
打电话告诉你现在是10点。
because it's really easy to slide by
因为很容易就能溜过去。
your bedtime and then all of a sudden
你的就寝时间到了，然后突然
it's like all bets are off. So set the
一切都变得不可预测了。所以设定
alarm 20 minutes for [__] you just got
闹钟响了，还有20分钟，因为你刚收到的那些破事儿。
to do. So, in our house, it used to be
待办事项。所以，在我们家，以前是这样的
getting backpacks together for school
准备上学用的书包
for our kids, finding sports equipment,
为我们的孩子寻找运动器材，
maybe laying out my stuff for work the
或许是在整理工作用品
next day or getting last emails sent,
第二天或收到最后发送的邮件，
something like that. 20 minutes for
差不多就是这样。 20分钟
hygiene, right? Brush your teeth, wash
讲究卫生吧？刷牙，洗手
your face, maybe take a shower,
你的脸，或许该洗个澡了。
something along those lines. And then 20
大概就是这个意思。然后是20
minutes for some form of meditation,
几分钟时间进行某种形式的冥想，
relaxation, prayer. I don't care what
放松，祈祷。我不在乎什么
you do, but it has to be something
确实如此，但这必须是某种东西。
that's calming to get you there. Okay?
这样能让你平静下来。好的？
So, my one of my favorite techniques to
所以，我最喜欢的技巧之一是
do is meditation. Now, I'm going to be
要做的是冥想。现在，我打算……
honest with you. I'm a terrible
对你坦诚相待。我真是个糟糕的人
meditator. I have never been able to do
冥想者。我一直都做不到这一点。
it. I've actually gotten kicked out of
它。我其实已经被赶出去了。
meditation retreats because I'm the guy
冥想静修，因为我就是那个人
that's like, "What's going on?" Like, am
那就像是，“发生了什么事？”比如，我是
I doing it right? You know, I'm kind of
我这样做对吗？你知道，我有点
that that person. And so, I was I was
就是那个人。所以，我当时就是我。
told about this tool called a Muse
提到了一种叫做缪斯的工具。
headband. We have one right here. So,
头巾。我们这里就有一个。所以，
this is my personal Muse. I actually
这是我的缪斯女神。我其实
brought it from home. And um you'll
从家里带来的。嗯，你会
notice on the inside there are sensors
注意内部有传感器
here. And there are sensors along the
这里。沿途还设有传感器
earpiece here. And so what happens is is
耳机在这里。所以接下来发生的事情是……
you wear it on your head, right? And
你把它戴在头上，对吧？和
it's measuring your brain waves. And so
它在测量你的脑电波。所以
when we're Yeah. Check it out. And so
当我们是“是的”时。一探究竟。所以
when we're when we're doing it and we're
当我们做这件事的时候，我们
measuring brain waves. Yep. Exactly. And
测量脑电波。是的。确切地。和
that goes on the back part. Yeah. There
那是装在背面的。是的。那里
you go. So what's cool about this is
你去。所以，这件事的妙处在于……
it's attached to an app. And then while
它与一个应用程序关联。然后，当
it's measuring your brain waves, you're
它在测量你的脑电波，你
listening to a particular music. It
聆听某种特定的音乐。它
could be a guided meditation. It could
可以是引导冥想。有可能
be any of those things. And while you're
可以是以上任何一种情况。当你
doing this, the volume gets lower. And
这样做，音量就会降低。和
then you know you're getting closer to a
那么你就知道你离目标越来越近了。
meditative state.
冥想状态。
&gt;&gt; The volume comes down when
音量降低时
&gt;&gt; on the app when your brain wave starts
在应用程序上，当你的脑电波开始时
to relax.
放松一下。
&gt;&gt; Oh, okay.
哦好的。
&gt;&gt; So, you're immediately getting feedback.
所以，你能立即得到反馈。
We can try it if you want. Um, but it's
如果你愿意，我们可以试试。嗯，但是……
pretty interesting. And then when you
很有意思。然后当你
get to the alpha state, little birds
小鸟们，进入阿尔法状态吧！
start chirping.
开始鸣叫。
&gt;&gt; The alpha state.
阿尔法状态。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. The alpha state is when your eyes
是的。 α 状态是指你的眼睛
are closed and you're at the most
已经关门了，而你现在最……
relaxed state of your brain waves. It's
脑电波处于放松状态。它是
called the alpha state. And that's
称为α状态。就是这样。
really what people are trying to get to
人们真正想要表达的是什么
for meditation.
用于冥想。
&gt;&gt; And are you affiliated with this company
您与这家公司有关联吗？
in any way?
以任何方式？
&gt;&gt; I am not.
我不是。
&gt;&gt; And how much does it cost? I think it's
价格是多少？我认为是
around $275
大约 275 美元
I think is the headband.
我想应该是头带。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Interesting.
好的。有趣的。
&gt;&gt; It's pretty fascinating. Um I I've been
这真是太有趣了。嗯，我一直
pretty impressed with them.
他们给我留下了相当深刻的印象。
&gt;&gt; So that's meditation.
这就是冥想。
&gt;&gt; You talked about breath work as well
你也谈到了呼吸练习。
before.
前。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Let's talk about it. So one of the
是的。我们来谈谈这件事吧。所以其中之一
other things that I do is I do something
我做的其他事情是……
Well, this isn't breath work. This is
嗯，这不是呼吸练习。这是
called progressive muscle relaxation. So
称为渐进式肌肉放松。所以
this is where you tense and relax
这里是让你绷紧和放松的地方
muscles starting from your feet and
从脚部开始的肌肉
going all the way up your body. And as
一直延伸到你的全身。而且
you tense and relax the muscles, you
你绷紧和放松肌肉，你
feel that relaxation from releasing that
感受释放带来的放松感
tension and it helps you fall asleep.
缓解紧张情绪有助于入睡。
Um, actually, you know what I can do is
嗯，其实，你知道我能做什么吗？
I can send you a an audio file that has
我可以给你发送一个音频文件，其中包含
me walking through progressive muscle
我走过渐进肌肉
relaxation that we can make available
我们可以提供的放松方式
for everybody if you want. We for free.
如果你愿意的话，可以给所有人。我们免费。
It's no big deal.
没什么大不了的。
&gt;&gt; Amazing. I'll put that in the
惊人的。我会把它放进去。
description below as well.
下面还有详细描述。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Yeah. People will really dig it. I
是的。是的。人们一定会非常喜欢它。我
think they'll really enjoy it. So,
我觉得他们一定会很喜欢。所以，
that's another thing that we do. But
这也是我们做的事情之一。但
now, let's talk about the middle of the
现在，我们来谈谈中间部分。
night, right? So, by the way, do you
晚上，对吧？对了，你呢？
have this as an issue? Have this has
这个问题你遇到过吗？拥有这个
this happened to you before? It it
你以前遇到过这种情况吗？它
happens sometimes and it's typically
这种情况有时会发生，而且通常
when like my sleep is somewhat
当我的睡眠感觉有点……
disordered or disruptive or when there's
混乱的、扰乱秩序的，或者当有
really something on my mind.
这件事一直萦绕在我心头。
&gt;&gt; Yes. So that that precipitatory anxiety
是的。因此，这种突发性焦虑
like before a flight like if I have an
就像登机前一样，比如如果我有一个
8:00 in the morning flight like I sleep
早上8点的航班，我睡得像个孩子
like [__] the night before because I'm
前一天晚上感觉糟透了，因为我
constantly worried about that. Right.
我一直为此担忧。正确的。
But a lot of times what people do
但很多时候人们的行为
normally is they just wake up in the
通常情况下，他们只是醒来。
middle of the night and they can't
半夜他们也做不到
return to sleep and they're really not
重新入睡，他们真的不是
sure why. So number one there's biology
当然知道原因。首先是生物学。
involved. So your core body temperature
涉及。所以你的核心体温
rises rises rises and when it hits a
上升，上升，上升，当它到达……
peak it drops. That drop is then a
达到顶峰后下降。那次下降就是
signal to your brain to release
向大脑发出释放信号
melatonin. Right? Again, the key that
褪黑素。正确的？再次强调，关键在于
starts the engine for sleep. However,
启动睡眠引擎。然而，
your core body temperature continues to
你的核心体温持续升高
drop, drop, drop. By the way, this is
滴答，滴答，滴答。顺便说一下，这是
the reason why we tell people you want
我们告诉人们你想要什么的原因
to sleep in the cool, not the warm
睡在凉爽的地方，而不是温暖的地方。
environment. Because again, your core
环境。因为，再一次，你的核心
body temperature is dropping. If it's
体温正在下降。如果是
too hot, your core body temperature
太热了，你的核心体温
can't go down and you can't get to
下不去，也到不了
sleep,
睡觉，
&gt;&gt; which tracks with evolution.
这与进化相符。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. So, here's where it gets
确切地。所以，事情就发展到这里了。
interesting is it keeps going, going,
有趣的是，它一直在持续，持续下去。
going, and then at some point in time,
去，然后在某个时候，
your body has to heat up. And if it
你的身体需要升温。如果是这样的话
doesn't heat up, you go hypothermic.
如果身体无法升温，就会体温过低。
Guess what time that is? Between 1 and 3
猜猜现在是什么时间？介于 1 和 3 之间
o'clock in the morning.
凌晨一点。
&gt;&gt; Oh, your body starts heating up at 1 1
哦，你的身体从1点1分开始升温。
and 3.
3.
&gt;&gt; Every single person's body on Earth does
地球上每个人的身体都会
this. Everybody on Earth wakes up
这。地球上的每个人都醒了。
between 1 and 3:00 in the morning.
凌晨1点至3点之间。
However, most people burp, roll over,
然而，大多数人打嗝、翻身、
get comfortable, and fall back asleep in
找个舒服的姿势，然后重新睡着。
30 seconds. However, there's a select
30秒。然而，也有一部分人
group of people who end up being my
最终成为我家人的那群人
patients who don't have that. And there
没有这种症状的患者。就在那里
here in lies the problem. So, here are
问题就在这里。所以，以下是……
the steps you want to take in the middle
你想在中间采取的步骤
of the night to be able to solve this
夜幕降临，我才能解决这个问题。
issue. So number one, don't go pee. I
问题。所以第一点，别去小便。我
know, I know, I know people like, "What?
我知道，我知道，我知道有些人会说，“什么？
What are you talking about, Michael?" So
迈克尔，你在说什么？
here's what ends up happening is when
结果就是，当
people wake up in the middle of the
人们在半夜醒来
night, they say to themselves, "Well,
夜里，他们对自己说：“好吧，
I'm up. I might as well go pee." Right?
我醒了。我干脆去小便吧。对吧？
Here's the problem. Remember I told you
问题就在这里。记得我跟你说过吗？
the big metric was in order to enter
关键指标是进入
into a state of unconsciousness, you
进入无意识状态，你
need a heart rate of 60 or below. Right?
心率需低于60。正确的？
What do you think happens to your heart
你认为你的心脏会发生什么变化？
rate when you go from a lying position
从躺姿到起身时的速率
to a seated position to a standing
从坐姿到站姿
position? You walk across the room, your
位置？你穿过房间，你的
heart rate goes straight up. So what we
心率骤然上升。所以，我们
want to do is keep your heart rate down.
你要做的就是保持心率降低。
So, if you don't really have to go to
所以，如果你真的不必去……
the bathroom, don't go to the bathroom.
别去洗手间。
75% of people sleep on their sides and
75%的人侧卧睡觉，
they kind of squunch up, which means
它们有点蜷缩起来，这意味着
they're putting pressure on their
他们正在向他们施压
bladder. So, my guess is is that most of
膀胱。所以，我的猜测是，大部分
those people, if all you did was when
如果你所做的只是当……时，那些人，
you woke up is lie and get on your back
你醒来后躺下，仰面朝天。
for about 25 seconds and see if you
持续约25秒，看看你是否
still need to pee. If you don't need to
还是想小便。如果你不需要
pee, stay in bed and keep your heart
尿尿，待在床上，保持心脏稳定
rate down. If you need to pee, please go
利率下降。如果你想小便，请去
pee. Right? If you're going to go to the
撒尿。正确的？如果你要去……
bathroom, have a strategically placed
浴室，要有一个位置合理的浴室门
nightlight along the way so you don't
沿途装上夜灯，这样你就不会
have to flip on the light in the water
得在水里打开灯。
closet because if you do that, you just
衣柜，因为如果你那样做，你就会……
told your brain it's morning and it
告诉你的大脑现在是早上，然后它
stops producing melatonin. But let's say
停止分泌褪黑激素。但假设
you don't have to pee. The second thing,
你不必小便。第二件事，
don't look at your phone. Now, this
不要看手机。现在，这个
turns out to be very difficult for 99%
结果发现，这对99%的人来说都非常困难
of the people out there because the
因为外面的人们
first thing they do is they grab their
他们做的第一件事就是抓住他们的
phone and they head to the bathroom,
他们打电话过去，然后去了洗手间。
right? and they're either checking
正确的？他们要么正在检查
emails, looking at Facebook or Twitter
电子邮件，浏览 Facebook 或 Twitter
or whatever social media they're on,
或者他们使用的任何社交媒体平台，
&gt;&gt; or we're just trying to figure out what
或者我们只是想弄清楚什么
time it is
时间到了
&gt;&gt; or and that's where the problem is is as
或者说，问题就出在这里。
soon as you see the time, you instantly
你一看到时间，就立刻
do the mental math and now you're pissed
稍微算一下，你现在肯定很生气。
off, right? It's 3:30 in the morning. I
关掉了，对吧？现在是凌晨3点30分。我
got to get up at 6:00. Sleep, sleep,
早上六点就得起床。睡觉，睡觉，
sleep. And you try to force your brain
睡觉。你试图强迫自己思考
to sleep. Dude, in the history of time,
睡觉。老兄，在历史长河中，
nobody has been able to force their
没有人能够强迫他们
brain to sleep, okay? Because your heart
大脑该休息了，好吗？因为你的心
rate's going in the wrong way, right? It
利率走势不利，对吧？它
needs to be coming down. So, if you can,
需要拆除。所以，如果可以的话，
don't look at the clock. All right, so
别看时间。好的，所以
you haven't peed, you haven't looked at
你还没小便，你还没看过
the clock, but you're still awake and
时间已到，但你仍然清醒着。
nothing's going on. Here's where the
什么事也没发生。这就是……
breathing technique comes in. It's
呼吸技巧就派上用场了。
called 478
拨打478
breathing. I did not develop this
呼吸。这不是我开发的。
technique. It was developed by Dr.
技术。它是由博士开发的。
Andrew Wild, Harvard trained natural
安德鲁·怀尔德，哈佛大学训练的自然
doctor, super smart dude. Um, and uh, he
医生，超级聪明的人。嗯，还有，他
did it for the military to teach them
这样做是为了军队，为了教导他们。
how to lower their heart rate during
如何降低他们的心率
stressful situations. We use it because
压力大的情况。我们使用它是因为
it helps lower our heart rate past 60.
它有助于将我们的心率降至 60 以下。
And it's super simple. I'm going to get
而且非常简单。我要去
you to try it. So, go ahead and sit up
你也试试吧。所以，请坐起来。
straight. Okay. And so all you're going
直的。好的。所以你们都走了
to do is breathe in for a count of four.
要做的就是吸气，默数到四。
You're going to hold for a count of
你要保持这个姿势数秒
seven. And you're going to breathe out
七。然后你要呼气
for a count of eight. And I'm going to
数到八。我要……
walk you through it. I want you to have
带你一步步了解。我希望你拥有
your eyes closed. And what I also want
你闭上了眼睛。还有我想要的
you to do, you're going to go in through
你要做的，你要进去
the nose, out through the mouth. And
鼻子，从嘴巴出来。和
then what I also want you to do is
那么，我还想让你做的是……
picture the number in your head. So when
在脑海中想象这个数字。所以当
I say breathe in two, three, four, you
我说吸气，两、三、四，你
should picture the two, the three, the
应该想象这两个、三个、
four in your mind's eye. Okay?
脑海中浮现出四个画面。好的？
&gt;&gt; With my eyes closed.
我闭着眼睛。
&gt;&gt; With your eyes closed. You ready?
闭上眼睛。准备好了吗？
&gt;&gt; Yep. Breathe in. 2 3 4. Hold. 2 3 4 5 6
是的。吸气。2 3 4。屏住呼吸。 2 3 4 5 6
7. Push. 2 3 4 5 6 7 8. Good. You want
7. 推。 2 3 4 5 6 7 8. 好。你想
to get through about 20 cycles of that.
大约要完成 20 个这样的循环。
It's incredibly relaxing. I actually did
真是太放松了。我确实这么做了
it before I came out here to do the pod
在我来这里录制播客之前就做好了。
because it helps lower my heart rate and
因为它有助于降低我的心率，
gets me centered.
让我平静下来。
H. It's pretty remarkable. Now, there's
H：这真是太了不起了。现在，有
some problems with the technique. Number
该技术存在一些问题。数字
one, sometimes it's hard to hold for
第一，有时候很难坚持下去
seven, and sometimes it's really hard to
七，有时真的很难
push for eight. So, I tell people you
争取八分。所以，我告诉人们你
can do this four, five, six, 4, 6, 7, or
可以做四、五、六、4、6、7，或者
478. So, just work your way up to it,
478. 所以，一步一步来就行了。
right? If if it's too hard to hold your
正确的？如果握住它太难了
breath for 7 seconds or it's too too
屏住呼吸7秒钟，否则就太久了。
hard to push your breath for eight, you
你很难屏住呼吸八秒钟。
can do a little bit less just while
可以少做一些，同时
you're getting used to it. And then the
你渐渐习惯了。然后是
other big thing is it's hard to figure
另一件大事是很难弄清楚
out where the 20 cycles is because you
之所以会出现20个循环，是因为你
need to get to 20 cycles of this. So,
需要完成20个循环。所以，
what I have people do is take their
我让人们做的就是带走他们的
hands and make light fists while they're
双手握成轻拳，同时……
doing this. And when they do one cycle,
这样做。当他们完成一个循环后，
they put out a finger. Another cycle,
他们伸出一根手指。又一个周期，
put out a finger. And before you know
伸出一根手指。不知不觉中，你就会明白。
it, you got 10. And when you bring it
它，你有10个。当你把它带来的时候
back, you've done 20 cycles.
你已经完成了 20 个循环。
&gt;&gt; It's funny. I just did two and I start
真搞笑。我刚做了两个，然后就开始了。
yawning.
打哈欠。
&gt;&gt; I know. I just saw that. I'm telling
我知道。我刚才看到了。我正在告诉
you, dude, this thing works, right? And
哥们儿，这玩意儿能用吧？和
so, I have people do this technique.
所以，我让别人来运用这种技术。
Here's the best part is it avoids monkey
最棒的是它避开了猴子
mind, right? So, what is monkey mind?
明白吗？那么，什么是猴心？
Monkey mind is I'm thinking about stuff
我的思绪像猴子一样，一直在想各种各样的事情。
that I have no business thinking about
我根本不该去想这件事
in the middle of the night for
在半夜
absolutely no reason. Like what's on the
完全没有理由。比如上面有什么
grocery list or what did I say to my
购物清单，或者我对我的……说了什么？
spouse or did that podcast go okay or
配偶怎么样？或者那个播客节目怎么样？
any of the things that might be floating
任何可能漂浮的东西
through your head? You cannot count and
在你脑海里？你不能计数和
worry at the same time.
与此同时，我也感到担忧。
&gt;&gt; And why does it work? What's going on in
它为什么有效？发生了什么事？
my physiology? Uh-huh. You're
我的生理状况？嗯哼。你是
distracting the brain from the thing
转移大脑对那件事的注意力
that's stressing you out and it's
那让你压力很大，而且
lowering your heart rate and then the
降低心率，然后
natural sleep process comes in after it.
自然睡眠过程随后发生。
So, all these are are distraction
所以，这些都是干扰因素。
techniques to be clear. Now, there's
明确技术要点。现在，有
there's several of them out there. One
市面上有很多这样的产品。一
of the other ones I use for some of my
我还有一些其他的，用于我的
patients is I tell them, "Hey, count
我对病人说：“嘿，数数。”
backwards from 300 by threes. It's
从 300 开始倒数，每次减 3。它是
mathematically so complicated you can't
数学上太复杂了，你无法理解
think of anything else and it's so damn
想想别的什么事，真是太糟糕了。
boring. You're out like a light." On
无聊的。你睡得像死猪一样。
that point of distractions, a lot of
那个容易分心的点，很多
people go to bed listening to podcasts
人们睡觉前会听播客。
or movies. Jack was just saying that,
或者电影。杰克刚才就是这么说的。
you know, he he needs to listen to
你知道，他需要听听
something to fall asleep. I'm the same.
助眠的东西。我也是。
I listen to like serial killer stuff,
我喜欢听连环杀手之类的故事，
&gt;&gt; which is, you know,
你知道，就是
&gt;&gt; that's interesting.
那很有意思。
&gt;&gt; Don't don't judge me.
请不要评判我。
&gt;&gt; Wait till we get to the dreams part of
等我们讲到梦境部分再说吧。
the podcast. I can't wait to hear what
播客。我迫不及待地想知道……
you dream about. I
你梦见的。我
&gt;&gt; I don't I think I always try and figure
我不认为我总是试图弄明白
out why it is. And I My sister's the
找出原因。而我，我姐姐是
same, my sister Amanda, and she
我妹妹阿曼达也是，她
&gt;&gt; she listens to serial killer stuff to
她会听连环杀手相关的资料
fall asleep. I think it's because this
睡着。我认为是因为这个原因。
is just hypothesis. My mom would always
这只是假设。我妈妈总是
ask me to put on forensic files, which
请我把取证文件放上去，这
was this like serial murder documentary
这是像连环杀人案纪录片吗？
thing when we were younger cuz she
我们小时候的事，因为她
couldn't use the remote. So my mom would
遥控器无法使用。所以我妈妈会
say she'd pass me the remote, say, "Put
她说她会把遥控器递给我，说：“放
on forensic files." And I'd like put on
关于法医档案。”我想穿上
the number for her, right?
那是她的号码，对吧？
&gt;&gt; And so that was always playing in our
所以，这始终在我们心中回荡。
house at night time. And we all had TVs
夜晚的房子。我们家家户户都有电视。
in our bedroom that just mirrored what
我们卧室里那东西正好映照着什么
was ever what was playing downstairs,
楼下一直播放的是什么，
course.
课程。
&gt;&gt; So when I got into bed,
所以当我躺到床上时，
&gt;&gt; I'd watch
我会看
fall asleep.
睡着。
&gt;&gt; This explains a lot about you.
这就能解释你很多事情了。
&gt;&gt; I know, right? You say that to people,
我知道，对吧？你对别人这么说，
they think you're yours. Yeah.
他们以为你是你的。是的。
&gt;&gt; So, let me tell you what it's like in my
那么，让我来告诉你我的情况吧。
house. And actually, you and I have a
房子。事实上，你我之间有一种
commonality. So, in my house, we have a
共同点。所以，在我家，我们有一个
big screen TV. It's on all night long.
大屏幕电视。它整晚都在播放。
&gt;&gt; Where? In which room?
在哪里？在哪个房间？
&gt;&gt; In my bedroom.
在我的卧室里。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; Okay. When I met my wife, she said to
好的。当我遇到我妻子时，她说
me, "Michael, if you ever happen to
我，“迈克尔，如果你碰巧……”
spend the night, I want to let you know
今晚留下来过夜吧，我想让你知道
that I sleep with the television on." I
我睡觉时电视开着。
said, "Don't worry about that, Lauren.
他说：“别担心，劳伦。”
I'm gonna be a sleep doctor. I'm gonna
我要成为一名睡眠医生。我要
fix that." We we met when I was uh 30,
解决这个问题。”我们相遇时我大概30岁，
so uh known her for quite a while. And
我认识她很久了。和
uh you ever tried to change something in
呃，你有没有试过改变一些东西？
your bed partner? Yeah, good luck.
你的床伴？祝你好运。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, good luck. So I took the TV out.
祝你好运。所以我把电视机搬走了。
She said, "If you ever want to come back
她说：“如果你以后还想回来的话。”
in here again, I suggest you put the I
我建议你再把“I”放在这里。
put the TV back in." And then I studied
把电视放回去。”然后我就开始学习。
her to learn what was going on. And it
让她了解发生了什么事。而且它
turns out that she's listening to it out
原来她正在偷听。
of what I call the corner of her ear.
我称之为她耳角的地方。
Her eyes aren't even open. And half the
她眼睛都没睁开。还有一半
time it's a episode of Seinfeld or
有时候是《宋飞正传》的一集，或者
something like that. My wife actually
差不多就是这样。我妻子其实
likes murder mysteries and so it's
他喜欢谋杀悬疑小说，所以……
usually forensic files or something
通常是法医文件或其他什么
along those lines that's going on. But
事情正朝着这个方向发展。但
for her, it's a perfect distraction
对她来说，这是个完美的消遣。
technique. Now, there's a second thing
技术。现在，还有第二件事。
that's important uh in our bedroom that
那在我们的卧室里很重要。
happens uh is we have two dogs. They
问题是，我们家有两条狗。他们
sleep in the bed with us. I'm the
和我们一起睡一张床。我是
freaking sleep doctor, dude. Like, it's
真是个睡眠医生啊，老兄。就像，它是
insane. But the point here is sleep is
疯狂的。但重点是睡眠是
flexible. Okay? Just because it works
灵活的。好的？仅仅因为它有效。
for you doesn't mean it works for your
对你来说有效并不意味着对你也有效
bed partner. And and vice versa is also
床伴。反之亦然。
true, right? Like just because some
没错吧？就像因为某些
people can't sleep with the TV on
人们开着电视睡不着觉
doesn't mean that it's going to mess up
但这并不意味着它一定会搞砸。
your sleep forever to have the
让你永远拥有安稳的睡眠。
television on cuz it's not. And by the
电视开着，因为它没开。并且通过
way, 99% of TVs have timers built into
事实上，99%的电视都内置了定时器。
them. Like if you don't know what it is,
他们。如果你不知道那是什么的话，
ask your kid. I had to ask my son. He
问问你的孩子。我不得不问我儿子。他
showed me how to use it. We turned it
他教我怎么用。我们把它翻转了
off. It wasn't a problem, right? So
离开。这应该不是问题吧？所以
creating a sleep environment that is
创造一个良好的睡眠环境
conducive to sleep for you and your bed
有利于你和你的床的睡眠。
partner can have a lot of variation to
伴侣可以有很多变化
it. And I don't think people there's no
它。而且我不认为那里的人没有
hard and fast rule that says, "Hey,
一条铁律，意思是：“嘿，
nobody should ever sleep with the TV
任何人都不应该抱着电视睡觉。
on." I mean, there are people out there
“我的意思是，外面还有人……”
who say that, but quite frankly,
那些这么说的人，但坦白讲，
everybody sleeps with the TV on.
大家都开着电视睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Well, a lot of people do. I I I wouldn't
很多人都这么做。我不会
put the TV on in our bedroom. I mean,
把卧室里的电视打开。我是说，
we've done it once or twice or whatever,
我们做过一两次之类的，
cuz we're watching something and we slip
因为我们在看东西，然后就滑倒了。
off to sleep and I wake up and I realize
睡着后，我醒来，然后我意识到
it's on and I turn it off.
它开着，我把它关掉了。
&gt;&gt; But I I also really think it's an
但我真的也认为这是一个
important point to say that people will
需要强调的一点是，人们会
listen to podcasts like this. They'll
收听类似这样的播客。他们会
listen to the like biohackers of the
听听那些生物黑客们怎么说
world and then they'll get so militant
全世界，然后他们就会变得非常激进。
about how they fall asleep that it will
关于他们如何入睡，这将
cause friction because one partner is
造成摩擦，因为一方是
different.
不同的。
&gt;&gt; Don't do that. And I had this problem in
别那样做。我遇到了这个问题
my relationship which was
我的关系是
&gt;&gt; my girlfriend sleeps in silence and is
我的女朋友睡觉很安静，
has like just such a glorious routine to
就像这样一套精彩绝伦的日常流程
everything she does.
她做的每一件事。
&gt;&gt; And I am
而我
&gt;&gt; completely the opposite
完全相反
&gt;&gt; and the opposite like I need to like I
反之亦然，就像我需要喜欢我
want to listen to a murder. I could be
想听听谋杀案。我可能是
on my phone. It's like when I look at my
在我的手机上。就像当我看着我的
Whoop scores
Whoop得分
&gt;&gt; works for me.
对我来说没问题。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; It's like I am getting I have I get
感觉就像我得到了我拥有我得到
great sleep even if I'm listening to a
即使我在听音乐，也能睡得很好。
serial killer documentary.
连环杀手纪录片。
&gt;&gt; So
所以
&gt;&gt; but not if you eat a cookie before bed.
但如果你在睡前吃一块饼干，那就另当别论了。
&gt;&gt; Not if I eat a cookie. That's that's
除非我吃块饼干。就是这样。
gone. But I so what I do is I put one
走了。但所以我的做法是，我放一个
AirPod in in my right ear. So whichever
我的右耳戴着AirPods。所以无论
ear is not going to be on the pillow
耳朵不会放在枕头上。
&gt;&gt; and it means I can listen to her if she
这意味着如果她……我可以听她的。
says something.
说些什么。
&gt;&gt; But when it's silence, all I hear is the
但当周围一片寂静时，我听到的只有……
thing that I'm listening to.
我正在听的东西。
&gt;&gt; So I've got a trick for you.
我有个小窍门要告诉你。
&gt;&gt; And I wake up in the morning and dig the
我早上醒来，开始挖掘
AirPod out of the bed where it ended up.
AirPod 掉出了床，落在了它最终落下的地方。
&gt;&gt; Right. So now I'm going to help you with
正确的。现在我要来帮你……
the digging of the AirPod. So first of
挖掘AirPods。首先，
all, they now make these things called
现在，他们制造了所有这些东西，叫做
pillow speakers.
枕头音箱。
&gt;&gt; Oh, interesting.
哦，有意思。
&gt;&gt; Right. So it's a it's a it's a Bluetooth
正确的。所以，它就是蓝牙
speaker that will attach to your phone
可连接到手机上的扬声器
that you can just slide and it's just
你可以直接滑进去，就这么简单。
under your pillow so only you can hear
放在枕头底下，这样只有你能听到
it. So, that's number one. You might
它。这是第一点。你可能
want to consider that. And they're
我想考虑一下这一点。他们是
pretty inexpensive. Number two, they now
价格相当便宜。第二，他们现在
make specifically earbuds designed to be
专门制造专为……设计的耳塞
slept in.
睡过头了。
&gt;&gt; Oh, nice.
哦，不错。
&gt;&gt; So, there's a a new company out called
所以，现在有一家新公司叫……
Next Sense. Um, and they have developed
下一个感官。嗯，他们已经发展起来了。
an earbud that actually measures your
一款可以实际测量你身体尺寸的耳塞
brain waves while you are sleeping. And
睡眠时的脑电波。和
when you move into a lighter stage of
当你进入一个较轻的阶段时
sleep, it sends in a frequency signal to
睡眠时，它会发送一个频率信号
help you go back to sleep or to stay in
帮助你重新入睡或保持睡眠
that depth of sleep. Brand new company.
那种深度睡眠。全新公司。
Next sense. I have nothing to do with
下一个感觉。我与此无关
them. I mean, it's a friend of mine who
他们。我的意思是，这是我的一个朋友
owns the company, but I'm not on their
他拥有这家公司，但我不在他们的名单上。
own.
自己的。
&gt;&gt; I would like something to do with them
我想和他们做点什么。
&gt;&gt; if we'll figure that out.
如果我们能想出办法的话。
&gt;&gt; So, does it allow you to play your music
那么，它能让你播放音乐吗？
as well or your or your podcast or
也包括你的播客或其他内容
whatever?
任何？
&gt;&gt; I can listen to Diary of a CEO every
我可以每周都听《CEO日记》
single night while I fall asleep and it
一夜过去，我睡着了，然后……
will make sure that I don't wake up from
我会确保自己不会从睡梦中醒来
any dreams.
任何梦想。
&gt;&gt; And you can still like and subscribe and
你仍然可以点赞和订阅。
stuff.
东西。
&gt;&gt; Even through the earbuds, of course. I
当然，即使是通过耳塞也是如此。我
think everybody should like and
认为每个人都应该喜欢和
subscribe.
订阅。
&gt;&gt; That's a good feature like an AI agent
那就像人工智能代理一样，是个很棒的功能。
that helps you subscribe. Okay, so
这有助于您订阅。好的，所以
that's that's you woke up in the middle
那就是你半夜醒来的时候。
of the night. You don't pee. You don't
夜幕降临。你不小便。你没有
check your phone. You're doing these
查看你的手机。你在做这些
breathing exercises. You don't give
呼吸练习。你不给
yourself a hard time.
给自己制造了一段艰难时期。
&gt;&gt; And then what happens? It doesn't work.
然后会发生什么？它不起作用。
What do you do? Yeah. Right. So, there's
你做什么工作？是的。正确的。所以，就是这样。
the new research on something called
一项关于某种东西的新研究
non-sleep deep rest. We call it yoga
非睡眠深度休息。我们称之为瑜伽
nidra. Okay? It's been around for
尼德拉。好的？它已经存在很久了
thousands of years. When you lie relaxed
数千年。当你放松地躺着时
in like a corpse pose like this, you're
摆出像这样的尸体姿势，你
actually doing something that's valuable
真正做一些有价值的事情
for your sleep. Now, I want to be clear.
为了你的睡眠。现在，我想把话说清楚。
It's not the same as sleep, but if you
这和睡眠不一样，但是如果你
lie there for an hour, it's like 20
躺在那里一个小时，就像20分钟一样。
minutes worth of sleep. So everybody
几分钟的睡眠。所以大家
should know that even lying relaxed and
应该知道，即使是放松地躺着，
calm is very very helpful right but if
冷静确实很有帮助，对吧？但是如果
you start to get anxious and your heart
你开始感到焦虑，你的心跳也加快了。
rate starts to tick up you need to get
利率开始上升，你需要……
yourself out of bed because that's when
让自己起床，因为那时……
because all you're doing then is
因为你那时所做的只是
thinking hey this bed is this place
心想，嘿，这张床就是这个地方
where I get anxious and pissed off. This
这让我感到焦虑和愤怒。这
is not a place to sleep. So as long as
不是睡觉的地方。所以只要
you stay nice and quiet the non-sleep
你保持安静，不睡觉
deep rest absolutely the thing to do.
深度休息绝对是正确的做法。
The other big thing that I do and by the
我做的另一件大事，也是通过……
way this happens to me on occasion too
这种情况偶尔也会发生在我身上。
like I'm not immune to it just because
好像我并非对此免疫，仅仅因为
I'm a sleep doctor. You have to stay
我是一名睡眠医生。你必须留下
positive. And what I what do I mean by
积极的。而我的意思是什么？
that is everybody when they wake up in
这就是每个人醒来时的样子。
the middle of the night, your brain is
半夜时分，你的大脑……
set to negativity. There's no reason you
设置为消极模式。你没有理由
should be up at 3:00 in the morning that
凌晨三点就应该起床。
something good is going on, right?
肯定有什么好事发生了，对吧？
Nobody's coming in wishing you happy
没有人进来祝你快乐
birthday at 3:00 in the morning.
凌晨3点过生日。
Something terrible has happened. And
发生可怕的事情了。和
your brain has gotten accustomed to
你的大脑已经习惯了
that. So when it wakes up, it
那。所以当它醒来时，
immediately goes to the negative and you
立即转向负面，然后你
start thinking about bad things. You
开始想一些不好的事情。你
can't stop your first thought, but you
你无法阻止你的第一个念头，但是你
can stop your second thought, right?
可以打消你的第二个念头，对吧？
Right? And so when you wake up and you
正确的？所以当你醒来的时候
think negative, what I want you to
往坏处想，这就是我希望你做的。
replace that with is, "Okay, Michael,
把那句话替换成：“好的，迈克尔，
for some reason, your body has decided
出于某种原因，你的身体决定
to wake up at 3:00 in the morning, it's
凌晨三点起床，真是……
not the game that I wanted to be playing
这不是我想玩的游戏。
tonight. However, I think I'm going to
今晚。不过，我想我会……
be okay. I'm just going to lie here and
没事的。我就躺在这里吧。
relax and let the natural sleep process
放松，顺其自然，进入睡眠状态。
take over. If I feel my heart rate
接管。如果我感觉到我的心率
increasing, I'm going to go to another
增加，我要去另一个地方。
room in the house where I've already got
房子里我已经有的那个房间
a book and a light set up so I can do a
一本书和一套照明设备，这样我就可以……
little bit of light reading and then
读了点轻松的书，然后
come back to sleep." And I just tell
“回来睡觉吧。”然后我就告诉
myself that I give myself permission to
我允许自己这样做
just chill, just relax. And then you
放松，别紧张。然后你
know what happens? The natural sleep
知道会发生什么吗？自然睡眠
process comes over. As soon as your
过程结束了。一旦你
heart rate starts to go down, your body
心率开始下降，你的身体
wants to get back to sleep. And so it
想继续睡觉。所以就是这样。
really has a lot to do with heart rate.
这其实与心率有很大关系。
&gt;&gt; I love having these conversations on the
我喜欢进行这些对话。
diio because I have a huge amount of
因为我有大量的
sympathy and concern for people that
对那些人的同情和关心
don't get sufficient sleep. And I know
睡眠不足。我知道
there's a lot of people that don't. And
很多人都不这么认为。和
I actually think it's to some degree
我觉得在某种程度上确实如此。
it's somewhat increasing because of the
由于以下原因，它略有增加：
way we live our lives. I was looking at
我们的生活方式。我当时正在看
some of the stats around the increase
关于增长的一些统计数据
and there's a study done in 2025 and
还有一项研究计划在2025年进行，
early 2026 that revealed we're in a
2026年初揭示了我们正处于一个
global sleep crisis.
全球睡眠危机。
&gt;&gt; Oh yes, we are.
是的，我们是。
&gt;&gt; Both the CDC and Stanford Medicine
美国疾病控制与预防中心和斯坦福大学医学院
report said that one in three adults and
报告称，三分之一的成年人和
nearly 80% of teenagers are now
近80%的青少年现在
chronically sleepdeprived.
长期睡眠不足。
&gt;&gt; Correct. A 2026 survey by the American
正确的。美国2026年的一项调查
Academy of Sleep Medicine found that 93%
美国睡眠医学会发现，93%
of Gen Z admit to regularly losing sleep
Z世代承认经常失眠
due to social media usage. And 71% of
由于社交媒体的使用。 71%
employed respondents globally have said
全球受访的就业人员表示
&gt;&gt; that they sometimes call in sick at
他们有时会打电话请病假
least once or twice due to poor sleep.
至少一两次是由于睡眠不足引起的。
&gt;&gt; Just to sleep. Yeah. When I was down in
只想睡觉。是的。当我身处低谷时
Australia doing some work down there, a
澳大利亚在那边做了一些工作，
lot of Australians they take holiday and
很多澳大利亚人会去度假，
they just sleep.
它们只是睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Just to catch up. Like it's it's pretty
只是为了跟上进度。它很漂亮
remarkable. We're in a very sleep-d
卓越。我们处于一种非常困倦的状态
deprived society and I think there's a
这是一个贫困的社会，我认为存在着……
couple of different reasons why that is.
原因有二。
Number one,
第一，
&gt;&gt; have you seen what's going on outside in
你看到外面发生了什么事吗？
the world today? It's pretty crazy out
当今世界是什么样的？外面真是太疯狂了。
there. Well, I can understand why people
那里。嗯，我能理解为什么人们
are getting a little anxious.
有点焦虑了。
&gt;&gt; I think one could argue it's been
我认为有人可能会说，这种情况已经发生了。
crazier through history, but we never
历史上曾出现过更疯狂的事件，但我们从未经历过。
knew about it,
我知道这件事，
&gt;&gt; right? Well, I mean, the media getting
正确的？嗯，我的意思是，媒体正在……
it to getting us this information so
它帮助我们获取这些信息。
quickly, I think, is definitely what I
我觉得，很快，这绝对是我要做的。
would agree with you. It was much
我同意你的看法。非常多
crazier during like World War II, you
二战时期更疯狂，你
know, and stuff like that. Now we're
知道，诸如此类的事情。现在我们是
getting information so quickly and
如此迅速地获取信息
people are getting so ratcheted up about
人们对此事反应如此激烈
it. I think that has something to do
它。我认为这与此有关
with it. But if I I think the bigger
和它一起。但如果我考虑更大的问题。
culprit is people being overweight. You
罪魁祸首是人们超重。你
know, when you look here in the United
你知道，当你在这里，在美国的时候。
States and you look at the obesity
各州，看看肥胖问题。
epidemic and you look at people being
疫情爆发，你看看人们的情况
overweight, it's something close to like
超重，差不多就是这种感觉。
70s something percent of people in
70% 的人
America are overweight. When you're
美国人普遍超重。当你
overweight, that puts you in line for
超重会让你面临……
potentially having something called
可能患有某种疾病
sleep apnea. Now, I want to be clear,
睡眠呼吸暂停。现在，我想明确一点，
not everybody with sleep apnea is
并非所有患有睡眠呼吸暂停症的人都是
overweight, but a a large percentage of
超重，但很大一部分
the people with sleep apnnea are bigger
患有睡眠呼吸暂停的人体型更大。
people. And so, when you look at a
人们。所以，当你观察一个
society that's getting bigger and all
社会规模越来越大等等
the unhealthy food that we've got going
我们现在吃的都是些不健康的食物。
on, like all this highly processed food,
就像所有这些高度加工的食品一样，
things of that nature, that isn't
诸如此类的事情，那不是……
helping anybody, it's adding the pounds.
帮助任何人，都会增加体重。
And specifically, like for men, we gain
具体来说，就像男性一样，我们获得了
weight through our necks. Like I I don't
脖子上压着重物。就像我，我不
know if you've ever noticed it, but like
不知道你有没有注意到，但是就像
if you ever were heavy and you lose
如果你曾经很胖，然后你减肥了
weight, the first thing somebody says
体重，人们说的第一句话
is, "Oh, it looks like you lost weight
是，“哦，看起来你瘦了”
cuz I can tell from your face, right?"
因为我从你的表情就能看出来，对吧？
and they're like, "Oh, your neck looks,
他们会说：“哦，你的脖子看起来……”
you know, different now." And so, we see
你知道，现在不一样了。”所以，我们看到
a lot of what's going on in the world
世界上正在发生的很多事情
from a weight perspective and a food
从体重和食物的角度来看
perspective could be driving some of the
视角可能是某些因素驱动的。
sleep problems. Then there's the anxiety
睡眠问题。然后还有焦虑。
perspective that I spoke of earlier that
我之前提到的那种观点
I think comes in. And again, I I agree
我觉得他进来了。而且，我再次同意。
with you. I don't think we have more
与你。我不认为我们还有更多。
crazy stuff going on. I think we know
真是乱成一团。我想我们都知道
about more crazy stuff that's going on,
关于更多正在发生的疯狂事情，
&gt;&gt; but also work is now largely digital.
但现在的工作也大多是数字化的。
And I imagine for my great-grandfather,
我想，对于我的曾祖父来说，
he would go to, I don't know, the
他会去，我不知道，那个
factory or wherever he works. His work
工厂或者他工作的任何其他地方。他的作品
would finish at 6.
最终会停在6点。
&gt;&gt; Yes. Your work doesn't finish at 6 now.
是的。你的工作现在不是6点就结束了。
It finishes when you're awake.
它会在你醒来的时候结束。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Absolutely. It finishes when you
是的。绝对地。当……时结束
go to sleep.
睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Exactly.
是的。确切地。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. And and that becomes problematic,
是的。这就成了问题。
right? Because a lot of times also, by
正确的？因为很多时候，也是通过
the way, you need to have dividers in
顺便说一下，你需要用分隔线。
your home. Like let's say you live in a
你的家。比如说，你住在……
studio apartment and your bed is your
单身公寓，你的床就是你的
couch is your kitchen, right? You have
沙发就是你的厨房，对吧？你有
no designated spot for sleep. Your body
没有专门的睡觉地点。你的身体
needs to know, hey, this is the spot
需要知道，嘿，就是这里
where I can chill out and finally get
一个我可以放松身心，最终获得
some rest. And I think a lot of times
休息一下。而且我觉得很多时候
our environments just aren't that way.
我们的环境并非如此。
So many of us are pursuing passive forms
我们当中很多人都在追求被动形式
of income and to build side businesses
增加收入并发展副业
in order to help us cover our bills. And
为了帮助我们支付账单。和
that opportunity is here with our
机会就在眼前！
sponsor Stan, a business that I co-own.
赞助 Stan，这是我共同拥有的企业。
It is the platform that can help you
这是一个可以帮助你的平台
take full advantage of your own
充分利用你自己的优势
financial situation. Stan enables you to
财务状况。 Stan 使您能够
work for yourself. It makes selling
为自己工作。它使销售变得容易
digital products, courses, memberships,
数字产品、课程、会员资格、
and more simple products more scalable
更简单的产品，更具可扩展性
and easier to do. You can turn your
而且更容易做到。你可以把你的
ideas into income and get the support to
将想法转化为收入并获得支持
grow whatever you're building. And we've
无论你建造什么，都要让它生长壮大。我们已经
just launched Dare to Dream. It's for
刚刚推出了“敢于梦想”项目。这是为了
those who are ready to make the shift
那些准备好做出转变的人
from thinking to building, from planning
从构思到建造，从规划
to actually doing the thing. It's about
真正去做这件事。这是关于
seeing that dream in your head and
在脑海中看到那个梦境
knowing exactly what it takes to bring
确切地知道带来什么
it to life. It's not too late to join
赋予它生命。现在加入还不晚。
the challenge. Enter to win $100,000.
挑战。参与活动赢取10万美元奖金。
Visit daretodream.stan.store.
访问 daretodream.stan.store。
I've had so many founders speak to me
很多创始人跟我交流过。
and say, "Why didn't this particular ad
然后问：“为什么这个广告没有成功？”
that I ran on this platform work for
我在这个平台上运行的工作
me?" Maybe the copy wasn't good. The
我？”也许是文案写得不好。
creative wasn't strong. But usually the
创意能力不强。但通常情况下
problem is they're not having the right
问题在于他们没有获得应有的权利。
conversation because that ad never
因为那则广告从未引发过对话
reached the right person. And if you're
联系对了人。如果你是
in B2B marketing, that is much of the
在B2B营销中，这占据了很大一部分。
game. And this is where LinkedIn ads
游戏。这就是LinkedIn广告的投放位置。
solves that problem for you. Their
帮你解决这个问题。他们的
targeting is ridiculously specific. You
目标定位精准得离谱。你
can target by job title, seniority,
可以按职位、资历进行筛选
company size, industry, and even
公司规模、行业，甚至
someone's skill set. And their network
某人的技能组合。以及他们的网络
includes over a billion professionals.
其中包括超过十亿专业人士。
About 130 million of them are decision
其中约有1.3亿人正在做决定
makers. So when you use LinkedIn ads,
制造商。所以，当你使用LinkedIn广告时，
you're putting your brand in front of
你正在将你的品牌置于……之前
the right people. And LinkedIn ads also
合适的人选。 LinkedIn广告也
drive the highest B2B return on ad spend
实现最高的 B2B 广告支出回报率
across all ad networks in my experience.
就我的经验而言，在所有广告网络中都是如此。
If you want to give them a try, head
如果你想尝试一下，请前往
over to linkedin.com/diary.
转到 linkedin.com/diary。
And when you spend $250 on your first
当你第一次消费满 250 美元时
LinkedIn ads campaign, you'll get an
LinkedIn广告活动，您将获得
extra $250 credit from me for the next
我额外提供 250 美元信用额度，供下次使用。
one. That's linkedin.com/diary.
一。那是 linkedin.com/diary。
Terms and conditions apply.
须遵守相关条款和条件。
&gt;&gt; Which sleep disorder should we start
我们应该从哪种睡眠障碍入手？
with?
和？
&gt;&gt; Sleep apnea and insomnia. Sleep apnea,
睡眠呼吸暂停和失眠。睡眠呼吸暂停症
for folks out there who may not know
对于那些可能不了解的人来说
what it is, is when you are snoring at
这就是打鼾的时候。
night. Almost everybody who has sleep
夜晚。几乎所有有睡眠的人
apnea snores. Not everybody, but almost
睡眠呼吸暂停引起的打鼾。并非所有人，但几乎
everybody. And when you're sucking air
所有人。当你吸气的时候
in, you pull your tongue to the back of
进去的时候，你要把舌头拉到舌头的后部。
your throat and you cut off your air.
你的喉咙被堵住了，你呼吸困难。
And you literally stop breathing, right,
然后你就真的停止呼吸了，对吧？
for a few seconds. And then all a sudden
持续几秒钟。然后突然
you and you make all this kind of
你，还有你，让这一切变得如此……
grunting, groaning noises. and then you
哼哼唧唧、呻吟声。然后你
wake up. This can happen hundreds of
醒醒。这种情况可能发生数百次。
times a night and it can be very
一晚上好几次，而且可能非常
problematic because of course it wakes
这当然是个问题，因为它会唤醒……
you up every single time that you have
你每次都振作起来，你……
one of these events, right? And so as an
是其中一项活动吗？因此，作为一个
example, we measure the events per hour.
例如，我们以每小时为单位统计事件数。
So as an example, somebody with sleep
举个例子，睡眠不足的人
apnnea could have between five and 15
睡眠呼吸暂停可能持续五到十五年。
times per hour that they stop breathing
每小时停止呼吸的次数
and that's mild.
这还算温和的。
&gt;&gt; So how are they going to get into the
那么他们要如何进入呢？
deep sleep that clears out their brain?
深度睡眠能让大脑彻底清醒吗？
&gt;&gt; That's the problem, right? And so apnea
这就是问题所在，对吧？所以，睡眠呼吸暂停
prevents them from getting into a lot of
防止他们陷入很多困境
that deep sleep. And so their brain
深度睡眠。所以他们的大脑
doesn't clear out and then they got
没能清除干净，然后他们就……
they're they're kind of screwed. So at
他们有点儿倒霉了。所以，在
the end of the day, the the goal here is
归根结底，我们的目标是……
to get as many people to number one
让尽可能多的人登上第一名
identify if they have a sleep disorder
确定他们是否患有睡眠障碍
and then be able to try to figure out
然后能够尝试弄清楚
what to do about it. And the percentage
该怎么办？以及百分比
of people in the US that have
美国有……的人
undiagnosed sleep apnea is pretty big.
未确诊的睡眠呼吸暂停症病例相当多。
It's like somewhere between I think like
我觉得它介于两者之间……
18 to 20%.
18%至20%。
&gt;&gt; This is crazy. I was just looking at the
这太疯狂了。我刚才在看……
stats. It says according to 2026 data
统计数据。报告称，根据2026年的数据。
approximately
大约
million people to 1 billion adults
百万人口到10亿成年人
worldwide have obstructive sleep apnnea
全世界都有阻塞性睡眠呼吸暂停症患者
which is what one in seven
也就是七分之一。
&gt;&gt; yeah that's about right
嗯，差不多就是这样。
&gt;&gt; making it as common as diabetes. One in
使其像糖尿病一样常见。一
seven people listening have sleep
七个人在听，他们睡着了
apnnea.
睡眠呼吸暂停。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Wow.
哇。
&gt;&gt; As popular as diabetes. Let that sink in
与糖尿病一样普遍。好好想想。
for like half a second. Everybody knows
大概持续了半秒钟。人人都知道
what diabetes is. Almost nobody knows
什么是糖尿病？几乎没人知道
what sleep disorders are. Specifically
什么是睡眠障碍？具体来说
sleep apnnea. And it says 80 to 90% of
睡眠呼吸暂停。报告称，80%到90%
those people remain undiagnosed. That is
这些人仍未确诊。那是
correct.
正确的。
&gt;&gt; So there's people listening right
所以有人在听，对吧？
there's actually a huge percentage of
实际上有很大比例
people listening right now
现在正在收听的人们
&gt;&gt; that have sleep apnea and have no idea
患有睡眠呼吸暂停症却毫不知情的人
that they have it.
他们有。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. Right.
确切地。正确的。
&gt;&gt; How would they know?
他们怎么会知道？
&gt;&gt; Do the sleep test.
做睡眠测试。
&gt;&gt; This thing here.
就是这个东西。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; And what would this show?
那这会展现什么呢？
&gt;&gt; So this would this actually collects
所以这实际上会收集这些信息。
what is your oxygen levels throughout
你的血氧水平如何？
the night? What is your heart rate
夜晚？你的心率是多少？
throughout the night? How many times do
整夜？多少次
you actually stop breathing? And also
你真的停止呼吸了吗？而且
the depth of your sleep, which stages of
你的睡眠深度，你睡眠的阶段
sleep you get when you fall asleep,
你入睡后所获得的睡眠，
things like that. And what would this
诸如此类的事情。那又会怎样呢？
So, you know, because people are going
所以，你知道，因为人们要去
to be like, "How do I know if I need to
比如，“我怎么知道我是否需要……”
do the test?"
做测试吗？
&gt;&gt; So, great question. So, you want to
问得好。所以你想
think about the symptoms that you might
想想你可能出现的症状。
have. So, do you snore? Do you wake up
有。你打鼾吗？你醒来了吗？
gasping for air? Has anybody told you
喘不过气来？有人告诉过你吗？
that your snoring stops for brief
你的鼾声短暂停止
periods of time or that they've heard
一段时间内，或者他们听说过
you gasping for air? Do you wake up with
你呼吸困难吗？你醒来时是否……
a headache in the morning? Do you find
早上头疼？你觉得
your moods are up and down? All of those
你情绪起伏不定吗？所有这些
are signs and symptoms of sleep apnnea.
是睡眠呼吸暂停的体征和症状。
&gt;&gt; And this test, are you affiliated with
这项测试，你与……有关联
this company at all? I am not. But um we
这家公司到底怎么样？我不是。但是，嗯，我们
do have that test on my website. We sell
我的网站上有那个测试。我们出售
it to people so that way we can test
它被传递给其他人，这样我们就可以进行测试了。
them.
他们。
&gt;&gt; And how much does it cost?
价格是多少？
&gt;&gt; $189.
189美元。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So it's not
好的。所以并非如此
&gt;&gt; it's not exorbitantly expensive. And it
价格并不算太贵。而且它
also is covered by insurance.
也在保险范围内。
&gt;&gt; And it connects to an app.
它可以连接到一个应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh. Absolutely. So you'd put it
嗯哼。绝对地。所以你会这么说
through your sleeve.
透过你的袖子。
&gt;&gt; So I' I'd put that there and like this.
所以我会把它放在那里，像这样。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Exactly. And that's it. You go to
是的。确切地。就这样。你去
bed, wake up, then the information ports
睡觉，醒来，然后是信息端口
over to your phone and then tells us
然后拿起手机告诉我们
exactly what's going on. Now, here's
到底发生了什么？现在，是这样的
where it gets even better. I know,
更精彩的还在后面。我知道，
right?
正确的？
&gt;&gt; Can you imagine me getting in bed with
你能想象我和……上床吗？
my fiance and being like, "Come on,
我未婚夫说：“拜托，
babe. Let's
宝贝。我们开始吧
&gt;&gt; We're recording all kinds of good stuff.
我们正在录制各种各样的好东西。
Who knows what she might like?
谁知道她会喜欢什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Is this going to help my sex life?"
这会改善我的性生活吗？
&gt;&gt; It's absolutely it will because getting
绝对会，因为获得
into bed and knowing how well you sleep
躺到床上，知道自己睡得如何
and knowing if you have sleep apnea or
以及了解你是否患有睡眠呼吸暂停症
not will definitely affect your sex
不会影响你的性生活
life. Also, by the way, I've saved more
生活。顺便说一句，我已经存了更多钱了。
marriages as a sleep doctor than I ever
作为一名睡眠医生，我比任何人都更了解婚姻。
would have as a marital therapist
曾担任婚姻治疗师
dealing with snoring in the middle of
应对打鼾问题
the night and things like that. So,
夜晚之类的事情。所以，
you'd be you'd be surprised. But what's
你会感到惊讶的。但是，什么是……
nice about this is it's one night. You
好处是只有一晚。你
don't have to do it multiple nights.
不必连续几个晚上都这样做。
It's super easy. Um, and again, believe
非常简单。嗯，还有，再次强调，相信
it or not, that's disposable. You can
不管是不是，那都是一次性的。你可以
actually throw that whole thing away
把那整个东西都扔掉吧
after it's all said and done.
一切尘埃落定之后。
&gt;&gt; And on that point, before we just go a
关于这一点，在我们继续之前……
little bit further into sleep apnnea,
对睡眠呼吸暂停症有了更深入的了解，
should should we be sleeping in bed with
我们应该和……睡在一张床上吗？
our partners? And I know that's an
我们的合作伙伴？我知道那是一个
interesting thing.
有趣的事。
&gt;&gt; Great question. Great question. The
问得好。问得好。这
strength of your relationship has
你们关系的牢固程度
nothing to do with where you sleep.
这跟你睡在哪里无关。
Okay? So, lots of people are like, "I
好的？所以，很多人都会说：“我
got to sleep with my partner otherwise
否则就得和我的伴侣睡觉。
my relationship's going to go to [__]
我的关系要完蛋了。
and everything's going to go terrible
一切都会变得很糟糕。
and we're never going to have sex and
我们永远不会发生性关系。
we're not true." Okay. So, a lot of
我们并不真实。”好吧。所以，很多
times for people that I have, so for
对于我认识的人来说，时间就是如此，所以对于
example, I've got people who um have
例如，我认识一些人，他们……有
sleep apnnea and they use a a machine to
睡眠呼吸暂停症患者使用机器进行治疗。
help them sleep called a CPAP machine,
帮助他们入睡的呼吸机叫做CPAP呼吸机，
right? And um that noise for some people
正确的？嗯，有些人觉得那种噪音很刺耳。
can be disruptive and so they sleep,
可能会扰乱他们的睡眠，所以他们会睡觉。
let's say, in a different room, right?
比如说，在另一个房间里，对吧？
So, is that is that detrimental to your
所以，这对你真的那么不利吗？
marriage? No, it's not. Because here's
婚姻？不，不是。因为这里是
what you do is you vacation on the
你所做的就是去度假
weekends in your bedroom, right? I can't
周末都待在卧室里，对吧？我不能
count the number of people who sleep
统计睡觉的人数
separately during the week and then
在一周内分别进行，然后
together on the weekends. And it turns
周末一起度过。然后它就变了
out that they get much better sleep
结果发现他们睡眠质量更好
during the week. And then guess what?
工作日期间。然后你猜怎么着？
Intimacy shows up much faster on the
亲密关系在……上表现得更快。
weekends because they're not so tired.
周末他们不太累。
Used to be, you know, not tonight I have
以前是这样，你知道，但今晚不行了。
a headache. It was really not tonight
头痛。今晚真的不是那样。
I'm exhausted. When you allow your
我累极了。当你允许你的
partner to get good sleep during the
伴侣在睡眠期间也能睡个好觉
week, there's a reasonably good shot
本周，有一次相当不错的机会。
that you're going to be able to be
你将能够成为
intimate over the weekend if they got
如果他们周末有亲密关系的话
good sleep. So, wearing that to bed
睡个好觉。所以，穿着那件衣服睡觉
might not be the sexiest thing in the
这可能不是最性感的事
universe, but it's better than having
宇宙，但总比没有好。
sleep apnnea and eventually ending up
睡眠呼吸暂停，最终导致
dead.
死的。
&gt;&gt; Are the symptoms of sleep apnnea
睡眠呼吸暂停的症状有哪些？
different for men and women?
男女之间有什么区别？
&gt;&gt; They are. Great question. So, it turns
没错。问得好。所以，事情就是这样。
out that men and women are quite
这表明男人和女人都相当
different, but we've historically been
虽然有所不同，但我们历来如此
scoring them the same. So women don't
给他们相同的分数。所以女性不会
have a tendency to have as much snoring
容易打鼾
as men do. Um women have a tendency to
就像男人那样。嗯，女性往往有这种倾向
have more arousals where they wake up
醒来后更容易受到刺激
constantly. Women have a tendency to
不断地。女性往往有以下倾向
report headaches in the morning more so
早上头痛的情况更为常见
than men do. So it's actually different
比男性做得更多。所以实际上有所不同。
types of symptoms for women versus men
女性与男性症状类型差异
when it comes to sleep apnea to the
说到睡眠呼吸暂停症……
point where we're now considering using
我们现在正在考虑使用这一点
different testing devices. So this
不同的测试设备。所以这
testing device um would not necessarily
测试设备不一定
measure EEG and in women EEG might be
测量脑电图，女性脑电图可能
important. That's what we're learning.
重要的。这就是我们正在学习的。
So, as an example, our company is
例如，我们公司是
finding a device specifically to send to
找到专门用来发送的设备
women so that way we can more accurately
这样我们就能更准确地了解女性了。
measure sleep apnea in women. Now,
测量女性睡眠呼吸暂停症。现在，
there's a lot of questions about
关于这个问题有很多疑问。
treatment for sleep apnea. And the
治疗睡眠呼吸暂停症。以及
biggest reason why nobody gets sleep
导致大家睡不着觉的最大原因
tested is because they're afraid that
接受测试是因为他们害怕
they're going to end up sleeping with a
他们最终会和……睡觉
CPAP machine on their face at night. And
他们晚上睡觉时脸上戴着呼吸机。和
so, let me describe to your audience
那么，让我来向你们的听众介绍一下。
what that is. Also, full disclosure, I
那是什么？另外，坦白地说，我
have sleep apnea. I don't look like
患有睡眠呼吸暂停症。我看起来不像
somebody who has sleep apnea. I stop
患有睡眠呼吸暂停症的人。我停了下来
breathing in my sleep. I think it's 26
睡梦中呼吸。我认为是26
times an hour. I know, right? Kind of
每小时。我知道，对吧？有点儿
crazy. And I wear a CPAT machine and it
疯狂的。我戴着一台CPAT（心肺复苏）仪，它
helps me sleep every single night. Let
它让我每晚都能睡个好觉。让
me explain what it is. So, when your
让我解释一下它是什么。所以，当你
throat closes here, CPAT machine is a
喉咙在此处闭合，CPAT 机器是
little air compressor with a tube and a
小型空气压缩机，带软管和
mask that sits on your nose, pushes a
戴在鼻子上的口罩，推入一个
just thin stream of just air, and when
只是一股细细的气流，当
it hits that blockage, it ever so
它撞上了那个堵塞物，它总是
slightly opens it up, shoots air
稍微打开，喷出空气
straight down to your lungs. Now, you
直达肺部。现在轮到你
might be saying to yourself, "That
你可能会对自己说：“那
sounds barbaric. That is insane. That's
听起来很野蛮。这太疯狂了。那是
a haird dryer blowing up my nose all
吹风机对着我的鼻子吹风
night long. Here's what I can tell you
彻夜未眠。我可以告诉你的是
is when you have a severe case of sleep
就是你患有严重睡眠障碍的时候
apnea, this can be a lifesaver. This can
睡眠呼吸暂停，这可以救命。这可以
be one of the biggest, most important
成为规模最大、最重要的机构之一
things that you possibly do. Now, a lot
你可能会做的事情。现在，很多
of people say, "Oh, I don't think I
很多人说：“哦，我不认为我
could sleep with a mask on my face."
我可以戴着眼罩睡觉。
Well, that's not the only treatment.
嗯，这并不是唯一的治疗方法。
There are other treatments called oral
还有其他一些治疗方法，称为口服疗法。
appliances. This is like a a mouthguard
家用电器。这就像一个护齿器
like you see the footballers wear, but
就像足球运动员穿的那种衣服一样，但是
it's an upper and a lower. and the lower
它分为上衣和下衣。以及较低的
slowly brings your jaw forward which
慢慢地将下巴向前移动，
opens up your posterior airway space.
打开后气道空间。
The same way that air pushes things
就像空气推动物体一样
aside, the oral appliance structurally
除此之外，口腔矫治器的结构
moves your jaw slightly forward thereby
从而使你的下巴略微向前移动
opening up your airway. So that works
打开你的呼吸道。这样就行了。
well and there's no mask on your face.
而且你脸上没戴口罩。
There's a third device that you can wear
还有第三种可以穿戴的设备。
on your tongue that vibrates that
你舌头上那种震动的感觉
shrinks your tongue by a couple of
让你的舌头缩短几英寸
millimeters which opens up this
毫米，这便打开了这一点。
posterior airway space and allows you to
后气道空间，并允许您
breathe better.
呼吸更顺畅了。
&gt;&gt; Have you tried all of them?
你都试过了吗？
&gt;&gt; I have as a matter of fact. And why did
事实上，我已经有了。为什么会这样？
you choose the apnea machine?
你选择睡眠呼吸暂停治疗机吗？
&gt;&gt; So for me, the apnea machine worked the
所以对我来说，睡眠呼吸暂停机确实有效。
best and made the most sense for me
对我来说，这是最好也是最合理的。
right now. But I'll be honest with you,
现在。但我得跟你说实话，
I will probably get the uh mouthguard
我大概会买个牙套。
for when I travel. There's a lot that
方便我旅行时使用。有很多
can be done out there. And by the way,
在那里是可以做到的。顺便说一句，
there's also surgeries and surgeries are
还有手术，手术就是
a little bit more permanent fix. Um, but
一个更持久的解决方案。嗯，但是
in many cases, those surgeries can be
在许多情况下，这些手术可以
quite effective. Also, by the way,
效果很好。另外，顺便提一下，
they're working on a pill
他们正在研发一种药丸
&gt;&gt; for sleep apnnea now. And that's just
现在就来治疗睡眠呼吸暂停症。仅此而已
apnea. We haven't even talked about
睡眠呼吸暂停。我们甚至还没谈到……
insomnia yet.
失眠症尚未痊愈。
&gt;&gt; I was just reading about the FDA
我刚才在看关于FDA（美国食品药品监督管理局）的资料。
approving a drug. Yeah, it's it's quite
批准一种药物。是的，相当
remarkable. And there's actually two I
卓越。实际上有两个我
think there's actually three different
我认为实际上有三种不同的
companies that are working on different
从事不同工作的公司
drugs right now for sleep apnea. And I
目前治疗睡眠呼吸暂停的药物。我
mean to be clear, when that happens, I
我的意思是说清楚点，当这种情况发生时，我
think it's pretty much game over for
我觉得这基本上已经结束了。
sleep apnea, right? I mean once we can
是睡眠呼吸暂停吗？我的意思是，一旦我们能够
get it in a pill form, which means
服用药片形式，这意味着
compliance increases dramatically, we
合规性显著提高，我们
can help a lot of people with sleep
可以帮助很多人改善睡眠
apnea, which I think would be pretty
睡眠呼吸暂停，我认为这会相当
amazing.
惊人的。
&gt;&gt; And women are heavily undiagnosed,
而且女性患者中未确诊的比例很高。
right? Because we heavily
正确的？因为我们重度
&gt;&gt; we think of it as I mean I've heard it
我们认为它就像我听说过的那样。
being referred to as a sort of an old
被称作某种古老的
man's disease.
男人的疾病。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. And oh, absolutely. And here's the
是的。哦，当然。这就是……
thing. Many women have a tendency to
事物。许多女性都有这种倾向
report insomnia types of symptoms over
报告失眠症状类型
sleep apnea types of symptoms when in
睡眠呼吸暂停的症状类型
fact they actually have under
事实上，他们实际上拥有
undiagnosed sleep apnnea, which we can
未确诊的睡眠呼吸暂停，我们可以
catch.
抓住。
&gt;&gt; We talked a little bit earlier, but um
我们之前聊过一会儿，但是……
from many of the conversations I've had
从我参与的许多对话中可以看出这一点
on the show about Alzheimer's,
在关于阿尔茨海默病的节目中，
&gt;&gt; yes,
是的，
&gt;&gt; your chance of um getting Alzheimer's, I
你患阿尔茨海默病的几率，我
imagine, is going to increase, right?
想象一下，这会增加，对吧？
Because absolutely you have sleep
因为你肯定有睡眠
apnnea.
睡眠呼吸暂停。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, because when you have sleep
是的。嗯，因为当你睡觉的时候
apnnea, it keeps you out of the deeper
睡眠呼吸暂停症，它能让你远离更深的海域。
stages of sleep. the deeper stages of
睡眠阶段。更深层次的阶段
sleep is where that lymphatic system
睡眠是淋巴系统运作的关键时期。
comes in and scoops out those proteins
进来把那些蛋白质舀出来。
and that's really probably one of those
这很可能就是其中之一。
big causes for it. So that's one of the
造成这种情况的主要原因有很多。所以这是其中之一
things that we always want people to
我们一直希望人们做的事情
understand. But there's also something
理解。但还有其他一些因素。
else that I think is important to maybe
我觉得其他一些可能比较重要的事
talk about which is on the other side
谈谈另一边的情况
not sleep apnnea side but on the
不是睡眠呼吸暂停症那边，而是在
insomnia side which is there's a lot of
失眠的一面，也就是有很多
people who go and they go to the
去的人，他们去
drugstore and they buy an
他们去药店买了一个
over-the-counter sleep aid. Right now
非处方助眠药。现在
I'm not talking about supplementation
我说的不是补充剂。
yet. We can get into supplements in a
然而。我们可以深入探讨补充剂的问题。
minute if you want to, but I'm talking
如果你想的话，可以聊一分钟，但我说的是……
about things like the PM medications,
关于PM药物之类的事情，
right? You know, they so here in
正确的？你知道，他们在这里
America, we have them where there's like
在美国，我们有它们，就像……
there's like an analesic plus a PM. So
就像是镇静剂加上PM。所以
there's Tylenol PM, Advil PM, and what
有泰诺PM、艾德维尔PM，还有什么？
it is is it's a pain reliever, but they
它是一种止痛药，但是
add something called dyenhydramine and
加入一种叫做染料木胺的物质
it makes you feel sleepy and it makes
它会让你感到困倦，而且它使
you fall asleep. Dyenhydramine is
你睡着了。苯海拉明是
actually an antihistamine, right? So
实际上是一种抗组胺药，对吧？所以
it's used for congestion and things like
它用于缓解拥堵等问题
that. But there's now data to suggest
那。但现在有数据表明
that daily use of the PM part of this,
每日使用PM部分，
not the pain relieving part, but the PM
不是缓解疼痛的部分，而是首相
part can lead almost directly to
部分内容几乎可以直接导致
Alzheimer's.
阿尔茨海默病。
&gt;&gt; Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
&gt;&gt; Right. So, if people can just go to bed
正确的。所以，如果人们可以安心睡觉的话
and follow a couple simple rules and go
遵循几条简单的规则，然后出发
to bed naturally, you'd be shocked at
自然入睡会让你大吃一惊。
how much better your world is going to
你的世界将会变得多么美好
be. The Queensland Brain Institute um at
是。昆士兰脑研究所
the University of Queensland found that
昆士兰大学发现：
people with untreated apnea have a 45%
未经治疗的睡眠呼吸暂停患者死亡率高达 45%。
higher risk of developing Alzheimer's
患阿尔茨海默病的风险更高
disease.
疾病。
&gt;&gt; Like I said,
正如我所说，
&gt;&gt; which is crazy.
真是太疯狂了。
&gt;&gt; Soant here's the thing is we've got all
所以，关键是我们已经拥有了一切
these people who are watching your show
正在观看你节目的这些人
right now. They need to start thinking
现在。他们需要开始思考
in their head like maybe I have sleep
他们脑子里想着，也许我睡着了
apnea, maybe I don't, but maybe I should
睡眠呼吸暂停，也许我没有，但也许我应该有。
take a look at what are some of the
来看看有哪些……
symptoms and see if that's something
观察症状，看看是不是这个问题。
that could be going on for me. Because
我可能也会遇到这种情况。因为
again, testing is available. And to be
再次强调，检测是可行的。并且成为
clear, it's not like I'm the only guy
很明显，我又不是唯一一个这样的人
out there testing people. I mean, there
出去测试人们。我的意思是，那里
are sleep doctors all over the world
世界各地的睡眠医生
that are testing people. My
那些正在测试人们的人。我的
encouragement to people is, hey, figure
鼓励他人就是，嘿，想想看
it out. If if you can't figure it out,
把它拿出来。如果你实在想不明白，
you know, shoot us an email. We'll find
你知道，给我们发封邮件就行了。我们会找到
a sleep center for you to go to. But if
一个供你去的睡眠中心。但是如果
you think there's something going on,
你觉得事情有点蹊跷，
it's definitely worth checking out
绝对值得一看
because, by the way, you can stay with
顺便说一句，你可以留下来
undiagnosed sleep apnnea for your entire
未确诊的睡眠呼吸暂停症会伴随您一生。
life. And it all it does is basically
生活。它所做的基本上就是
break down everything that's going on
把所有正在发生的事情都分析一遍
inside. And that's not what you want.
里面。而那并非你想要的。
Like remember sleep is recovery, right?
别忘了睡眠是恢复体力的方式，对吧？
This is how your body still functions.
这就是你身体仍然能够正常运作的方式。
Like if you want to lead a nice
比如，如果你想领导一个美好的组织
prosperous life, you want to sleep.
生活富足，你想睡觉。
&gt;&gt; Insomnia has become a bit of a word that
失眠这个词已经变得有点……
people throw around
人们随意地
&gt;&gt; for sure,
一定，
&gt;&gt; right? They they kind of self diagnose
正确的？他们有点像是在自我诊断
themselves. We kind of think of it as
他们自己。我们大致把它看作是
this one specific thing. I think people
就是这件事。我认为人们
say, "I have insomnia when they just
我说，“当他们刚出现症状时，我就会失眠。”
don't sleep well."
睡不好觉。
&gt;&gt; Right.
正确的。
&gt;&gt; What is insomnia and what's the big myth
什么是失眠？关于失眠的种种误区又是什么？
around it?
周围呢？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So, number one, there's a couple
是的。首先，有几个
of different flavors of insomnia.
不同类型的失眠。
There's the I can't fall asleep. There's
还有一种情况是我无法入睡。有
the I can't stay asleep, which we talked
我睡不着，我们聊过这个。
about quite a bit. There's the I wake up
相当多。还有我醒来的时候
too early, and then there's just the I
太早了，然后就只剩下我了。
wake up from unrefreshing sleep. So, we
从昏昏沉沉的睡眠中醒来。所以，我们
really think that there are four sort of
真的认为有四种类型
types of insomnia, right? And um when
失眠的类型，对吧？嗯，当
people I would say some of the biggest
我认为其中一些人是最顶尖的。
myths that a lot of people have
很多人都有的误解
surrounding insomnia is or like the
失眠症的成因是或类似于
biggest problem that they do is when
他们最大的问题是当
somebody has a really crappy night then
有人昨晚过得特别糟糕
what they try to do is the next evening
他们试图在第二天晚上做的事情
go to bed early and try to catch up on
早点睡觉，尽量补上落下的功课。
some of that sleep that they missed. So
他们错过了一些睡眠。所以
to be clear this is a terrible idea
说清楚点，这是个糟糕的主意。
because your circadian rhythm isn't
因为你的昼夜节律不正常
ready to go to bed early. So you lie in
准备早点睡觉。所以你躺在
bed and you're exhausted but you can't
你躺在床上，筋疲力尽，但你却做不到。
fall asleep. you're what I call wired
睡着。你真是个十足的怪人。
and tired, right? And so what we want
而且很累，对吧？所以，我们想要什么？
people to do is if you do have a bout of
人们应该做的是，如果你真的患上了某种疾病……
insomnia where you have difficulty
失眠，难以入睡
falling asleep or difficulty staying
难以入睡或难以保持睡眠
asleep, number one, don't overcaffeinate
睡着了，第一，别摄入过量咖啡因。
during the daytime. So many people are
白天。很多人都是
like, "Oh, I'm dragging. I got to get a
比如，“哦，我拖着疲惫的身体。我得去拿……”
coffee," you know, and and they and they
你知道，咖啡，还有他们，还有他们
caffeinate, caffeinate, caffeinate, and
咖啡因，咖啡因，咖啡因，以及
then they caffeinate so late into the
然后他们很晚还在摄入咖啡因
day that they have shitty sleep that
他们那天睡眠很差。
night, and now we're in the washing
夜幕降临，现在我们正在洗衣房里。
machine cycle going over and over and
机器循环往复地运转
over. It sounds like you might be
超过。听起来你可能是
relating to this uh a little bit maybe
跟这个有点关系，或许吧。
yourself. And then so we want to avoid
你自己。所以，我们想要避免
that. The other thing we want to avoid
那。我们想要避免的另一件事
is over stimulation at night, right? So
是不是因为夜间过度刺激？所以
a lot of pimps people get that nervous
很多皮条客都会有这种紧张情绪。
energy and so they're just doing doing.
他们精力充沛，所以他们只是在做事情。
Again, you need runway to land the
再次强调，你需要跑道才能降落。
plane. So give yourself some kind of
飞机。所以给自己一些……
that space. Um and then just make sure
那个空间。嗯，然后一定要确保
that you've got some level of
你已经具备一定程度的
regularity. I would argue for my
规律性。我会为我的论点辩护。
insomnia patients, but quite honestly
失眠患者，但说实话
for anybody who's watching this, the
对于所有正在观看这段视频的人来说，
number one sleep tip that I can give
我能给出的第一条睡眠建议
people is to wake up at the same time
人们要在同一时间醒来
seven days a week. Not go to bed. I
一周七天。不要去睡觉。我
don't actually care when you go to bed
其实我并不在意你什么时候睡觉。
that much. I know there's a lot of sleep
就这么多。我知道有很多睡眠
specialists out there who are like, you
像你这样的专家有很多。
got to go to bed at the same time and
必须在同一时间上床睡觉
wake up at the same time. I'm not of
在同一时间起床。我不是
that ilk. I don't really care that much
同类。我其实不太在意。
about the going to bed time. I really
关于就寝时间。我真的
only care about the wake up time. Let me
只关心起床时间。让我
explain why. When you wake up in the
请解释原因。当你醒来时
morning, sunlight hits your eye and you
清晨，阳光照射进你的眼睛，你
have a special cell in your eye called
你的眼睛里有一种叫做……的特殊细胞
the melanopsin cell which sends a signal
黑视素细胞发出信号
to your brain to turn off the melatonin
大脑会发出信号来关闭褪黑激素。
faucet in your head. But it sets a timer
脑袋里像有个水龙头。但它会设置一个定时器。
for exactly 14 hours later. It's called
14 小时后。它叫做
the melatonin phase response curve. So
褪黑激素相位反应曲线。所以
if you're waking up at 6, melatonin
如果你早上6点起床，褪黑素
turns off until about 8:00 p.m. Then it
晚上8点左右才会重新开放。然后它
takes about a couple hours for it to get
大约需要几个小时才能完成
up and in. So then you start to get
向上并向内。然后你就开始……
sleep around 9:30 and you go to bed. But
晚上九点半左右睡觉。但
if you did that and now it's Saturday
如果你那样做了，现在已经是星期六了。
and you sleep in until 8, melatonin
然后你睡到八点，褪黑素
doesn't kick off until 10:00 Saturday
比赛要到周六上午10点才开始。
night. So what I'm saying is the time
夜晚。所以我的意思是，时间
that you wake up directly determines
你醒来的时间直接决定了
when your internal melatonin kicks into
当你体内褪黑激素开始分泌时
gear. So if everybody woke up at the
齿轮。所以如果每个人都在……醒来
exact same time every single day, seven
每天同一时间，七点
days a week, automatically you would get
一周中的某些天，你会自动获得
tired at the right time and you would
在合适的时间感到疲倦，你就会
start going to sleep.
开始睡觉。
&gt;&gt; And is there two different types of
是否存在两种不同类型的
insomnia? Sometimes I hear primary,
失眠？有时我会听到主要，
secondary insomnia. I think you have
继发性失眠。我认为你已经
that on your YouTube channel.
在你的 YouTube 频道上。
&gt;&gt; So when you look at primary insomnia
所以，当你审视原发性失眠症时
versus secondary insomnia, the way we
与继发性失眠相比，我们
categorize that, secondary insomnia is
将失眠症归类为继发性失眠症。
usually due to something else that's
通常是由于其他原因造成的
going on in your life. So
你生活中正在发生的事情。所以
&gt;&gt; psychology,
心理学，
&gt;&gt; so maybe caffeine abuse.
所以可能是咖啡因摄入过量。
&gt;&gt; Okay?
好的？
&gt;&gt; Right? Um maybe something along those
正确的？嗯，或许跟这些差不多
lines. Whereas primary insomnia is
线条。而原发性失眠症则是
there's nothing else. You the only thing
没有别的了。你是我唯一的依靠
you've got going on is sleep disorder.
你患的是睡眠障碍。
Another example of of something where
另一个例子是……
insomnia might be secondary would be
失眠可能是继发性的
pain.
疼痛。
&gt;&gt; Right? So if you have a pain syndrome,
正确的？所以，如果你患有疼痛综合征，
if you have fibromyalgia or low back
如果你患有纤维肌痛或腰痛
pain, that could prevent you from
疼痛可能会阻止你
sleeping. That would be secondary
睡眠。那将是次要的。
insomnia, secondary to pain.
疼痛引起的失眠。
&gt;&gt; And I hear that the most common
我听说最常见的
treatment for insomnia is CBT therapy.
治疗失眠的方法是认知行为疗法。
&gt;&gt; So yes and no.
所以，既是也不是。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; So I would say that the most common
所以我认为最常见的是
therapy for insomnia is alcohol.
治疗失眠的方法是饮酒。
&gt;&gt; More people drink themselves to sleep
越来越多的人借酒消愁入睡
&gt;&gt; than any other single thing out there.
比其他任何单一事物都更胜一筹。
Um and then you start to get into the
嗯，然后你就开始深入了解
pharmacy of it all. And there's a lot of
一切皆药房。而且还有很多
pharmaceutical drugs out there that
市面上有一些药品
people utilize for for sleep. And I want
人们利用它来睡觉。而我想要
to make a point if I can is there's
如果可以的话，我想强调一点：
nothing wrong with needing a pill to
需要吃药并没有什么错。
sleep. Okay? I want to be very clear
睡觉。好的？我想非常明确地说明一点。
about this. There are people out there
关于这件事。世界上还有人
who need pills, right? All kinds of
谁还需要药片呢？各种各样的
different ones. Thank you. There's a
不同的。谢谢。有一个
whole host of reasons why you and your
你和你的原因有很多
doctor may have come to the conclusion
医生可能已经得出结论
that a sleeping tablet is good for you.
服用安眠药对你有好处。
The problem comes when those sleeping
问题出在那些睡觉的人身上。
tablets are overprescribed. So insomnia
药片被过度处方。所以失眠
is in the in the sleep world, we call it
在睡眠世界里，我们称之为
a door handle diagnosis because when the
门把手诊断，因为当
doctor has their hand on the door and
医生把手放在门上，
they're just about to leave, that's when
他们正要离开的时候，
the patient says, "Oh, and by the way,
病人说：“哦，对了，
I'm not sleeping."
我睡不着。
&gt;&gt; And then the doctor usually pulls out
然后医生通常会拔出来
the prescription pad and says, you know,
处方笺上写着，你知道的，
ambient or trazadone or something like
环境、曲唑酮或其他类似的东西
that, writes it up, says, "Here, come
他把它写下来，说：“来，到这儿来。”
back in 30 days." Well, you haven't
30天后回来。” 好吧，你还没回来。
really done anything for this person.
真的为这个人做过任何事。
You've handed them a pill. And by the
你递给他们一颗药丸。并且通过
way, now they're probably either
现在，他们可能要么是
psychologically or physiologically
心理上或生理上
addicted to said pill right now. Once
我现在对这种药片上瘾了。一次
again, if you've got a major mental
再说一遍，如果你有严重的心理问题
health issue, I don't think I care. I
健康问题？我觉得我不在乎。我
think it's okay for you to have your
我觉得你拥有你的
AMVN and be fine. And
AMVN，没事的。和
&gt;&gt; and a lot of people that do have
很多确实有这种能力的人
insomnia have depression.
失眠会导致抑郁症。
&gt;&gt; Oh, I think it's one of the biggest
哦，我认为它是最大的之一。
things that we see. But I would argue
我们所看到的事物。但我认为……
anxiety might be a little bit more than
焦虑可能比这还要严重一些。
depression. But yes, anxiety and
沮丧。是的，焦虑和
depression, I would argue, make up 75%
我认为，抑郁症占所有病例的75%。
of insomnia at any given time. Right? I
随时可能出现失眠症状。正确的？我
work with people and I do something
与人合作，我做一些事情
called cognitive behavioral therapy for
称为认知行为疗法
insomnia which you correctly identified
你正确指出的失眠症
as CBTI, right? And so I work with
作为CBTI，对吧？所以我与……合作
patients all the time. Um, and that's
一直都是病人。嗯，就是这样。
exactly what we do is we reschedule
我们所做的就是重新安排时间。
them. So that's the behavioral part. And
他们。以上就是行为方面的部分。和
then the cognitive part is we talk to
然后认知部分就是我们与……交谈
them about how do you think about sleep?
他们问你对睡眠有什么看法？
Because a lot of people think about
因为很多人都在思考
sleep in disastrous ways. They're like,
睡眠状况糟糕透顶。他们就像是：
if I don't get eight hours, my old day
如果我一天工作时间不到八小时，那就跟以前一样了。
is screwed and everything's going to
一切都完了，所有事情都会……
happen. It rarely happens that way. Like
发生。这种情况很少发生。喜欢
it's called catastrophizing. You just
这叫做灾难化思维。你只是
make it worse and worse and worse. And
让情况越来越糟，越来越糟。和
so we look at those cognitive
所以我们来看一下这些认知方面的问题。
distortions and we help fix them in
我们会帮助解决这些失真问题。
therapy by really kind of what I call
治疗，我称之为
doing the math. And so I say, "Well,
算算账。所以我说，“好吧，
have you ever had four hours of sleep?"
你睡过四个小时吗？
"Yes." "Did you do something terrible
“是的。”你是不是做了什么可怕的事情？
the next day?" "No." "So where's your
第二天呢？“不。”“那你呢？”
evidence?" Right? And you start to get
证据？对吧？然后你就开始……
people to challenge themselves and all
人们要挑战自我，所有
of a sudden they kind of they can kind
突然间，他们有点像，他们可以像
of get there. There's also another area
到达那里。还有另一个区域
of that a lot of people go to somewhere
很多人都会去某个地方。
in between the pills and therapy, and
在服药和接受治疗的间隙，以及
that's supplementation. So there's a lot
那是补充剂。所以有很多
of people out there who like to use
有些人喜欢使用
supplements and try to understand how to
补充剂，并尝试了解如何使用
fix quote their insomnia with
用以下方法解决他们的失眠问题
supplementation. So if we can let's talk
补充。如果可以的话，我们来谈谈吧。
a little bit about supplements and sort
简单介绍一下补充剂和分类
of what's good and what's bad.
区分好与坏。
&gt;&gt; What is the difference between a
两者之间有什么区别？
supplement and a pill or is it you
补充剂和药丸，还是你？
talking about the same thing here? So
你们说的是同一件事吗？所以
under the context of this conversation,
在本次对话的背景下，
a supplement is a non FDA regulated
膳食补充剂不受美国食品药品监督管理局 (FDA) 监管。
thing that you can purchase at any
你可以在任何一家商店买到的东西
drugstore and a pill is a by
药店和药丸是……
prescription only from a doctor.
必须凭医生处方购买。
&gt;&gt; Okay,
好的，
&gt;&gt; that's how we're going to make the
这就是我们制作的方法。
distinction for this particular
这一特殊之处
conversation.
对话。
&gt;&gt; Okay, so those pills that are in front
好的，所以前面那些药片。
of you there,
你们在那儿吗？
&gt;&gt; so right in front of me, these are most
所以就在我眼前，这些是最主要的
these are actually all supplements. So
这些实际上都是保健品。所以
these are different. So these are not
这两者是不同的。所以这些不是
pharmaceuticals. These are different
药品。这些是不同的
things. So, we've got
事物。所以，我们有了
&gt;&gt; I mean, in different countries, it's
我的意思是，在不同的国家，情况各不相同。
different, right?
不一样，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Great point. So, let's talk about
说得对。那么，我们来谈谈……
melatonin since that's kind of the
褪黑素，因为它有点像……
biggie that a lot of people like to know
很多人都想知道的大事
about. So, number one, melatonin is by
关于。所以，第一点，褪黑素是由……
prescription only almost everywhere
几乎所有地方都需要处方才能购买
other than the United States,
除美国以外，
&gt;&gt; right? So, in England, in Australia, in
正确的？所以，在英国，在澳大利亚，在
Europe, you can't just walk into the
欧洲，你不能就这么走进去。
drugstore and buy melatonin. And there's
去药店购买褪黑素。还有……
a reason. A lot of people don't realize
一个理由。很多人都没意识到这一点。
it, but melatonin is a hormone. There's
它，但褪黑激素是一种激素。有
a reason you can't go to the CVS and get
你不能去CVS买东西的原因
testosterone and estrogen, right?
是睾酮和雌激素，对吧？
Because hormones affect the entire
因为激素会影响整个身体。
system. They affect all three almost 300
系统。它们影响了这三者，近300人。
different things in your body. So what
你身体里的不同部位。所以呢
you don't want to do is have somebody
你不想做的就是让某人
just willy-nilly grabbing a hormone and
随意地抓起一种激素，
starting to pop it without somebody
开始独自一人把它弹出来
understanding what's going on with them.
了解他们身上发生了什么。
More importantly, melatonin in
更重要的是，褪黑素
particular, and the point I wanted to
具体来说，我想表达的是……
make earlier about depression, melatonin
及早了解抑郁症和褪黑激素
interacts with all SSRI medication. An
与所有 SSRI 类药物有相互作用。一个
SSRI is a serotonin specific reuptake
SSRI 是一种选择性血清素再摄取抑制剂。
inhibitor, an anti-depressant. So things
抑制剂，一种抗抑郁药。所以事情
like Prozac, Zoloft, um, Selelexa, all
比如百忧解、左洛复、嗯、司来昔布，等等
of those are medications that will be
其中一些药物将会是
affected by melatonin ingestion and
受褪黑素摄入的影响
nobody knows that it is. In addition,
没人知道真相。此外，
melatonin affects birth control. Yes,
褪黑素会影响避孕效果。是的，
you heard it here, birth control. It
你没听错，是避孕。它
affects blood pressure medication and it
影响血压药物及其
affects diabetes medication. So, one of
影响糖尿病药物治疗。所以，其中一个
the problems is that people go into the
问题在于人们进入
local drugstore and they're like, "Oh,
当地药店，他们会说：“哦，
I'm going to grab some melatonin and I'm
我打算去买点褪黑素，然后……
going to make my sleep better because
会改善我的睡眠质量，因为
I'm sleeping poorly." So, first of all,
我睡眠很差。所以，首先，
that's not what melatonin does.
褪黑素并不是起到那种作用的。
Melatonin is a sleep regulator, not a
褪黑激素是一种睡眠调节剂，而不是……
sleep initiator. Melatonin doesn't
睡眠启动器。褪黑素不会。
affect sleep drive. Melatonin affects
影响睡眠驱动力。褪黑素的影响
sleep rhythm. So, remember in the
睡眠节律。所以，记住在
beginning of our conversation, we're
在我们对话的开始，我们
talking about the two systems. Melatonin
谈谈这两个系统。褪黑素
only affects your brain telling it when
只会影响你的大脑，告诉它何时
it's time to go to bed. It does not make
该睡觉了。它不会造成
you sleepy. That's a denisonin. We
你困了。那是丹尼森宁。我们
already talked about adenosin and
已经讨论过腺苷和
caffeine and how similar their molecular
咖啡因及其分子结构的相似性
structures are. So when you look at
结构是。所以当你观察
something like melatonin, you need to
你需要服用褪黑素之类的东西。
really be thoughtful about using it.
使用时一定要慎重考虑。
Number two, melatonin is not to be used
第二，褪黑素不应该使用。
in children. Okay? So a lot of people
在儿童中。好的？所以很多人
are like, "Michael, I've got
就像是，“迈克尔，我……”
pediatricians all over the country
全国各地的儿科医生
telling my telling me to give my
告诉我，告诉我给我我的
children melatonin." I'm going to say it
儿童褪黑素。” 我要说出来。
right here in front of everybody. That
就在大家面前。那
is the dumbest idea I have heard in a
这是我听过的最愚蠢的想法。
long time because you just taught your
很久了，因为你刚刚教了你的
child that they need a pill to sleep.
孩子需要吃药才能入睡。
Normally, no child needs pills to sleep.
通常情况下，孩子不需要吃药就能入睡。
And by the way, most children make
顺便说一句，大多数孩子都会……
almost four times the amount of
几乎是原来的四倍
melatonin that their brain even needs.
大脑甚至需要褪黑激素。
So, giving them extra melatonin doesn't
所以，给他们额外补充褪黑素并不会有帮助。
do you any good. There is, however, one
对你有好处吗？然而，有一个
group of children where melatonin does
一组服用褪黑素的儿童
work well, and that's in kids on the
效果很好，这对孩子们来说尤其如此。
autism spectrum. um we don't know
自闭症谱系。嗯，我们不知道。
exactly why but um or at least I don't
具体原因是什么？嗯，或者至少我不知道。
but there is data to suggest that at
但有数据表明，
five six seven milligrams that that can
五、六、七毫克，那可以
be very helpful for them. Dosage also is
对他们非常有帮助。剂量也是
a problem like if you go to the
例如，如果你去……
drugstore you can you almost can't find
药店里几乎找不到
it in the appropriate dose. The
服用适当剂量。这
appropriate dose is anywhere from about
合适的剂量大约在
half a milligram to one and a half
0.5毫克至1.5毫克
milligrams. Maybe top out at three but
毫克。或许最多也就三个，但
that's about as high as you want to go.
这差不多就是你能达到的最高高度了。
But when you go to CVS you find a
但是当你去CVS药店时，你会发现
gummies in 10 and 20 milligrams. And
10毫克和20毫克规格的软糖。和
people tell me all the time, "Oh, I
人们总是跟我说，“哦，我
can't take melatonin. It gives me crazy
不能服用褪黑素。这让我抓狂
dreams." Number one side effect of
梦想。” 第一个副作用
overdosing on melatonin is crazy dreams.
服用过量褪黑素会导致疯狂的梦境。
&gt;&gt; On this point of going to a supermarket
说到去超市这件事，
and picking some melatonin off the
并从……上摘一些褪黑素
shelf,
架子，
&gt;&gt; FDA approval and the lack of FDA
FDA批准和缺乏FDA
approval in melatonin means that there's
褪黑素获得批准意味着……
less clarity on what's actually in
对于实际包含的内容，目前尚不清楚。
there. Right.
那里。正确的。
&gt;&gt; That's exactly right. I was reading
完全正确。我在看书
about a study in 2024
关于2024年的一项研究
um where they looked at different
嗯，他们看的地方各不相同
melatonins that were found on the shelf
在货架上发现的褪黑素
&gt;&gt; and they found very different things
他们发现了截然不同的事情。
inside the bottle.
瓶子里面。
&gt;&gt; Very very different things. They looked
完全是两码事。他们看起来
at an analysis of melatonin gummies
对褪黑素软糖的分析
marketed for children and found that the
针对儿童市场销售的产品，结果发现
actual amount of melatonin ranged from
实际褪黑激素含量范围为
0%
0%
&gt;&gt; right
正确的
&gt;&gt; to 667%
高达667%
of what was listed on the label.
与标签上所列内容一致。
&gt;&gt; Yep. See it all the time. And in the
是的。经常看到这种情况。而且在
same study, melatonin gummies, some
同一项研究，褪黑素软糖，一些
melatonin gummies contained absolutely
褪黑素软糖绝对含有
no melatonin, while others contained
不含褪黑素，而其他产品则含有褪黑素。
hazardous contaminants like CBD that
有害污染物，例如CBD
were not disclosed on the label.
标签上并未注明。
&gt;&gt; Yep.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Because melatonin is sold as a
因为褪黑素是作为一种……出售的
supplement in the US and not a drug, the
在美国，它是一种膳食补充剂，而不是药品。
FDA does not test it for safety or
FDA并未对其进行安全性测试。
accuracy before it hits the shelf.
在产品上架前确保其准确性。
&gt;&gt; You are 100% correct. And that's a huge
你说的完全正确。那可是件大事。
problem. Just think about that for a
问题。好好想想这件事
second. I mean, the market for melatonin
第二。我的意思是，褪黑素的市场
is tremendous. It's huge in the
太棒了。它在……方面非常巨大
supplement world. Yet, there's no
补品世界。然而，却没有
regulation. whatsoever. Nobody knows
规定。任何。没人知道
about these interaction effects which
关于这些交互作用效应
are big, big, big. And by the way, most
非常大，非常大，非常大。顺便说一句，大多数
people are using it wrong. There's
人们使用错误。有
really only three maybe four different
实际上只有三四种不同的
instances when melatonin would be
褪黑素适用情况
useful. I would use melatonin for jet
有用。我会用褪黑素来缓解喷射。
lag, and we should talk about jet lag.
时差，我们应该谈谈时差反应。
&gt;&gt; Um I I would use uh melatonin for shift
嗯，我会用褪黑素来缓解换班时的不适。
workers, right? So for people who work,
工人，对吧？所以对于上班族来说，
you know, night shift who have to sleep
你知道，上夜班的人得睡觉
during the daytime, they would be
白天，他们会……
excellent people to use melatonin.
非常适合使用褪黑素的人群。
people with a melatonin deficiency. A
褪黑激素缺乏症患者。一个
lot of people don't think about that,
很多人都没想过这一点。
but right around age 50 is when if
但大约在50岁左右，如果
you're going to have a melatonin
你要服用褪黑素
deficiency, we start to see that
从这种不足中，我们开始看到……
happening for people is it their the
对人们来说，发生的事情是他们的
ability to produce melatonin begins to
产生褪黑激素的能力开始
decline. So, I think those three
衰退。所以，我认为这三个
situations absolutely would be on board
情况绝对会符合要求。
for melatonin. Believe it or not,
褪黑素。信不信由你，
there's some data to show that in ADD
有一些数据显示，在注意力缺陷障碍（ADD）中
and ADHD there's uh some use for
对于多动症患者来说，这方面也有一些用处。
melatonin and then also for a very
褪黑素，然后也用于非常
specific sleeping disorder called REM
特定的睡眠障碍称为快速眼动睡眠（REM）。
behavior disorder.
行为障碍。
&gt;&gt; We're going melatonin crazy as a
我们都快疯了，都在疯狂服用褪黑素。
society, aren't we?
我们不就是这个社会吗？
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. We don't need it. It's
绝对地。我们不需要它。它是
completely unnecessary.
完全没必要。
&gt;&gt; I was looking at the data. In 1999, 0.4%
我在查看数据。 1999年，0.4%
of Americans said they used melatonin.
美国人表示他们使用褪黑素。
Today, it's almost 30%. So, 70 million
如今，这一比例已接近30%。所以，7000万
Americans up, dude. That is problematic.
美国人，振作起来，伙计。那很成问题。
And again, they have no idea what it's
他们仍然完全不知道那是什么。
doing to them, right? And they're giving
对吧？他们正在给予
it to their kids. Like, I can't think of
传给他们的孩子。比如，我想不出什么来
anything worse for a young female
对年轻女性来说，还有什么比这更糟糕的呢？
developing body than to add a
比添加一个正在发育的身体
contraceptive when it's not necessary.
不必要的避孕措施。
Like, it just doesn't make sense to me.
我完全无法理解。
The rise in children overdosing on sleep
儿童睡眠过量事件的增加
gummies is the fastest growing trend in
软糖是增长最快的趋势
poison control data.
中毒控制数据。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I think it's like almost 600%
是的，我觉得差不多有600%了。
increase or something crazy like that
增加或者类似这样的疯狂变化
for kids who have uh gotten uh who've
对于那些已经……已经……的孩子们
overdosed on melatonin like within there
就像体内过量服用褪黑素一样
was a study that came out maybe a year
那是一项大概一年前发表的研究。
ago, year and a half ago showed like
一年半前，情况就像
almost 600% of uh increase in uh
呃，增长了近600%。
overdoses for kids. Like that's pretty
儿童药物过量。那真漂亮
messed up when you start to think about
当你开始思考的时候，事情就变得一团糟了
it. And here's the thing, kids know how
它。关键在于，孩子们都知道该怎么做。
to sleep,
入睡，
&gt;&gt; right? You just got to stop. You just
正确的？你必须停止这种行为。你只是
got to let them sleep, right? You got to
得让他们睡觉，对吧？你必须
give them some parameters. Here's when
给他们设定一些参数。这就是时候
you go to bed. Here's when you wake up.
你上床睡觉。这就是你醒来的时候。
Don't get out of bed. You know, don't
别下床。你知道，不要
come in and ask for 12 glasses of water.
进来要12杯水。
You know, all the all the stuff that
你知道，所有那些东西
goes on there. I mean, it this isn't
就在那里。我的意思是，如果这不是
hard.
难的。
&gt;&gt; So, when and how So, I used melatonin
所以，我何时以及如何使用了褪黑素。
once in my life.
我一生只有一次。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; And I got to be honest, it [__]
说实话，这他妈太糟糕了
worked.
成功了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Oh, if you use it right, it works,
是的。哦，只要使用方法正确，它就有效。
bro.
兄弟。
&gt;&gt; And it was it was actually about a week
实际上，大概过了一周左右。
ago because I'd been struggling with
之前因为我一直很苦恼
lots of jet lag. I'd flown from the UK
时差反应很严重。我从英国飞过来的。
to the LA to UK to LA to Cape Town to
到洛杉矶到英国到洛杉矶到开普敦
Middle East to wherever and I was
从中东到任何地方，我都在那里
getting to bed every night at like 4:00
每天晚上大概四点就上床睡觉
or 5 a.m. and still waking up at, you
或者凌晨5点，你仍然会醒来。
know, having to wake up at about 10:00.
我知道，我得在早上10点左右起床。
&gt;&gt; So, I thought, I need to correct this.
所以我想，我需要纠正这一点。
It's been going for two weeks and I need
已经持续两周了，我需要
to correct this.
为了纠正这一点。
&gt;&gt; Absolutely.
绝对地。
&gt;&gt; So, I thought, [__] it, I'm going to
所以，我想，去他妈的，我要……
cave. I g I took the melatonin and
洞穴。我服用了褪黑素，
corrected it.
已更正。
&gt;&gt; Yes, it does. So, let's talk about jet
是的，确实如此。那么，我们来聊聊喷气式飞机吧。
lag. So, it's a bit of a story, but I
落后。所以，这说来话长，但我
got involved with a company that um has
参与了一家公司，这家公司……
got an app, which is very interesting.
我下载了一个应用程序，非常有趣。
Okay. Um I don't have any like I'm not
好的。嗯，我没有，我不是那种人。
invested in the company, just to be
投资这家公司，只是为了
clear, but it's one of my close friends
很清楚，但那是我一位好朋友。
who developed this. So, I'm kind of a
谁开发的？所以，我算是……
space nerd.
太空迷。
&gt;&gt; It's not Time Shifter.
这不是《时间旅行者》。
&gt;&gt; It is Time Shifter.
这是时间转换器。
&gt;&gt; Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
&gt;&gt; It is.
这是。
&gt;&gt; I also like an affiliation with Time
我也很喜欢与《时代》杂志的合作关系。
Shifter
换挡器
&gt;&gt; because I used to Yeah, I will get you
因为我以前……是的，我会找到你的
that. So, here's what's fascinating is
那。所以，最令人着迷的是……
the way the whole time shifter started
整个时间转换器的开端
was um so aren't you kind of a space
嗯，所以你不是有点太空迷吗？
guy? Like, aren't you
男的？难道不是吗？
&gt;&gt; I'm an investor in SpaceX and
我是SpaceX的投资者，
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, I'm a space nerd myself,
好的。我本人也是个太空迷。
right? So, you know, the the ISS is
正确的？所以，你知道，国际空间站是
moving around at 17,500 miles an hour
以每小时 17,500 英里的速度移动
around the Earth. It's cooking.
环绕地球。正在烹饪。
&gt;&gt; ISS meaning the International Space
ISS 指的是国际空间站
Station. It's whipping around, right?
车站。它飞速旋转，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Can you imagine how many sunrises and
你能想象有多少次日出吗？
sunsets they get in a given day?
一天中他们能看到的日落有哪些？
&gt;&gt; Oh, no. How many?
哦，不。多少？
&gt;&gt; Every two hours. So, they basically get
每两小时一次。所以，他们基本上得到了
12.
12.
&gt;&gt; Wow. Think about how messed up their
哇。想想他们有多糟糕
circadian rhythms would be from seeing
昼夜节律是通过观察获得的
the sunrise and seeing it go and see it
日出，看着它升起，再看着它升起。
gets really messed up, right? And by the
事情变得非常糟糕，对吧？并且通过
way, you don't want to make big mistakes
总之，你不想犯大错。
in the space station. Like you don't
在空间站里。就像你不会那样
leave the air lock open, you know, or
你知道，把气闸打开。
[__] like that. Like that's when things
诸如此类的事情。就像那时候事情发生的时候
get really really bad. So they called
情况会变得非常非常糟糕。所以他们打电话
down to NASA and they were like, "Hey,
甚至联系了NASA，他们说：“嘿，
we got a problem up here. Everybody
我们这边出了点问题。大家
wants to use the lab at the same time
想同时使用实验室
like people seeing the sun. Like what's
就像人们看到太阳一样。比如什么是
going on?" So they called a buddy of
发生了什么事？”于是他们给一个朋友打了电话。
mine named Steven Lachley over at
我的名字叫 Steven Lachley，在
Harvard. Stephen is arguably the one of
哈佛大学。斯蒂芬可以说是其中之一
the best circadian researchers in the
最优秀的昼夜节律研究人员
world. um super smart dude and he was
世界。嗯，他是个超级聪明的人，而且他……
like, "Well, let's send up a lighting
比如，“好吧，让我们派人去放个闪电吧。”
kit and let's create ships on the space
工具包，让我们在太空中建造飞船吧
station."
车站。”
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Right. So that's exactly what they did.
正确的。所以他们就这么做了。
So they sent up a lighting kit. I think
所以他们送来了一套照明设备。我认为
it was on the Colombia um shuttle before
那是在哥伦比亚的摆渡机上
it got decommissioned. And they set up
它退役了。他们开始筹划
lighting and then they set up timing for
然后他们设置灯光，并调整时间。
lighting. And so there was a morning
灯光。于是，就有了那一个早晨。
shift, a midshift, and a night shift for
轮班、中班和夜班
the astronauts. Once they got the
宇航员们。一旦他们得到了
algorithm working, they brought it down
算法运行正常，他们把它搞垮了。
terrestrially and they put it into the
在陆地上，他们把它放进了
Mercedes-Benz uh Formula 1 race car
梅赛德斯-奔驰一级方程式赛车
team. So they gave it to Lewis Hamilton.
团队。所以他们把奖给了刘易斯·汉密尔顿。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Right. Because when you think about it,
正确的。因为仔细想想，
think about what he has to do, right?
想想他必须做什么，对吧？
He's on or off the podium on hundreds of
他数百次登上或离开领奖台
a second, right? And he's in a different
一秒钟，对吧？他身处另一个世界。
country every 3 weeks,
每3周访问一次该国，
&gt;&gt; right? So this guy's got jet lag like
正确的？所以这家伙得了时差反应。
you wouldn't believe. And so once we
你简直不敢相信。所以一旦我们
were able to get it going there, then we
我们成功地在那里启动了它，然后我们
created the time shifter app. And so
创建了时间转换器应用程序。所以
it's an app you can get it on your
这是一个你可以下载到手机上的应用程序
phone. And what you do is you put in
电话。而你所做的就是投入
your flight number and it automatically
您提供的航班号将自动
pulls up the flight and knows where you
调出航班信息，知道你在哪里。
are. This is why I think that jet lag is
是。这就是我认为时差反应的原因
a math problem. Let me explain. We
一道数学题。让我解释一下。我们
learned about 20 years ago that when you
大约20年前我了解到，当你
take a certain frequency and intensity
采取一定的频率和强度
of light and you shine it in somebody's
你用光照射别人的……
eyes, you can move their circadian
眼睛，你可以移动它们的昼夜节律
rhythm by about eight hours if you want
如果需要，可以调整节奏，大约八小时。
to.
到。
&gt;&gt; That circadian rhythm again being
再次强调，昼夜节律
&gt;&gt; being that internal biological clock,
那就是我们体内的生物钟。
the time when your body wants to go to
当你的身体想要……的时候
bed and wants to wake up. We can
躺在床上，想醒过来。我们可以
actually move that by about 8 hours with
实际上，这大约会提前8个小时。
about 10,000 lux, which is the
大约10000勒克斯，也就是
brightness level of blue light,
蓝光亮度级别
particular frequency of light. Okay? So
特定频率的光。好的？所以
when you hit that, if you start in LA
当你达到那个阶段时，如果你从洛杉矶开始。
and you're going to Manchester, right,
你要去曼彻斯特，对吧？
and there's a big time difference and
而且时差很大。
you know what time it is in LA and you
你知道洛杉矶现在几点，而且你
know what time it is in Manchester, it's
知道曼彻斯特现在几点吗？
a math problem of when do you get the
一个数学问题：何时才能得到
light.
光。
&gt;&gt; So that's what time shifter is, is it
所以这就是时间转换器，是吗？
determines when do you need that light
决定何时需要那盏灯
and then on the times when you don't
然后，在你没有……的时候
need light, it has you use caffeine,
需要光照，它会让你摄入咖啡因。
right? Or to keep you awake or if it's
正确的？或者为了让你保持清醒，或者如果是的话
time to sleep, then you use a little bit
该睡觉了，然后你用一点点
of melatonin. That's when melatonin
褪黑素。那时褪黑激素
becomes so valuable.
变得如此宝贵。
&gt;&gt; It also tells you when to eat.
它还会告诉你什么时候该吃饭。
&gt;&gt; It does. It tells you all of these
确实如此。它会告诉你所有这些
different things. And it's kind of nice
不同的事情。这感觉还不错。
because it kind of shows up on your
因为它会以某种方式显示在你的……上
phone. It's like, "Hey, do this then. Do
电话。就好像是，“嘿，那就这么做。做
this then." And it works really, really
那就这样吧。”而且它真的非常有效。
well. But yeah, Time Shifter is one of
出色地。是的，《时间转换者》是其中之一。
my favorites. Uh I've been uh using it
我的最爱。呃，我一直在用它
literally for 15 years.
足足15年。
&gt;&gt; Wow.
哇。
&gt;&gt; And it solves jet lag, bro. Like we're
它还能解决时差问题，兄弟。就像我们一样
going to fix that for you. No, no
我会帮你解决这个问题。不，不
question.
问题。
&gt;&gt; How often should someone be having
一个人应该多久吃一次
melatonin? Is there like too often?
褪黑素？点赞次数是不是太多了？
Because some people literally have it
因为有些人确实拥有它
every day. Yeah, I would argue it's a
每天。是的，我认为这是一个
bad idea. So, if you have a melatonin
馊主意。所以，如果你服用褪黑素
deficiency, sure, have it every day.
缺乏症？当然有，每天都有。
But, um, or if you're a shift worker,
但是，嗯，或者如果你是轮班工作者，
probably. But I I use it only for jet
大概。但我只用它来喷射
lag myself. Otherwise, I'm not using it
自己落后了。否则，我就不用它了。
on the regular.
定期。
&gt;&gt; And what's the risk there of having it
拥有它的风险是什么？
every day? Is it?
每天？是吗？
&gt;&gt; Uh, it's a good question. So, when you
嗯，问得好。所以，当你
start to look at melatonin overdose and
开始关注褪黑素过量服用问题
you start to look at melatonin on board
你开始关注机载褪黑素。
for long periods of time, there's been
长期以来，一直存在着
some conflict in the in the research.
研究中存在一些冲突。
Um, there's a group of people that say
嗯，有一群人说
if you stay on melatonin for extended
如果你长期服用褪黑素
periods of time, your body stops
在某些时期，你的身体会停止运转
producing it. There's another group of
生产它。还有另一组
people that have looked at research and
看过研究的人
have said actually that's not the case.
有人说过，实际上并非如此。
So, right now we have we have studies
所以，目前我们有研究
that lead out to about a year or so on
那之后大约过了一年左右。
melatonin. And when you stop their
褪黑素。当你停止他们的
melatonin production after they've been
他们之后褪黑激素的产生
taking it for a year, their body seems
服用一年后，他们的身体似乎
to start back up no problem. It's
重新启动没问题。它是
different than testosterone, right? So
与睾酮不同，对吧？所以
with testosterone, we know that when men
我们知道，睾酮会使男性……
start taking testosterone, their body
开始服用睾酮，他们的身体
actually stops producing it. With
实际上停止生产了。和
melatonin, that does not appear to be
褪黑素，这似乎并非
the case, but we don't have studies that
确实存在这种情况，但我们没有相关的研究。
go out past, you know, that yearong. And
出去走走，你知道，过了那一年。和
so if somebody's been taking melatonin
所以如果有人一直在服用褪黑素
every day for 5 10 years, you know, you
每天持续5到10年，你知道，你
you kind of start to wonder uh what's
你会开始有点好奇，呃，这到底是什么？
going to happen. Also, don't forget that
即将发生。还有，别忘了……
that melatonin is different than the
褪黑激素与……不同
melatonin that's actually produced in
实际上在体内产生的褪黑激素
your head. I think it was Andrew
你的头。我想应该是安德鲁
Huberman who I was speaking to a couple
我当时正在和一对夫妇交谈，他们叫胡伯曼。
of weeks ago that was was saying about
几周前，有人说过……
not giving kids an overdose of
不要给孩子过量服用
melatonin. And I think afterwards I I
褪黑素。而且我觉得之后我
was doing some research on it and I read
我正在查阅相关资料，然后我读到
something that said it has an impact on
有话说它会对……产生影响
puberty potentially.
可能进入青春期。
&gt;&gt; So in high dosages melatonin is a
所以，高剂量褪黑素是一种
contraceptive.
避孕药。
&gt;&gt; So that would pause puberty.
这样就能暂停青春期发育。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. Or change it
确切地。或者改变它
&gt;&gt; and ways we may or may not know. So, I
以及我们可能知道也可能不知道的方式。所以，我
agree with Andrew on that point that
我同意安德鲁的这一点。
again, melatonin is not something that
再次强调，褪黑素并非某种……
kids need unless you've got kids on the
除非你有孩子在身边，否则孩子们需要
spectrum, which is again where I find it
频谱，我又是在那里找到它的。
to be helpful and I've treated kids with
为了提供帮助，我曾用以下方式治疗过孩子
that before, but generally speaking, I
以前是这样，但总的来说，我
don't put melatonin on anybody under the
不要给任何未成年人服用褪黑素。
age of 18.
18岁。
&gt;&gt; Am I more likely to have nightmares if
如果……我更容易做噩梦吗？
I'm having lots of melatonin?
我服用了很多褪黑素？
&gt;&gt; If you're overdosing, you are. So, the
如果你服用过量，那就是过量了。所以，
number one side effect of a high dose of
高剂量的第一副作用
melatonin is super vivid dreams and then
褪黑素会带来超级生动的梦境，然后……
eventually nightmares.
最终会变成噩梦。
&gt;&gt; Why? I'm not really sure. If I was
为什么？我不太确定。如果我
garnering a guess, then what I would say
先猜猜看，然后我会说什么？
is that part of the reason why that you
这是你这样做的部分原因吗？
have crazy vivid dreams from melatonin
服用褪黑激素后会做非常逼真的梦
is because it probably does put you into
这是因为它很可能确实会让你陷入
REM sleep a little bit quicker than you
快速眼动睡眠比你快一点
normally would and might keep you there
通常情况下会，而且可能会让你留在那里。
a little bit longer. I don't have any
再过一会儿。我没有
data to support that. So, I want to be
有数据支持这一点。所以，我想成为
clear. Um, this is more of a hypothesis
清除。嗯，这更像是一种假设。
on my end, but that might make intuitive
就我而言，但这可能很直观。
sense to me.
对我来说有道理。
&gt;&gt; Just on a quick search, um, Sure. You're
简单搜索了一下，嗯，当然可以。你是
right. It says it keep keeps you in REM
正确的。它说它能让你保持快速眼动睡眠状态。
sleep a little bit longer and more
多睡一会儿，多睡一会儿
intensely.
强烈地。
&gt;&gt; There you go.
好了。
&gt;&gt; This leads to vivid highly vivid dreams
这会导致非常生动逼真的梦境。
or night terrors which paradoxically
或者夜惊，这自相矛盾地
makes you wake up feeling more
让你醒来感觉更
exhausted.
筋疲力尽的。
&gt;&gt; Right. I can't count the number of
正确的。我数不清有多少个
people who tell me
告诉我这些的人
&gt;&gt; I need to go back to sleep because I'm
我得回去睡觉了，因为我……
so exhausted from my dreams.
做梦做得太累了。
&gt;&gt; Oh wow.
哇哦。
&gt;&gt; Right.
正确的。
&gt;&gt; So let's finish off on these supplements
那么，我们最后再来谈谈这些补充剂。
then.
然后。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Absolutely. So we talked a little
是的。绝对地。于是我们聊了一会儿。
bit about melatonin which like I said
关于褪黑素，就像我刚才说的。
select usage. Um a couple of other ones
选择用途。嗯，还有几个其他的
that we've got here um one of them is
我们这里有一个，其中一个是……
Valyan. Right. So when we talk Valyan is
瓦利安。正确的。所以当我们谈到瓦利安时
probably the most studied it's a root um
可能是研究最多的，它是一个根。
it's called the Valyrian root but to be
它被称为瓦雷利亚语词根，但实际上
clear it's an anti-anxiety medication
很明显，这是一种抗焦虑药物。
right so what it is is it's it helps
对，所以它的作用是帮助
lower your level of anxiety um and that
降低你的焦虑程度，嗯，还有
is the reason why it has a tendency to
这就是它有这种倾向的原因
work interestingly when you look at the
当你观察它时，你会发现它很有趣。
data it works better when combined with
数据与……结合使用效果更好
hops like what you'd find in beer so a
就像啤酒里用的那种啤酒花一样。
lot of times when you're looking for a
很多时候，当你寻找……
preparation you should look for Valyan
你应该寻找瓦利安的准备工作
plus hops as the preparation also we
此外，我们还加入了啤酒花作为配料。
should talk for a talking about
应该谈谈谈论
supplements. A lot of people don't
补充剂。很多人都不这么做。
understand this, but a lot of people
我明白这一点，但很多人
will put a whole bunch of different
会放很多不同的东西
supplements together and put it into a
将各种补充剂混合在一起，放入一个
capsule. I don't think that's the best
胶囊。我觉得那不是最好的。
idea. I think you should have single
主意。我认为你应该单身
ingredient supplementation.
成分补充。
&gt;&gt; Why?
为什么？
&gt;&gt; Well, number one, you get the correct
首先，你要得到正确的
dose so you know it's actually working
服用剂量，这样你就知道它确实有效。
for you. There's a lot of companies out
为你。有很多公司
there that are uh that make a powder or
有一些能制成粉末的
something and they put a bunch of stuff
他们放了一些东西，还放了一堆东西。
in it and they put just enough in there
他们往里面放了适量的料。
to be able to say it on the ingredient
能够在配料表上注明
profile, but not enough for it to
有一定背景，但还不足以……
actually do any good for the patient.
实际上对病人没有任何好处。
So, I like using single ingredient pro
所以我喜欢使用单一成分产品
uh supplement profiles because I know
呃，补充剂成分表，因为我知道
exactly how much of each thing that I'm
我每样东西到底有多少
going to get in there and I can make
我要进去，而且我能做到
sure that it's the correct dosage for
务必确保剂量正确。
the what the person needs. So, I prefer
这个人需要的东西。所以，我更喜欢
single ingredient supplementation.
单一成分补充剂。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, val Valyan.
好的。所以，val Valyan。
&gt;&gt; Yep. Valyan root.
是的。瓦利安根。
&gt;&gt; Not going to mess up my hormones?
不会扰乱我的激素水平吧？
&gt;&gt; Nope. It's not going to mess up your
没有。这不会搞砸你的
hormones.
激素。
&gt;&gt; Going to help me with overthinking?
能帮我克服过度思考吗？
&gt;&gt; Probably not. What it'll probably do is
可能不会。它可能会这样做：
slow your thinking down a little bit
稍微放慢你的思考速度。
depending upon how much of it you take.
取决于你服用的剂量。
Um, I think if you were looking for a if
嗯，我想如果你在寻找一个“如果”
you're looking for something that's
你正在寻找这样的东西
going to slow down your thinking, then I
然后我打算放慢你的思考速度。
would say we don't have the the thing
会说我们没有那个东西。
here, but it's called GABA, GABA. Um,
这里，但它叫做 GABA，GABA。嗯，
gamma amunobbuteric acid. So, this is a
γ-氨基丁酸。所以，这是一个
substance that your body makes. It's
你身体产生的物质。它是
kind of the breaks of the brain, and you
大脑的某种断裂，还有你
can buy it um as a supplement. I've had
可以作为保健品购买。我已经有了
several people use that, and that seems
好几个人都用那个，而且这似乎
to help calm people down in the evening
帮助人们在晚上平静下来
times.
次数。
&gt;&gt; What about ashwanaganda or whatever it's
那南非醉茄或者其他什么药材呢？
called?
叫什么？
&gt;&gt; Ashwagandha.
南非醉茄。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. I just kind of like saying it.
确切地。我就是喜欢这么说。
So, here's my theory on supplementation
所以，这是我关于补充剂的理论
is the first thing I tell people to do
这是我告诉人们要做的第一件事。
is go do blood work. Okay? What
去做血液检查。好的？什么
deficiencies do you have? Fix your
你有哪些不足之处？修复你的
deficiencies first before we start going
先找出不足之处，然后再开始行动。
to the valyians and the melatonins of it
对瓦利安人和它的褪黑素
all. If you're deficient in vitamin D,
全部。如果你缺乏维生素D，
magnesium, iron, fix those three things
镁、铁，补好这三样东西。
first. Dude, I can't tell you. I pro 15%
第一的。兄弟，我不能告诉你。我支持15%
of the people that show up at my
那些出现在我面前的人
doorstep we do blood work on and all I
我们在家门口做了血液检查，而我
do is fix their deficiencies and their
要做的就是弥补他们的不足和他们的
sleep magically gets better.
睡眠质量神奇地变好了。
&gt;&gt; What are some of the surprising things
有哪些令人惊讶的事情
though that you discover like blood
虽然你发现它就像血液
sugar like diabetes that impacts sleep?
血糖高得像糖尿病一样，会影响睡眠？
No,
不，
&gt;&gt; it absolutely does. I also think that a
确实如此。我也认为
lot of people who have uncontrolled
很多人无法控制
diabetes, it wakes them up in the middle
糖尿病，它会在半夜把他们吵醒。
of the night um because their blood
夜幕降临，因为他们的血液
sugar gets so low and then they're
血糖降到很低，然后他们……
hungry in the middle of the night. Then
半夜饿了。然后
they up eating in the middle of the
他们在中间吃东西
night then they have a sleep eating
晚上，他们会吃睡前食物。
syndrome which is kind of a pain.
这是一种很麻烦的综合征。
&gt;&gt; There's this one here that I've never
这里有一个我从未见过的
heard of before. What's this uh it's
以前听说过。这是什么？呃，这是……
called tryptophan. So uh elptophan in in
称为色氨酸。所以，呃，益生菌在
particular. So tryptophan is the
特别的。所以色氨酸是
substance that we find in turkey that
我们在火鸡中发现的那种物质
has a tendency to make people sleepy.
有使人犯困的倾向。
However, when you really look at the
然而，当你真正仔细审视……
data, you'd have to eat a 46 pound
根据数据，你得吃掉一个46磅的物体。
turkey in order to get enough tryptophan
为了摄取足够的色氨酸，可以吃火鸡。
to make you sleepy. Even in my best days
让你犯困。即使在我状态最好的时候
in college, dude, I couldn't eat a 46
老兄，大学的时候我连46号都吃不下。
pound turkey. Okay? Same holds true with
一磅火鸡。好的？同样的道理也适用于
milk. Um, tryptophan is the thing in
牛奶。嗯，色氨酸是关键所在。
warm milk that supposedly makes people
据说能使人变热的牛奶
uh, sleepy, but once again, you'd have
呃，有点困，但再一次，你会……
to drink almost a half a gallon of warm
喝了将近半加仑温水
milk, which is kind of disgusting um, in
牛奶，嗯，有点恶心。
order to do it. Tryptophan can be
奉命执行。色氨酸可以是
helpful for people if you have a
如果你有的话，这对人们会有帮助
tryptophan deficiency, but it's
色氨酸缺乏症，但它是
definitely something that lowers a
绝对是降低……的某种东西
little bit of anxiety and can make you
一点点焦虑就能让你
feel a little bit sleepy, but it is a
感觉有点困，但这是个
naturally occurring amino acid in your
你体内天然存在的氨基酸
system.
系统。
&gt;&gt; Calcium.
钙。
&gt;&gt; So, calcium turns out is interesting
所以，钙原来挺有意思的。
because when you mix calcium with
因为当你把钙和
magnesium, it's easier to absorb. So for
镁更容易被人体吸收。所以对于
some people mag we what we've discovered
有些人喜欢我们发现的东西
is if you have a magnesium deficiency
如果你缺镁的话……
and you fix the magnesium deficiency in
然后你解决了镁缺乏症。
many cases it can actually help with
很多情况下它确实能有所帮助。
overall sleep and calcium is one of the
整体睡眠和钙是其中之一
things that can be added to it that
可以添加到其中的内容
helps with absorption. Now unfortunately
有助于吸收。很遗憾，现在情况变得很糟糕。
the big problem is that there are 13
最大的问题是，有13个
different kinds of magnesium out there
市面上有各种不同的镁。
and so people don't know what's been
所以人们不知道发生了什么。
studied and what hasn't. So, I'm here to
研究过什么，以及哪些没有研究过。所以，我来这里是为了
let you know there's only a couple of
让你知道只有几个
brands out there that have actually been
市面上确实有一些品牌
studied for magnesium. The ones I like
研究了镁元素。我喜欢的那些
is there's one called magnesium 308,
有一种叫做镁308的元素，
which is made by a company called Magen.
它是由一家名为Magen的公司生产的。
Um, they actually have a published
嗯，他们实际上已经发表了一篇论文。
research study in the journals. That's
期刊上的研究论文。那是
why I mentioned their brand name. I have
这就是我提到他们品牌名称的原因。我有
no association with them. There's also
与他们没有任何关联。还有
another company called Upgraded
另一家名为 Upgraded 的公司
Formulas. They make a magnesium. And
公式。它们生产镁。和
kind of funny story is the guy who runs
有个挺搞笑的故事，就是那个跑腿的家伙。
mag uh upgraded formulas told me he says
mag uh 升级配方告诉我他说
my magnesium is the best in the world. I
我的镁是世界上最好的。我
can make anybody fall asleep. And I
能让任何人入睡。我
said, "Hey, you want to put your money
他说：“嘿，你想把钱投进去吗？”
where your mouth is? Let's do a clinical
你的嘴在哪儿？我们来做个临床研究。
trial." He handed me a check for 75
审判。”他递给我一张75美元的支票。
grand. I went and did a clinical trial
盛大。我去做了一项临床试验。
and he was right. His magnesium really
他说的没错。他的镁真的
made people sleep better.
改善了人们的睡眠质量。
&gt;&gt; What is magnesium doing?
镁的作用是什么？
&gt;&gt; So, we're not 100% sure. In the
所以，我们不能百分之百确定。在
deficient people, it's it's obviously
有缺陷的人，这显然是
clearing up the deficiency of magnesium.
纠正镁缺乏症。
And then magnesium is used in about I
然后镁被用于大约 I
think almost 300 different functions in
想想看，大约有300种不同的功能
the body. So it probably lets the body
身体。所以它可能让身体
work more efficiently and probably that
工作效率更高，而且可能
helps to overall sleep. But I'm not
有助于改善整体睡眠质量。但我不是
convinced that we have the whole
确信我们拥有全部
mechanism of action worked out. I will
作用机制已阐明。我会
tell you that when people take magnesium
告诉你，当人们服用镁时……
they tell me that they introspectively
他们告诉我，他们内省
feel calmer and we definitely know that
感觉更平静了，我们当然知道这一点。
it can definitely help uh cause a
它肯定有助于……
relaxation response in the musculature.
肌肉的放松反应。
So I think that might have something to
所以我认为这可能与此有关。
do with that.
就这么办吧。
&gt;&gt; Why did you bring a banana and a knife
你为什么带了香蕉和刀？
and a teapot? Ah, this is my favorite
还有茶壶？啊，这是我最喜欢的
way to get magnesium.
获取镁的方法。
&gt;&gt; A lot of people want to know, "How
很多人都想知道，“如何
should I take my supplements? I'm tired
我应该服用营养补充剂吗？我累了
of taking a fistful of pills every
每隔一段时间就吃一把药片
morning, Michael. There's these powders.
早上好，迈克尔。这里有这些粉末。
Like, what what's the best way?" The
比如，最好的方法是什么？
best way So, number one, supplementation
最佳方法，所以，第一，补充营养
is when you're not getting all of the
就是当你没有得到全部的
things, the vitamins and minerals that
这些东西，维生素和矿物质
you need from your food. So, the best
你需要从食物中摄取营养。所以，最好的
place to get it from is food. Generally
获取它的途径是食物。一般来说
speaking, turns out magnesium is one of
说到镁，它就是其中之一。
the best ones, but it's problematic
最好的那些，但这也有问题。
because we have to eat our magnesium.
因为我们必须从食物中摄取镁。
Our body doesn't actually produce it.
我们的身体实际上并不产生这种物质。
themselves. And by the way, you could
他们自己。顺便说一句，你可以
eat a bushel of kale and still not get
吃了一大堆羽衣甘蓝，还是没能
enough magnesium because here in the
这里有足够的镁
United States, the soil has been
美国，土壤一直是
overtilled, which means the magnesium
过度耕作，这意味着镁
isn't in the soil. So, it's not coming
不在土壤里。所以，它不会来了。
up through the root stocks and allowing
向上穿过根茎，并允许
people to have it. So, a lot of people
人们需要它。所以，很多人
require magnesium supplementation.
需要补充镁。
Believe it or not, between magnesium and
信不信由你，镁和
vitamin D, I'd say we've probably
维生素D，我想我们可能已经……
covered most of America in terms of
就面积而言，覆盖了美国的大部分地区。
having a deficiency. Bananas are loaded
存在缺陷。香蕉已装载完毕
with magnesium, but it turns out it's
含有镁，但结果却是
not the fruit, it's the peel.
不是果肉，而是果皮。
&gt;&gt; Oh. itself. So, no, I'm not going to
哦。本身。所以，不，我不会……
make you eat the peel. Don't worry. So,
让你连皮都吃掉。不用担心。所以，
I developed a recipe that I call banana
我研发了一种叫做香蕉的食谱。
tea. All this is is a regular old
茶。这一切都只是普通的旧事物。
banana. So, what I what you do is you
香蕉。所以，你所做的就是……
cut off the stem, right? And cut it in
把茎切掉，对吧？然后把它切进去
half and then you drop it in to some
一半，然后你把它扔进某个地方
boiling water. Okay? So, we've already
开水。好的？所以，我们已经
done this, right? And you can see the
已经做过了吧？你可以看到
banana has turned brown, right? It's
香蕉变褐了，对吧？它是
been soaking in the boiling water. So,
一直浸泡在沸水中。所以，
it's not really tea. It's just basically
它其实不是茶。基本上就是这样
hot banana water. But with the banana
热香蕉水。但是香蕉
from the skin, you also get these things
从皮肤上，你也会得到这些东西。
called phytostereroids that actually
被称为植物甾醇的物质，实际上
help you absorb the magnesium better
帮助你更好地吸收镁。
than if you just had it from a
比你直接从……那里得到它要好得多
supplement. So you have to really like
补充。所以你必须真的很喜欢
bananas. My daughter says it's very
香蕉。我女儿说这非常
banana e. Dad, the flavor, I mean.
香蕉 e.爸爸，我是说味道。
&gt;&gt; Oh, it does smell like bananas.
哦，闻起来确实像香蕉。
&gt;&gt; I'm telling you, if you like bananas,
我跟你说，如果你喜欢香蕉，
&gt;&gt; it's nice.
挺好的。
&gt;&gt; I know it's nice. And you can use this
我知道它很好。你可以使用这个
as a like an evening ritual and you can
就像一种晚间仪式，你可以
make banana tea and have it in the
做香蕉茶，然后喝。
evening with, you know, a biscuit or
晚上吃点饼干什么的，你知道的。
what have you and have a nice and read a
你有什么？祝你阅读愉快！
book and just be chill.
订个书，放松一下。
&gt;&gt; How do I know the magnesium is actually
我怎么知道镁含量是否真的存在
in there?
里面呢？
&gt;&gt; Cuz it came through from the from the um
因为它是从……传过来的
steeping in the water.
浸泡在水中。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; Well, you could test it if we want, but
当然，如果我们愿意的话，可以测试一下，但是
I can assure you it's in there. You need
我可以向你保证，它就在里面。你需要
to leave it in there for about 5 minutes
把它放在里面大约5分钟。
and we've been talking for a while, so
我们已经谈了一段时间了，所以
I'm pretty sure it's there.
我非常确定它在那里。
&gt;&gt; And and how long before sleep to get
睡前多久需要入睡？
those effects?
那些影响？
&gt;&gt; I would say about 2530 minutes. You
我估计大约是2530分钟。你
don't want to have too much, by the way,
顺便说一句，我不想​​有太多。
because then you're gonna have to wake
因为那样你就得醒来
up and pee. So try if you can
起来小便。所以，如果可以的话，就试试吧。
&gt;&gt; to be able to have it about 30 40
能够拥有大约30到40个
minutes before bed.
睡前几分钟。
&gt;&gt; So you can put it in anything. A lot of
所以你可以把它放进任何东西里。很多
people have different types of teas. So
人们喜欢喝不同种类的茶。所以
you could just use that as the water
你可以直接用它当水用。
instead.
反而。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Oh, without question. Actually,
是的。哦，毫无疑问。实际上，
that would be a really good idea. And
那真是个好主意。和
you could, if you did it, if you mix it
如果你这么做，如果你把它混合起来，你就能做到。
with like a fruit tea, like an herbal
像水果茶，像草药茶
fruit tea, that would be really
水果茶，那真是太棒了
delicious.
可口的。
&gt;&gt; Are there any other supplements that
还有其他补充剂吗？
you, you know, you do encourage people
你知道，你确实鼓励了人们
to take if they're struggling with sleep
如果他们睡眠不好，可以服用。
that we haven't talked about yet?
我们还没讨论过的吗？
&gt;&gt; We haven't talked about vitamin D, and
我们还没有讨论过维生素D，而且
that's a big one. So it turns out that
那可是个大问题。结果是这样的
vitamin D is a circadian pacemaker. So
维生素D是昼夜节律的调节器。所以
when light comes into your eyeballs, it
当光线进入你的眼球时，它
helps change your whole uh circadian
有助于改变你的整个昼夜节律
system. And if you're if light is coming
系统。如果你看到光明即将到来
in for a certain amount of time, about
在一定时间内，大约
15 minutes, your body will start to
15分钟后，你的身体会开始……
produce vitamin D. Vitamin D does a
产生维生素D。维生素D的作用是
whole host of important things to your
对你来说，有很多重要的事情
body. But most importantly from a sleep
身体。但最重要的是从睡眠中
perspective, is it helps regulate
从这个角度来看，它有助于调节
melatonin and when your body produces
褪黑激素以及身体产生褪黑激素的时间
it. So by taking vitamin D every day or
它。所以，每天服用维生素D或
getting 15 minutes of sunshine, either
晒15分钟太阳，
way, you're going to be in better shape.
这样一来，你的身体状况会更好。
So, like as an example, my morning
举个例子，我的早晨
routine that I have all my patients do
这是我要求所有患者都做的常规操作。
is I have them when they wake up in the
我会在他们醒来的时候拥有他们。
morning, I have them uh go outside if
早上，我让他们出去走走。
it's if it's, you know, nice out, sit in
如果天气好的话，就坐在里面。
a chair and have 15 deep breaths merely
找把椅子，深呼吸15次，就这么简单。
to wake up the respiratory system, then
然后唤醒呼吸系统
15 ounces of water cuz once again,
15盎司水，因为再一次，
remember, you're dehydrated, and then 15
记住，你脱水了，然后是15
minutes of sunshine. So, they can do all
阳光照射几分钟。所以他们可以做所有事
of this together at the same time. And
同时进行。和
it's a nice way to wake up in the
这是个不错的起床方式。
morning.
早晨。
I don't know any founder who started
我不认识任何一位创业者。
their business because they like doing
他们之所以做自己的生意，是因为他们喜欢这样做。
admin. But whether you like it or not,
行政。但不管你喜不喜欢，
it's a huge part of running a business
这是企业运营中至关重要的一部分。
successfully. And it's something that
成功地。这是某件事
can quickly become all-consuming,
可能很快就会让人完全沉浸其中，
confusing, and honestly a real tax
令人困惑，而且说实话，这确实是一笔不小的税。
because, you know, it's taking your
因为，你知道，这需要你
attention away from the most important
注意力从最重要的事情上转移开来
work. And that's why our sponsor Intuit
工作。这就是为什么我们的赞助商 Intuit 如此受欢迎的原因。
QuickBooks helps my team streamline a
QuickBooks帮助我的团队简化流程
lot of their admin. I asked my team
他们的很多管理员。我问了我的团队
about it and they said it saves them
他们谈到这件事时说，这能救他们。
around 12 hours a month. 78% of Intuate
每月大约12小时。 78% 的 Intuate
QuickBooks users say it's made running
QuickBooks用户表示，它让运行变得轻松快捷。
their business significantly easier. And
他们的业务开展起来轻松多了。和
Intuit QuickBooks new AI agent works
Intuit QuickBooks 的新 AI 代理有效
with you to streamline all of your
与您一起简化您的所有流程
workflows. They sync with all of the
工作流程。它们与所有
tools that you currently use. They
您目前使用的工具。他们
automate things that slow the wheel in
自动化那些会减慢速度的事情
the process of your business. They look
您的业​​务流程。他们看起来
after invoicing, payments, financial
开具发票、付款、财务之后
analysis, all of it in one place. But
分析结果，尽在一处。但
what is great is that it's not just AI.
最棒的是，它不仅仅是人工智能。
There's still human support on hand if
如果需要，仍然会有人工支持人员随时提供帮助。
you need it. Intuitit QuickBooks has
你需要它。 Intuit QuickBooks 拥有
evolved into a platform that scales with
演变成一个可扩展的平台
growing businesses. So if you want help
不断发展的企业。所以，如果你需要帮助的话
getting out of the weeds, out of admin,
摆脱琐事，摆脱行政工作
just search for IntuIt QuickBooks. Now,
只需搜索 IntuIt QuickBooks 即可。现在，
this is something that I've made for
这是我为……制作的东西
you. I realize that the DEIO audience
你。我意识到DEIO的受众
are strivals
是奋斗
that we want to accomplish. And one of
我们想要达成的目标。其中一个
the things I've learned is that when you
我学到的是，当你
aim at the big big big goal, it can feel
朝着远大的目标努力，你会感觉
incredibly psychologically uncomfortable
极度心理不适
because it's kind of like being stood at
因为感觉就像站在……
the foot of Mount Everest and looking
珠穆朗玛峰脚下，眺望
upwards. The way to accomplish your
向上。实现目标的方法
goals is by breaking them down into tiny
实现目标的方法是将目标分解成小块。
small steps. And we call this in our
小步前进。我们称之为我们的
team the 1%. And actually this
团队中那1%的人。实际上，
philosophy is highly responsible for
哲学对此负有很大责任
much of our success here. So, what we've
我们在这里取得的成功很大程度上归功于此。所以，我们已经……
done so that you at home can accomplish
这样做是为了方便您在家完成
any big goal that you have is we've made
你们的任何远大目标，我们都实现了。
these 1% diaries and we released these
我们发布了这些1%的日记。
last year and they all sold out. So, I
去年全部售罄。所以，我
asked my team over and over again to
我反复要求我的团队
bring the diaries back, but also to
把日记带回来，但也要
introduce some new colors and to make
引入一些新颜色并制作
some minor tweaks to the diary. So, now
对日记进行了一些小修改。所以现在
we have a better range for you. So, if
我们为您提供更丰富的选择。所以，如果
you have a big goal in mind and you need
你心中有一个远大的目标，你需要
a framework and a process and some
一个框架、一个流程和一些
motivation, then I highly recommend you
如果你有动力，那么我强烈推荐你
get one of these diaries before they all
趁它们还没全部售罄之前，赶紧入手一本吧
sell out once again. And you can get
再次售罄。而且你可以获得
yours now at the diary.com where you can
现在就访问 diary.com，即可拥有属于你的 diary.com，你可以在那里……
get 20% off our Black Friday bundle. And
黑色星期五特惠套装享八折优惠。和
if you want the link, the link is in the
如果你想要链接，链接就在这里。
description below.
详情如下。
&gt;&gt; So, let's talk about waking up in the
那么，我们来谈谈醒来时的感受吧。
morning.
早晨。
&gt;&gt; Sure.
当然。
&gt;&gt; Morning routines.
晨间例行事项。
&gt;&gt; Yep.
是的。
&gt;&gt; A lot of people talk about what's the
很多人都在谈论什么是
perfect morning routine? Do you need to
完美的晨间习惯？你需要吗？
have a morning routine? What's your take
你早上有固定的习惯吗？你的看法是什么？
on that? So, it depends upon how
就那件事而言？所以，这取决于如何
disciplined you want to be and it
你想成为一个自律的人，而且
depends upon how much time you have. I
这取决于你有多少时间。我
can tell you what my morning routine is
我可以告诉你我的晨间习惯是什么
because it's very specific and I I've
因为它非常具体，而且我已经
discovered that it works really really
发现它真的非常有效
well for me. So, I wake up naturally
对我来说是这样。所以，我自然醒来。
somewhere between 6:10 and about 6:25 or
大约在 6:10 到 6:25 之间，或者
so. My body just seems to naturally wake
所以。我的身体似乎自然而然地就醒了。
up. I do 15 minutes of red light
向上。我做了15分钟的红光照射。
therapy. So, I have a red light uh in my
治疗。所以，我的车上亮起了红灯。
office that I sit in front of and I do
我坐在办公室前面，我做
my meditation at the same time in the
同时，我的冥想也在进行中
morning time. So, I have about 15
早晨。所以，我大概有15个
minutes of meditation. Sometimes what
冥想几分钟。有时是什么
I'll do is um I'll sit on the floor and
我打算……嗯，我会坐在地板上，
the boys will come and sit on my lap and
男孩们会过来坐在我的腿上，
then we'll all meditate together. I know
然后我们一起冥想。我知道
that sounds a little weird. Then um we
听起来有点奇怪。然后，嗯，我们
use a we do a 15-minute walk. I try not
我们用……进行15分钟的步行。我尽量不
to have any music or any telephone or
拥有任何音乐或任何电话或
anything like that uh up at all up until
类似的事情，呃，一直到现在。
this point. I put the dogs away and then
这一点。我把狗关起来，然后
I hit the gym. I'm at the gym from about
我去健身房了。我从大约……开始就在健身房了。
8 till about 9:30, 10:00. I do a sauna
8点到9点半左右，10点。我蒸桑拿
every day afterwards and then I'm in
之后每天都这样，然后我就进去了。
front of my desk by about 10:30 and
大约10:30，我来到办公桌前。
that's is when I have my breakfast. And
那就是我吃早餐的时间。和
so I make the same breakfast almost
所以我几乎每天都做同样的早餐。
every morning. I do uh ground turkey
每天早上。我确实做了碎火鸡肉
with uh a third of a pound of ground
用三分之一磅的面粉
turkey, three eggs and broccoli and I I
火鸡、三个鸡蛋、西兰花和我
put it all into a skillet and I make it
把所有食材都放进煎锅里，然后我就开始做。
every morning.
每天早上。
&gt;&gt; Do you use any sleep trackers?
你使用睡眠追踪器吗？
&gt;&gt; In the past I've used uh a few of them.
过去我用过其中一些。
I I try them out because a lot of my
我尝试它们是因为我的很多……
patients try them out. Um, I think if I
患者们可以试用一下。嗯，我想如果我
was going to be looking at them, I think
我想，我本来打算看看它们的。
the aura ring probably does the best
灵气戒指的效果可能最好。
job. I really don't think they've gotten
工作。我真的不认为他们已经得到了
there quite yet because remember depth
还没到那儿，因为要记住深度
of sleep is based on brain waves and
睡眠是基于脑电波的
it's hard to get brain waves from your
很难从你的大脑中获取脑电波
finger, right? And so what they're doing
手指，对吧？所以他们正在做什么
is they're creating a proxy. So they're
他们是不是在创建一个代理服务器？所以他们是
looking at heart rate or oxygen or pulse
观察心率、血氧饱和度或脉搏
or something along those lines and then
或者类似的事情，然后
saying, "Okay, when Stephven's at this
他说：“好的，当斯蒂芬在这个时候……”
pulse, we think he's in REM sleep, so
根据脉搏判断，我们认为他处于快速眼动睡眠期，所以
we're going to label every time that REM
我们将标记每次快速眼动睡眠（REM）的时间。
sleep." when in fact they don't really
“睡觉。”但实际上他们根本不睡觉。”
know because they're not measuring your
知道是因为他们没有衡量你的
brain waves. So I think until we get to
脑电波。所以我觉得直到我们……
the point where we can measure brain
我们能够测量大脑的点
waves from distally, I think we'll have
我想我们会听到来自远端的波浪。
a little bit better shot at it. However,
这次尝试成功了一点。然而，
&gt;&gt; there's some interesting things that are
有些事情很有趣。
going on kind of in the sleep tracker
睡眠追踪器里正在发生一些事情
world. And some people get a little too
世界。有些人有点太过了。
into the whole tracking of it all, if
如果要把这一切都追踪起来的话
you know what I mean. Like I can't count
你知道我的意思。就像我不会数数一样
the number of people that are like, "Oh
很多人会说：“哦
my god, Dr. Bruce, you know, this says I
我的天哪，布鲁斯医生，你知道，这上面写着我
only slept 14 minutes last night. Like
昨晚只睡了14分钟。喜欢
what do I do?" And I'm like, "Well,
我该怎么办？” 我心想，“嗯，
number one, how much did you sleep the
第一，你睡了多久？
night before?" And they say, "Oh, 16
前一天晚上？”他们说：“哦，16
minutes." I'm like, "Okay, well, let's
几分钟。” 我心想，“好吧，那我们……”
check you tomorrow." They come back
明天再联系你。”他们回来了
tomorrow, it's even worse, 12 minutes.
明天情况更糟，只有 12 分钟。
I'm like, "Oh, you're fine." They're
我心想：“哦，你没事吧。”他们是
like, "What?" I'm like, "Look, it's
比如，“什么？”我心想，“你看，这是……”
being consistently inaccurate. There's
始终不准确。有
no way you only got 14 minutes of deep
不可能，你只有14分钟的深度。
sleep, right? That's just not how the
睡觉，对吧？事情并非如此。
body works, right? But if you got 14
身体机能正常运作，对吧？但如果你得了14分
minutes, 14 minutes, and then one night
分钟，14 分钟，然后是一个夜晚
you look at your score and it's 407
你看了看自己的分数，是407分。
minutes.
分钟。
&gt;&gt; I want to know what happened on that
我想知道那天发生了什么事。
night."
夜晚。”
&gt;&gt; My friend was a big fan of Whoop. So, he
我的朋友是 Whoop 的忠实粉丝。所以，他
told me to try a Whoop. I tried a Whoop.
他让我试试 Whoop。我试了试 Whoop。
the the most I think critical thing it's
我认为最关键的是……
done for me is it allowed me to create
对我来说，它让我能够创造
some understanding of like causation and
对类似因果关系的一些理解和
like associations with my sleep. So one
就像与我的睡眠相关的联想。所以一个
of the ones that completely changed my
那些彻底改变我人生的人
life when I first wore my Whoop, which
我第一次佩戴 Whoop 时的生活，
by the way I'm an investor in the
顺便说一下，我是这家公司的投资者。
company so I have to disclaimer that
所以我必须声明，这是公司的事情。
&gt;&gt; um was I didn't realize how impactful
嗯，我之前没意识到影响这么大。
sleep alcohol was on my sleep.
酒精影响了我的睡眠。
&gt;&gt; It's massive.
它非常庞大。
&gt;&gt; Like it blew my mind cuz I had had one
这简直让我震惊，因为我之前也经历过一次。
glass of wine.
一杯葡萄酒。
&gt;&gt; Yep. And then the bloody whoop thing
是的。然后就是那该死的呜呜声
said you're either really sick um really
你说你要么病得很重，要么真的病得很重。
stressed or you drank alcohol. And then
压力过大或者喝了酒。进而
I watched a video online where they
我在网上看过一个视频，他们在视频里
compared all of the devices to the
将所有设备与……进行了比较
hospital grade stuff.
医用级产品。
&gt;&gt; Yep. Poly synography
是的。多维概要
&gt;&gt; and the Whoop 4 was the closest to the
Whoop 4 是最接近的
hospital grade. And then I contacted the
医院级。然后我联系了
company and said can I invest etc etc.
公司并问我是否可以投资等等。
I've also tried I've also tried like a
我也试过，我也试过像……
sleep and
睡眠和
&gt;&gt; I would argue that temperature like if
我认为温度就像……
we're talking about what is the easiest
我们正在讨论的是最容易的
thing to manipulate to change your sleep
改变睡眠的技巧
either good or bad temperature is it um
温度是好是坏？嗯……
and people don't realize it but you can
人们没有意识到这一点，但你可以
change the temperature in your bedroom
调整卧室温度
even in your bed and you can change the
即使在床上，你也可以改变
quality of your sleep. You mentioned
睡眠质量。你提到
eight that's a company that has a a
八，那是一家拥有……的公司
topper type of thing that can change the
可以改变事物的顶部装饰物
uh the temperature underneath the
呃，下面的温度
covers. There's also taking a look at
封面。此外，还要看看
the the accutramal that's on. So
戴着的Accutramal。所以
pillows, sheets, comforters, all of
枕头、床单、被子，所有
those things. But if you can get your
那些东西。但是如果你能得到你的
body to cool down, your body will go
为了降温，你的身体会……
down and get into deeper stages of
深入并进入更深的阶段
sleep. If you can stay cool versus
睡觉。如果你能保持冷静……
bumping up and down all night long,
整夜颠簸摇晃，
let's say you're a woman in menopause,
假设你是一位处于更年期的女性，
right? That becomes highly disruptive.
正确的？这会造成极大的干扰。
And so by being a by being able to keep
因此，通过保持
a consistent temperature stimulus to the
对……持续的温度刺激
body, it ends up sleeping a whole lot
身体最终会睡很多觉。
better.
更好的。
&gt;&gt; Dreams. Let's talk about dreams. People
梦想。我们来聊聊梦想吧。人们
are so fascinated by dreams,
他们对梦境如此着迷，
&gt;&gt; aren't they? I love it.
难道不是吗？我喜欢它。
&gt;&gt; But but so little is known about dreams.
但是，关于梦的了解却少之又少。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, yes and no. I mean, here's
是的。嗯，算是，也不算。我的意思是，这里是……
the thing. Dreams have been studied
那个东西。梦境已被研究
honestly since the dawn of time. If you
老实说，自古以来就是如此。如果你
look in the Bible, you will see that
查阅圣经，你会发现……
people are talking about dreams. If you
人们在谈论梦想。如果你
look at ancient texts, people are
看看古代文献，人们是
wondering about these crazy movies that
想知道这些疯狂的电影是什么样的
are going on in my head. Right? When you
我脑子里一直在想这些事。正确的？当你
start to look at dreams, here's the
开始研究梦境，以下是……
thing that I will tell you is dreams
我要告诉你的是梦
mean something to the dreamer. They
对做梦者来说具有某种意义。他们
don't necessarily mean something to
并不一定意味着什么
somebody who is not the dreamer. And so
一个并非做梦者的人。所以
when I do dream work and so I so to be
当我做梦境工作时，我就是这样。
clear, just take a step back, I took a
明白了，退后一步，我退后了一步。
year and a half and I became a dream
一年半后，我变成了一个梦
therapist. So what does that mean? What
治疗师。那这意味着什么？什么
is that even is that even a thing? So
那真的存在吗？所以
dream therapy, by the way, is not dream
顺便一提，梦境疗法并非梦境。
interpretation. That is not here's a
解释。这里没有
symbol, here's what that means. Dream
这个符号的含义如下。梦
therapy is where you use dreams in the
治疗就是利用梦境来进行治疗。
therapeutic context to help people with
为人们提供治疗环境，以帮助他们
things like depression and anxiety.
比如抑郁症和焦虑症。
&gt;&gt; Let me give you an example. A nightmare,
我举个例子。一场噩梦，
right? So when somebody has, let's say
正确的？所以当有人拥有，比如说
somebody was in an active theater of war
有人身处战区。
and they watched one of their friends,
他们看着他们的一个朋友，
god forbid, something terrible happened
天哪，千万别发生什么可怕的事情。
to them and that image is now in their
对他们来说，那幅画面如今就留在了他们的记忆中。
head and now they constantly have this
头部，现在他们一直有这个问题
image over and over and over. But what
图像反复出现。但是什么
happens is they're going, going, going
事情的经过是，他们一直在走，走，走
going and they wake up. They're going,
他们走了，然后醒了。他们要走了，
going, going going going, they wake up.
他们醒了。
We talked a little bit about it earlier
我们之前稍微谈过这件事。
that dreams are emotional metabolism,
梦是情感代谢的一种形式。
right? So dreams are where you work out
正确的？所以，梦境就是你锻炼的地方。
all of these different things that are
所有这些不同的事物
going on in your head and kind of become
你脑子里想的那些事，然后就变成了
okay with them so that way next day you
他们同意了，这样第二天你就可以……
can kind of move forward and keep keep
可以继续前进并保持
doing your thing.
做你自己的事。
&gt;&gt; Do we need to explain why we dream
我们需要解释为什么我们会做梦吗？
because I think that's the big sort of
因为我认为这才是最重要的。
&gt;&gt; Sure. So there's a couple of theories.
当然。所以现在有两种说法。
One theory is is that this is a great
一种理论认为，这是一个巨大的
stage for for practice, right? So we
这是练习用的舞台，对吧？所以，我们
dream about things that we're eventually
梦想着我们最终会实现的事物
going to try in the real world and so we
我们将在现实世界中尝试，所以我们
get a chance to practice them in our
有机会在我们的……中练习它们
head beforehand to to make sure it
事先前往以确保
doesn't we don't kind of screw the whole
我们难道不会把一切都搞砸吗？
thing up. So there's that whole idea of
把事情办好。所以，这就是整个想法的由来……
being able to kind of work stuff out in
能够想办法解决问题
my head. Then there's the processing
我的头。然后是处理环节。
idea that we talked about before where
我们之前讨论过的想法是
this is emotional metabolism. So
这就是情绪代谢。所以
therapy,
治疗，
&gt;&gt; right? Exactly. It's like you go to
正确的？确切地。就像你去
therapy every single night. I actually
每晚都要接受治疗。我其实
that's a really good way to think about
这确实是一个很好的思考方式。
it. I hadn't thought about it like that,
它。我之前没这样想过。
but I think I'm going to use that. I'm
但我认为我会用它。我是
going to take that from you. Um, I like
我要把它从你这儿拿走。嗯，我喜欢
that dreams are therapy every single
梦境本身就是一种疗愈。
night because they really are. You're
夜晚，因为他们确实是。你是
really moving through a lot of that
确实经历了很多这样的事情。
emotionality. Some people think dreams
情绪化。有些人认为梦
are complete nonsense. Some people think
完全是胡说八道。有些人认为
that's just some crazy movie in your
那只是你看过的一部很疯狂的电影而已。
head and it's just this after effect of
头部，这只是后遗症而已
your brain moving into a different mode
你的大脑进入了一种不同的模式
and who knows what it could mean. I find
谁知道这意味着什么。我发现
that one hard to believe myself
我自己都难以置信。
&gt;&gt; because humans don't do anything.
因为人类什么都不做。
&gt;&gt; I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
&gt;&gt; That isn't for some type of survival
那并非出于某种生存目的。
benefit
益处
&gt;&gt; for sure.
一定。
&gt;&gt; It's a waste of energy or you know
这是浪费能源，或者你知道的。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I agree. And so if we looked at it
是的，我同意。所以如果我们仔细观察一下……
from an evolutionary perspective, like
从进化论的角度来看，比如
what is the evolutionary purpose of
进化的目的是什么？
dreams, I would argue that it probably
梦境，我认为很可能
has something to do with emotions and
这与情绪有关，
being able to uh move through some
能够呃，穿过一些
emotionally difficult times and or it's
情绪低落的时期，或者说，这是
an early warning system. A lot of people
预警系统。很多人
dream things and uh it helps them
做梦，嗯，这对他们有帮助。
understand something else that's going
了解其他正在发生的事情
on in their life. You ever heard the um
在他们的生活中。你听过“嗯”这个说法吗？
thing uh people say, I before I make a
人们常说的一件事，在我做之前……
big decision, I want to sleep on it.
这是个重大决定，我想好好考虑一下。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Right. this is what they're doing is
正确的。这就是他们正在做的。
when they sleep on it all these
当他们睡着时，所有这些
desperate pieces of information come
绝望的消息传来
together and work themselves so that you
共同努力，让自己变得如此，这样你
can come to a solution. So I think the
可以找到解决方案。所以我认为
other thing that reason that we dream is
我们做梦的另一个原因是
to come to solutions and to create
找到解决方案并创造
innovation
创新
&gt;&gt; that tracks in my life. I I can be going
这在我的生活中留下了印记。我可以走了
to bed really thinking about something
上床睡觉前，我一直在想一些事情。
quite like you know remunerating about
就像你知道的，报酬丰厚
something to the point that it's like
某种程度上就像
overthinking and it's a problem. It's
想太多是个问题。它是
stressing me out.
让我压力很大。
&gt;&gt; I can get eight hours sleep and wake up
我可以睡足八小时，然后醒来。
and it's like the clouds have parted,
仿佛拨云见日一般。
&gt;&gt; right? It's like magic.
正确的？简直就像魔法一样。
&gt;&gt; It's like magic.
简直就像魔法一样。
&gt;&gt; It's great. And I only real realized
这很棒。我直到最近才真正意识到
this in the last couple of years when
在过去的几年里，这种情况
you know business my businesses got
你知道我的生意有
bigger and there was more problems to to
规模更大，问题也更多。
work through that like actually I could
想想办法，其实我可以做到。
use sleep as a weapon against the
利用睡眠作为对抗……的武器
problem. Absolutely.
问题。绝对地。
&gt;&gt; Versus trying to stay up all night and
与试图熬夜相比
solve the problem. I could focus on the
解决问题。我可以专注于
sleep to solve the problem.
睡觉解决问题。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I do it all the time. And and what
是的。我经常这样做。还有什么
you can actually do it's called priming
你其实可以这么做，这叫做预热。
is you can think about the problem in a
你可以从以下角度思考这个问题：
in a way before you go to sleep and then
以某种方式，在你睡觉之前，然后
it triggers your brain to think about
它会触发你的大脑去思考……
the problem while you're sleeping. what
睡眠时出现的问题。什么
you write it down or do you
你把它写下来吗？还是……
&gt;&gt; There's a lot of different ways you can
有很多不同的方法可以
go about doing it. So, for example, what
开始去做吧。例如，什么
I have some people do is write down
我让一些人这样做，就是写下来。
everything they can remember in their
他们能记住的一切
dream beforehand before they come to
在他们到来之前就已做好了梦。
therapy. But what you can do is
治疗。但你可以做的是
something different. If you want to
一些不同的东西。如果你想
change your dream, you write it all
改变你的梦想，一切由你书写。
down, but that you change the ending.
向下，但你改变了结局。
Okay? And you read it several times
好的？你读了好几遍
before bed and it will actually change
睡前这样做，它真的会改变。
your dream.
你的梦想。
&gt;&gt; So, what am I writing down before bed
那么，我睡前要写些什么呢？
then?
然后？
&gt;&gt; So, let's say you had a scary dream.
假设你做了一个可怕的梦。
Okay? You're walking through a haunted
好的？你正走在一处闹鬼的地方
house and something terrible is going to
房子里似乎有什么可怕的事情要发生了。
happen when you walk out the back door
当你从后门出去时，就会发生这种情况
&gt;&gt; the night before.
前一天晚上。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. The night before. Then I have you
是的。前一天晚上。然后我就有你了
write all of that down and then when you
把所有这些都写下来，然后当你
come into session with me, I say, "Okay,
跟我一起来开会，我说：“好的，
we're going to change the ending because
我们要改结局，因为
at the at the very end, you walked out
最后，你走了出去。
onto the porch and somebody got you
你走到门廊上，然后有人抓住了你。
right." So instead of that happening,
没错。”所以，与其那样发生，
you're going to walk out to the porch
你要走到门廊去。
and you're going to pull out a gun and
然后你要拔枪……
you're going to shoot the guy. Okay? And
你要开枪打死他。好的？和
so we change that in the dream in the
所以我们在梦里改变了这一点。
right in what you wrote down and then we
就按你写下的来，然后我们
talk about it in therapy. And then right
在心理咨询中谈谈这件事。然后就对了
before bed, you read this to yourself
睡前，你把这段话读给自己听。
multiple times and it over 7 to 10 days,
多次，持续7到10天。
you change the ending of the dream.
你改变了梦的结局。
&gt;&gt; And how does that help?
那这有什么帮助呢？
&gt;&gt; So it makes it more positive. And when
所以这让它变得更积极了。而当
you change the ending, the reason you're
你改变了结局，原因如下：
waking up is something is scaring you so
醒来后，有什么事让你感到害怕吗？
much that you're waking up and you stop
很多时候你醒来，然后就停止了。
processing. And so when you change the
加工。所以当你改变
ending and you don't wake up, you
结束了，你再也醒不过来了，你
continue to process and then you move
继续处理，然后你移动
past the dream. Just like you said when
梦境已逝。就像你之前说的那样
you wake up and the clouds have cleared.
你醒来时，云层已经散去。
&gt;&gt; A lot of people wake up and the clouds
很多人醒来时，看到云层。
don't clear because they have nightmares
不要清理，因为他们会做噩梦。
and they keep repeating it over and over
他们一遍又一遍地重复着这句话。
and over again.
一遍又一遍。
&gt;&gt; H
H
&gt;&gt; it's quite remarkable. The process is
这真是太了不起了。这个过程是
very interesting. So what I do is I
很有意思。所以我的做法是……
bring them into session put them into a
把他们带进会议室，把他们安置好
mild hypnotic state uh only by doing
轻度催眠状态，嗯，只有通过这样做才能达到。
some simple breath work. Right? So let
一些简单的呼吸练习。正确的？所以，让我们
me give you an example of somebody that
我给你举个例子，这个人……
I worked with and tell you exactly how
我曾与他们共事，并会详细地告诉你具体情况。
it went. So I was working with somebody
它走了。当时我正在和某人一起工作。
who had had uh pretty significant
谁有过相当重要的经历
trauma. They had been raped. Right? And
创伤。她们遭到了强奸。正确的？和
so they were having nightmares about
所以他们做了噩梦
this. So serious situation, right? So
这。情况很严重，对吧？所以
she had a she had a nightmare of being
她做了一个噩梦，梦见自己……
in a jungle. And so I had her come in
在丛林里。于是我就让她进来了。
session, wrote it all down. And when we
会议内容全部记录下来了。当我们
got to the end, we were walking through
走到尽头，我们正穿过
the jungle. She was actually being
丛林。她实际上是
chased through the jungle. So I turn to
在丛林中追逐。于是我转向
her and I say, "Okay, well, we're in the
她和我说道：“好吧，我们现在在……”
jungle. Tell me more about this jungle."
丛林。请您多介绍一下这片丛林。
And she says, "What do you mean?" I
她问：“你什么意思？”我
said, "Well, in jungles there's lots of
他说：“嗯，丛林里有很多……”
tropical plants. There a lot of colorful
热带植物。有很多色彩缤纷的
flowers." and she'll stop and you can
“鲜花。”她会停下来，然后你就可以……
see she's looking around inside her head
你看，她正在环顾自己的内心世界。
at the dreamscape and then she says,
在梦境中，然后她说，
"Oh, there are there's some beautiful
哦，那里有一些美丽的
flowers over there. I've now advanced
那边有花。我现在已经晋升了
the dream, right?" Because she didn't
那是个梦，对吧？”因为她没有。
know there were flowers before. Now
我知道之前这里长过花。现在
she's imagined that they're flowers. I'm
她想象它们是花。我是
moving the dream forward. So, we go over
让梦想继续前进。所以，我们来回顾一下。
and we smell the flower. And I said,
我们闻到了花香。我说，
"Well, you know, usually in jungles
“嗯，你知道，通常在丛林里……”
there's there's animals. Are there any
那里有动物。有吗？
animals?"
动物？”
"Yeah, there's a lion." "Oh gosh, is the
“是啊，那儿有一头狮子。” “哦，天哪，是……”
lion friendly?" "Yeah, the lion is
对狮子友好吗？“是的，狮子是
friendly. Can we go over and talk to the
友好的。我们可以过去和他们谈谈吗？
lion? Yeah, Michael, we can. So, again,
狮子？是的，迈克尔，我们可以。所以，再说一遍，
in her head, we walk over. So, I say to
在她脑海里，我们走了过去。所以，我说
her, "Uh, does the lion have a name?"
她问：“呃，这只狮子有名字吗？”
And she said, "I don't know. Let me
她说：“我不知道。让我……”
ask." So, she asked the lion his name.
“问。”于是，她问狮子叫什么名字。
And she said, "Yeah, his name is Jack."
她说：“是的，他的名字叫杰克。”
And I said, "What does Jack mean to
我说：“杰克对……意味着什么？”
you?" And instantly she says, "Jack was
你？”她立刻回答说：“杰克是
my uncle and he saved me from getting
我叔叔救了我，让我免于……
raped by my stepfather."
我被继父强奸了。
Now, we're getting somewhere. Now, we
现在，我们终于取得进展了。现在，我们
understand what's chasing her. Now, we
弄清楚是什么在追赶她。现在，我们
understand where she's headed to. She's
了解她要去哪里。她是
trying to head to the person that saved
试图找到救命恩人
her. Now she starts to understand where
她。现在她开始明白这是哪里了。
this dream is coming from. And guess
这个梦源自何处？猜猜看
what? In three or four more sessions,
什么？再过三四次疗程​​，
she doesn't have the dream anymore
她不再有那个梦想了。
&gt;&gt; because you did what?
因为你做了什么？
&gt;&gt; Because she now understands where it is.
因为她现在知道它在哪里了。
She's no longer scared in the middle of
她不再害怕了
her dream. She's able to understand it,
她的梦想。她能理解。
wake up, and move forward.
醒醒吧，继续前进。
&gt;&gt; It's remarkable.
真是不可思议。
It's kind of the coolest thing ever. If
这简直太酷了。如果
you want to know the truth of the
你想知道真相
matter, working with people's dreams is
与人们的梦想打交道是件很重要的事。
just ma amazing stuff. And for people at
真是太棒了。对于那些……的人来说
home that might not have access to you,
可能无法联系到你的家
&gt;&gt; um is is a is there a simple thing that
嗯，是的，有没有什么简单的办法？
they can do to start to sort of get a
他们可以做些什么来开始获得某种程度的……
hold of these dreams?
你是否还能抓住这些梦想？
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Number one is you
是的。是的。是的。第一名就是你
could actually start a dream journal.
或许可以开始写梦境日记。
&gt;&gt; So it's just a journal. Um and there's a
所以它只是一本日记。嗯，还有
couple things that you would write down
有几件事你想写下来
in a given dream journal. So you might
在给定的梦境日记中。所以你可能会
write down um what was the theme, right?
把主题写下来，对吧？
So was it was like describe it like was
所以，就像描述它那样，是吗？
it dark out? Was it light out? Uh was it
天黑了吗？当时天亮了吗？呃，是吗？
scary? Was it happy? You might describe
可怕的？它快乐吗？你可以描述
the surroundings of it and you might
周围环境，你可能会
describe the people that are in it as
将其中的人物描述为
well. um and start listing these things
出色地。嗯，然后开始列出这些东西。
and getting as detailed as you possibly
尽可能详细地描述
can. Once you've kind of gotten through
能。一旦你大致度过了
the point of getting the details down of
记录细节的意义在于
your dream, then if you want to change
如果你梦想着改变，那就改变你的梦想吧。
them, you can change the ending. It's
你可以改变它们的结局。它是
not hard. You just change it the way you
不难。你只需改变它的方式即可
want it to be. Then you start to read it
希望如此。然后你开始读它
over for yourself. Now, I want to be
一切都由你自己决定。现在，我想成为
clear, in terrible nightmare situations,
清晰，在可怕的噩梦情境中，
this can be a little bit difficult. And
这可能有点困难。和
so, you're probably going to want to
所以，你可能想要
talk with your therapist about it and
和你的治疗师谈谈这件事。
maybe work with the therapist while
或许可以和治疗师一起工作
doing something like this. But it is
做类似的事情。但它是
absolutely possible to collect
完全可以收集
information from in a dream journal u
梦境日记中的信息
and be able to do some interesting stuff
并且能够做一些有趣的事情
with it. I would not recommend taking
和它一起。我不建议服用
your dream and stuffing it into chat GPT
把你的梦想塞进聊天 GPT
and asking chat GPT what it means. Um
然后询问聊天 GPT 这是什么意思。嗯
lots and lots of people are doing that
很多人都在这样做。
these days. And here's why that's
这些日子。原因如下：
probably not the best idea. So number
这可能不是个好主意。所以数字
one, unless chat GPT really knows and
除非聊天 GPT 真的知道，而且
understands you there, it's going to
它理解你，它会
give some very broadbased sort of
提供一些非常广泛的
encyclopedia. you know, here's a symbol
百科全书。你知道，这是一个符号
that means this type of thing, which
这意味着这类事情，即
once again, we have very little evidence
我们再次发现，我们几乎没有任何证据。
that that actually works. So, I would
这确实有效。所以，我会
argue that you're better off talking
辩称你最好还是多说话。
about your dreams with people who know
和了解你的人谈论你的梦想
you. Um, because they can actually help
你。嗯，因为它们确实能提供帮助。
you understand a little bit more about
你对以下内容有了更多了解
what's going on.
这是怎么回事。
&gt;&gt; There's a few other items on the table
桌子上还有其他一些物品。
here. Um, I mean, this is I don't use
这里。嗯，我的意思是，这个我不使用。
this exact one, but maybe I should, but
就是这个，不过也许我应该，但是……
this has been an absolute game changer
这彻底改变了游戏规则。
for me when I travel, when I'm on
对我来说，当我旅行时，当我在
planes.
飞机。
&gt;&gt; I love a good sleep mask. My wife says
我喜欢睡眠眼罩。我妻子说
it looks like I'm living in the 50s.
感觉我好像生活在上世纪50年代。
you know, when I'm wearing it. But I
你知道，当我戴着它的时候。但我
love a good sleep mask. That one in
我喜欢一款好用的睡眠眼罩。那个
particular is pretty cool because you
特别之处在于，你
can remove the eye cups and you can
可以取下眼罩，然后你可以
change the sizing of where you want it.
更改您想要放置的位置的大小。
And then these can actually you can
然后这些实际上你可以
replace these with things that heat or
用能加热或
cool.
凉爽的。
&gt;&gt; Um, but I love that that particular eye
嗯，但我很喜欢那双眼睛。
mask. It works. Yeah, it's really works
面具。有用。是的，它确实有效。
quite well. It's very dark in there. You
很好。里面很黑。你
definitely can't see up there.
绝对看不到上面。
&gt;&gt; Crazy,
疯狂的，
&gt;&gt; right?
正确的？
&gt;&gt; And then I've got one more thing that I
然后我还有一件事……
think people will find interesting. I
我觉得大家会觉得有趣。我
can't explain how how much of a game
无法解释这究竟是一场怎样的游戏
changer it has been to cover my eyes
它一直遮住我的眼睛
when I go to sleep because gosh the
当我睡觉的时候，因为天哪
amount of nights per week where I don't
每周有多少个晚上我不在家
know there's like a crack in the in the
我知道就像裂缝一样……
curtains or I don't know someone gets up
窗帘拉开，或者我不知道，有人起床了
early and
早期和
&gt;&gt; well also for you you're traveling all
对你来说也是，你一直在旅行
the time you're in different you're in
你所处的时间与你所处的时间不同。
planes you're in different environments
飞机上你会处于不同的环境中
also by the way every time you're in a
顺便说一句，每次你身处一个
different environment you have something
在不同的环境中，你会有一些东西。
called the first night effect so we see
被称为首夜效应，所以我们可以看到
this with every human on earth when you
当你这样做的时候，地球上的每个人都会这样。
sleep in a new place for the first night
第一晚睡在新地方
you never sleep well because it's new
你睡不好觉，因为一切都是新的。
sounds new sights you know, new smells,
听起来像是看到了新的景象，闻到了新的气味。
all that stuff is new. So, what's nice
这些都是新的东西。那么，什么好呢？
about having this is when I put one of
关于拥有这件事，就是当我放其中一个的时候
these on, I don't have to worry about
穿上这些，我就不用担心了。
light. I don't have to worry about
光。我不用担心
anything.
任何事物。
&gt;&gt; Does CO2 play a role?
二氧化碳是否发挥了作用？
&gt;&gt; In what way?
以什么方式？
&gt;&gt; In changing sleep. I was thinking if
改变睡眠。我在想如果
ventilation, the amount of oxygen in the
通风量，即氧气含量
room matters at all because sometimes I
房间大小并不重要，因为有时候我
go to hotels and they don't have windows
我去住酒店，结果发现它们都没有窗户。
you can open.
你可以打开。
&gt;&gt; Right. So, air quality is also a
正确的。所以，空气质量也是一个……
important thing, not just air quantity,
重要的不仅仅是空气量，
right? And so number number one thing if
正确的？所以，第一点是……
I was to tell people, hey, here's an
我要告诉人们，嘿，这里有一个
easy thing to do to to make your sleep
做个简单的办法就能让你睡个好觉
better, just go out and buy an air
最好还是直接出去买个空气清新剂。
purifier for your bedroom. Think about
卧室专用净化器。想想
it. It's the room you spend more time in
它。这是你待得最久的房间。
than any other room in the house. You
比房子里的任何其他房间都更宽敞。你
want that air to be fresh and filtered,
希望空气清新且经过过滤。
right? And not a big, it's not
正确的？而且不大，不是的
expensive. 20 25 bucks. One sits in the
昂贵的。 20到25美元。一个人坐在
corner, just runs the air, cycles all
角落里，空气流动，循环一切
day long. That way you know you have
一整天。这样你就知道你拥有
good clean fresh air. Um, also I tell
空气清新洁净。嗯，还有，我告诉
people open the windows once a week. Um,
人们每周开窗一次。嗯，
it's good to get fresh air in. Now, the
呼吸新鲜空气是件好事。现在，
only problem comes is if you have
唯一的问题是，如果你有
allergies and the allergens fly in and
过敏症和过敏原会飞进来，
there's pollen or dust or things like
里面可能有花粉、灰尘或其他类似的东西。
that, that can be somewhat problematic.
这可能会有些问题。
But generally speaking, if you don't
但总的来说，如果你不
have enough oxygen going on, you're
只要氧气充足，你就会……
definitely not going to sleep well and
肯定睡不好了。
your body's going to wake up. So, if you
你的身体即将苏醒。所以，如果你
were in, let's say, a oxygen restrictive
比如说，我们处于一种氧气受限的状态
environment, so let's say that you were
环境，所以假设你是
underneath the covers,
被子底下，
&gt;&gt; right? And you've got the thing all all
正确的？你已经把所有东西都搞定了。
the way over your head, you're not going
远远超出你的能力范围，你不会去的。
to sleep particularly well and
睡得特别好
eventually you're going to get so feel
最终你会明白的。
so restricted that you're going to open
限制如此之多，以至于你即将开放
up the covers. I want to understand the
掀开被子。我想了解……
best possible sleep position. I do have
最佳睡眠姿势。我确实有
a bed um in the room next door that we
隔壁房间有一张床，嗯，我们
can go to and talk about these pillows.
可以去那里谈谈这些枕头。
But before we do that,
但在此之前，
&gt;&gt; sure.
当然。
&gt;&gt; I would like to talk about
我想谈谈……
&gt;&gt; relationships, arguing with your
人际关系，与你争吵
partner, sex, all those kinds of things.
伴侣、性，诸如此类的事情。
What do I need to know
我需要了解什么
&gt;&gt; to protect my sleep, but also to protect
为了保护我的睡眠，也为了保护
my relationship? If we start with
我的关系？如果我们从……开始
talking about I know you wrote about it
说到我，我知道你写过关于它的文章。
in your book, um the power of when you
在你的书中，嗯，当你……时的力量
talked about I think it's on page 10
我记得好像是在第10页。
&gt;&gt; 101. You talk about arguing with your
101. 你谈到和你的人争论
partner before bed.
睡前与伴侣共度时光。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
Possibly the worst thing you can
这可能是你能做的最糟糕的事
possibly do is argue with your partner
可能会做的就是和你的伴侣争吵
before bed. Um because it's increasing
睡前。嗯，因为它正在增加
heart rate, right? What I tell all my
是心率吧？我告诉所有我
patients to do is if you if you need to
患者需要做的就是，如果你需要的话。
have an important discussion with your
和你的家人进行一次重要的谈话
spouse or your partner, do it right
配偶或伴侣，一定要做好。
after dinner, right? So like in that
晚饭后，对吧？就像那样
7:00 range, 7 to 8:00 range. So that way
7点钟方向，7点到8点钟方向。所以那样做
you have enough space and time to be
你有足够的空间和时间成为
able to discuss something and not
能够讨论某事而不是
hopefully go to bed angry if you can
如果可以的话，希望你能带着怒气入睡。
avoid it at all possible. It happens.
尽可能避免这种情况。这种事时有发生。
Look, I can't say that I've never gone
你看，我不能说我从没去过。
to bed angry. I'm sure you can't say
带着怒气入睡。我确信你不能这么说
that either. Sometimes things are a
也有可能。有时候事情就是这样
bigger deal. But if you can find better
更重要的事。但如果你能找到更好的
times to schedule those things, they
安排这些事情的时间，他们
work out a lot better. For me, the other
效果好得多。对我来说，另一个
thing that I oftentimes ask a lot of my
我经常问我的很多问题
patients to do is, for example, if
例如，如果患者需要做什么，
there's known issues that are going on,
目前存在一些已知问题，
like let's say somebody's going through
比如说，有人正在经历
marital therapy or there's there's an
婚姻治疗，或者还有……
issue that they're trying to work on,
他们正在努力解决的问题
then maybe that's better off done at
那么或许最好在……进行。
11:00 in the daytime versus starting to
白天11:00与开始
kind of address some of those issues in
在某种程度上解决其中的一些问题
the evening time. I like evening times
傍晚时分。我喜欢夜晚。
to be as stressfree as humanly possible.
尽可能让自己放松，远离压力。
Now, if you got something you got to
现在，如果你得到了某样东西，你就必须……
talk about, you got to talk about it.
谈谈这件事，你必须谈谈这件事。
But generally speaking, I would say the
但总的来说，我会说
le the less emotionality that you have
你的情绪越少，你的情绪就越容易波动。
in towards the evening, the better.
傍晚时分越好。
Unless it's joy or happiness.
除非是喜悦或幸福。
&gt;&gt; So many couples, they have these
很多夫妇都有这些
difficult conversations on the pillow.
枕边细语。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Including me sometimes.
有时候也包括我。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, and it makes sense like when
是的。嗯，这很有道理，就像……
else do you see that person, right? You
不然你还能见到那个人吗？你
haven't seen them all day. You're you're
今天一整天都没见到他们。你是 你是
literally face to face like, "Hey, I got
真的面对面，就像，“嘿，我……”
something I got to talk to you about.
有件事我得跟你说说。
This is kind of the best time to do it."
现在可以说是做这件事的最佳时机。
&gt;&gt; It ruins your sex life as well, doesn't
它也会毁了你的性生活，不是吗？
it? absolutely ruins your sex life
它？彻底毁了你的性生活
unless you have makeup sex afterwards
除非你们事后有和好性爱。
and then it's great but at the end of
然后一切都很棒，但到了最后……
the day it's not a lot of fun to have
那天没什么乐趣可言。
those conversations at night. That's
那些夜里的谈话。那是
again why I choose to if I'm going to
再次说明我为什么选择这样做。
have that conversation the best time
找个最佳时机进行那次谈话。
honestly to do it is right after
说实话，这样做是对的。
breakfast.
早餐。
&gt;&gt; In my relationship we've banned uh
在我的恋爱关系中，我们已经禁止了呃
difficult conversations at night time.
夜间的艰难对话。
&gt;&gt; Good. That's probably a smart move.
好的。这或许是个明智之举。
Dude,
老兄，
&gt;&gt; you're tired and it's going to destroy
你累了，这会毁了你。
your sleep,
你的睡眠，
&gt;&gt; right?
正确的？
&gt;&gt; You you can't think straight. You're
你无法正常思考。你是
probably more emotional
可能更情绪化
&gt;&gt; and you haven't put all the pieces
你还没有把所有碎片都拼好。
together yet of the issues that are
虽然这些问题都存在，但它们仍然值得关注。
really going on. I can assure you if you
真的发生了。我可以向你保证，如果你
sleep and then have your discussion in
睡一觉，然后再进行讨论。
the morning, you'll actually think about
早上，你真的会思考……
the issue better.
这个问题得到了更好的解决。
&gt;&gt; It's so crazy. As I've gotten older,
真是太疯狂了。随着年龄的增长，
I've realized how much of my mood is
我意识到我的情绪有多大程度上取决于
determined by my sleep. Like, it's so
由我的睡眠决定。简直太……
And I think it's got worse with age.
而且我觉得随着年龄增长情况越来越糟了。
&gt;&gt; Oh, absolutely it does.
哦，当然是这样。
&gt;&gt; Because at 25 you could blow [__] off.
因为25岁的时候你可以把一切都抛在脑后。
Oh, yeah. Or you could drink a monster
哦，是的。或者你可以喝一瓶怪兽能量饮料
or a
或
mood. Yeah. Sleep matters. And I think
情绪。是的。睡眠很重要。我觉得
that's what you're that's that's the
这就是你，这就是，这就是
button that you're pushing here. And I
你正在按的这个按钮。我
think it's important for your audience
我认为这对你的受众很重要
to hear that, right? is look, you're 33
听到这话肯定很震惊，对吧？你看，你都33岁了。
years old and you're already seeing
才几岁，你就已经看到了
things changing in your sleep that have
睡眠中发生的变化
a big effect in your life. I'm 58 years
对你的生活产生重大影响。我今年58岁
old, okay? I see the same thing
老了，好吗？我看到了同样的情况。
happening. Everybody, sleep is so
正在发生。各位，睡眠是如此重要
fundamental to the human condition that
对人类生存状况至关重要的是
it's one of those things that we've got
这是我们拥有的那种东西之一。
to really pay attention to. And the
务必注意。以及
thing is, most people don't pay
问题是，大多数人都不付钱。
attention to it because they're like,
引起重视，因为他们就像是：
"Well, my body does it automatically,
“嗯，我的身体会自动完成。”
Michael. Like, how tough could this be?"
迈克尔。这能有多难呢？
I walk into that room in the back of the
我走进后面的那个房间……
house, I turn off the lights, h go to
房子里，我关了灯，然后去了
bed, then I wake up, something magical
我躺在床上，然后醒来，感觉很奇妙。
happens, and I should be great, right?
事情发生了，我应该没问题，对吧？
doesn't always work that way.
并非总是如此。
&gt;&gt; I was reading in your work about the
我在读你的作品时，读到了关于……的内容。
best time to fall in love.
坠入爱河的最佳时机。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
&gt;&gt; That's a strange thing for a
对于一个……来说，这很奇怪。
&gt;&gt; somebody of your profession to be
你的同行会是……
thinking much about was in this book,
这本书里有很多值得思考的内容。
was it?
是吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it was.
是的，确实如此。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; When you think about it, everything is
仔细想想，一切都是
based on timing, right? So, the timing
根据时机来判断，对吧？所以，时机很重要。
when your hormones at a certain point
当你的荷尔蒙处于某个特定阶段时
and you meet that person and their
然后你遇到了那个人，以及他们的
hormones at a certain point and then all
激素在某个阶段会发生变化，然后一切都会改变。
of the sudden there's a connection,
突然之间，他们之间建立了一种联系。
&gt;&gt; right? That's hard to do when you're
正确的？当你……的时候，这很难做到。
exhausted, right? Try going on a first
累坏了吧？试着去体验一下第一次
date when you're completely like when
当你完全像那样的时候约会
it's the worst, right? You know, you're
真是最糟糕的，对吧？你知道，你是
not giving a good impression of
给人留下不好的印象
yourself. You know that you're not
你自己。你知道你不是
getting a good impression of that person
给那个人留下好印象
because your mind is not going where it
因为你的思绪没有飘到那里
needs to be. So, there's timing involved
必须如此。所以，时机很重要。
and understanding your chronoype and
了解你的计时器和
that person's chronoype really leads you
那个人的年代学真的会误导你
in that positive direction. And I would
朝着积极的方向发展。而我会
argue that it's pretty easy to fall in
认为很容易陷入这种境地
love at that time.
那时的爱情。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, in your book,
好的。所以，在你的书中，
&gt;&gt; um, Power of When,
嗯，《何时》的力量，
&gt;&gt; yes.
是的。
&gt;&gt; On page 9, uh,4, you say, "Dolphin's
在第9页，呃，4，你说，“海豚的
best mood is in the afternoon to
下午心情最好。
evening." So, the best time for them to
晚上。”所以，对他们来说，最好的时间是
fall in love is 8:00 p.m. Lions
坠入爱河的时间是晚上8点。狮子
&gt;&gt; 700 a.m.,
上午7点，
&gt;&gt; right? Cuz remember, they're early
正确的？因为记住，他们来得早。
morning people. They're exhausted at the
早起的人。他们筋疲力尽。
end.
结尾。
&gt;&gt; Damn. So, they should be going on
该死。所以他们应该继续前进。
morning dates.
早晨约会。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Bears,
熊，
&gt;&gt; 400 p.m. And the wolf, like me, 11:00
下午 4 点而那匹狼，和我一样，11:00
p.m. That tracks.
下午符合逻辑。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I get it. So, should I be doing
是的，我明白了。所以，我应该怎么做？
my, you know, okay, I'm in a
我的，你知道，好吧，我在一个
relationship. I'm about to be married.
关系。我即将结婚。
But, um, I should
但是，嗯，我应该
&gt;&gt; you got engaged. Congratulations.
你订婚了。恭喜。
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
&gt;&gt; Yeah,
是的，
&gt;&gt; but I should be doing my dates later. It
但我应该晚点再约会。它
kind of tracks. That's kind of when I
某种类型的曲目。大概就是那时候……
did them.
他们做到了。
&gt;&gt; Well, look at your whole schedule, dude.
哥们儿，看看你整个日程安排吧。
You don't do a thing before 11.
11点之前你什么都不用做。
&gt;&gt; That's true.
这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Right. I think you're exactly like I am.
正确的。我觉得你跟我一模一样。
&gt;&gt; Shall we go and look at the best
我们去看看最好的吧。
possible sleep position?
可能的睡姿？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, let's check it out. And we talk
好，我们去看看。我们交谈
about pillows, too.
关于枕头也是一样。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, I'll bring all the pillows
好的。所以，我会把所有的枕头都带来。
with me.
与我一起。
&gt;&gt; Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Okay. So, we're going to go into
好的。好的。所以，我们接下来要进入……
the next room where there's a bed and
隔壁房间有一张床，
you're going to tell me what can you
你要告诉我你能做什么
tell me when we look at the bed. How can
告诉我我们什么时候去看床。如何才能
you help?
你能帮忙吗？
&gt;&gt; So, there's a couple of different
所以，有好几种不同的
things. So, number one, I'm going to
事物。所以，第一点，我要……
look at your starting sleep position and
看看你开始时的睡姿
I'm going to give you some feedback
我会给你一些反馈
about that. Then, we're going to fit you
关于那件事。然后，我们会为你量身定制。
for the right kind of pillow for you.
选择适合你的枕头。
And then there's some cool technology in
然后还有一些很酷的技术
there that I want to show you as well
我也想给你们看看。
that can help keep you cool all night
这可以帮助你整晚保持凉爽。
long.
长的。
&gt;&gt; And do we need to take this with us?
我们需要把这个带走吗？
&gt;&gt; Yes, take that one. And then, how many
对，就选这个。然后，有多少个？
pillows are there?
有枕头吗？
&gt;&gt; I think there's five.
我认为有五个。
&gt;&gt; There's five different pillows. Okay,
共有五种不同的枕头。好的，
great. Let's
伟大的。我们开始吧
&gt;&gt; They all do different things.
他们各自从事不同的工作。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Okay, so we're now downstairs in a
好的。好的，我们现在在楼下。
bedroom we have in the house. I have
我们在房子里的卧室。我有
lots of pillows here, quite a few.
这里有很多枕头，相当多。
&gt;&gt; And there's a bunch of questions I have
我还有很多问题。
for you. The first is
为你。第一个是
&gt;&gt; pillows. Do they matter? Is there a
枕头。它们重要吗？是否有
perfect one? Is it different for every
完美吗？每个情况都不一样吗？
individual
个人
&gt;&gt; sleeping position? Is there a perfect
睡姿？是否存在完美？
sleeping position? There is.
睡姿？有。
&gt;&gt; And the third one is about temperature.
第三个问题与温度有关。
&gt;&gt; You got it. Let's go.
答对了。我们走吧。
&gt;&gt; So I just grab whatever pillow is in the
所以我随便抓了个枕头就用。
bed wherever I travel.
无论去哪里，我都能睡在床上。
&gt;&gt; Terrible idea.
真是个糟糕的主意。
&gt;&gt; Really
真的
&gt;&gt; terrible idea. So, first of all, a lot
糟糕的主意。首先，很多
of people need to understand that a
人们需要明白，
pillow is a bed for your head, right?
枕头是用来放头的，对吧？
And so, the goal here is to keep your
因此，这里的目标是保持你的
nose in line with your sternum, which is
鼻子与胸骨成一条直线，也就是
sort of the center part of your chest,
胸部中间那部分，
right? And but you don't want it facing
正确的？但是你不想让它朝向
down and you don't want it facing up.
朝下，不要朝上。
You want it to be completely in the
你希望它完全融入其中
center like that. And so, if you have a
像那样居中。所以，如果你有一个
pillow that tilts your head to the one
能将你的头向一侧倾斜的枕头
way or tilts your head to the other, it
把头歪向一边，或者把头转向另一边，它
causes a pain signal from the strain of
拉伤会引起疼痛信号
the musculature that goes to your brain.
通往大脑的肌肉组织。
You don't get into deep sleep. So, you
你无法进​​入深度睡眠。所以，你
really want to make sure that you've got
真的想确保你已经拥有
a good pillow. Otherwise, you end up
一个好枕头。否则，你最终会
with a crick in your neck. You don't get
脖子酸痛。你得不到
good deep sleep. It becomes problematic.
良好的深度睡眠。这就成了问题。
&gt;&gt; Okay. All
好的。全部
&gt;&gt; right. So, the big question is how do
正确的。所以，最大的问题是如何……
you pick a pillow? Right. So, first
你选枕头吗？正确的。首先，
question you want to ask yourself is
你想问自己的问题是：
squishy or firm? Right. So, let's take a
软软的还是硬的？正确的。那么，让我们来看一个……
look at our tower of pillows here.
看看我们这儿的枕头塔。
&gt;&gt; So, for you, let's let's take a look.
那么，我们一起来看看吧。
So, this is a pretty firm one. This is a
所以，这算是板上钉钉的事了。这是
basically a foam based hunk of foam
基本上就是一块泡沫状的泡沫
pillow, right? Versus this one, which is
枕头，对吧？相比之下，这个是
sort of the normal kind of pillow, much
就是那种普通的枕头，很多
more squishy. So, which are you? A
更软糯。那么，你是哪一种呢？一个
squishy or a firm?
软软的还是硬的？
&gt;&gt; That one.
那个。
&gt;&gt; Okay, perfect. So, you're more on the
好的，完美。所以，你更倾向于……
squishy, which means you like to
软绵绵的，这意味着你喜欢
manipulate the pillow. You don't want it
调整枕头的位置。你不想要它
to have a huge form factor where your
拥有巨大的外形尺寸，你的
like head is on a block of cheese,
就像脑袋放在一块奶酪上一样，
right? Got it. So, perfect. So, let's
正确的？知道了。太好了。那么，我们开始吧
move this foam pillow out of the way.
把这个泡沫枕头移开。
&gt;&gt; The second thing you want to look at
你要看的第二件事
from the pillow is when the fabric comes
枕头上的布料就是从枕头里出来的。
together here, it forms what's called a
在这里，它们共同构成了所谓的
knife's edge. So, it's where the two
刀刃般锋利。所以，这就是这两个地方。
pieces of fabric meet. Now, why is that
布料拼接在一起。那么，这是为什么呢？
important? Because when you have your
重要的？因为当你拥有你的
head on a pillow like this and the
头枕在这样的枕头上，
knife's edge is down here, you're not
刀刃就在这里，你不在。
getting as much support underneath your
获得尽可能多的支撑
neck here, right? So, in order to fix
这里是脖子，对吧？所以，为了解决这个问题
that, we have something called a gusset.
那，我们有一种叫做角撑板的东西。
So, a gusset is this piece of fabric
所以，衬布就是这块布料。
that comes along here. So, you notice
这里也出现了这种情况。所以，你注意到
these two pieces of fabric don't meet.
这两块布料并不吻合。
There's a thickness here. So, when you
这里有点厚度。所以，当你
were to sleep on it, it actually catches
如果仔细想想，它实际上会吸引人。
you all the way down. So, let's say you
你一路向下。假设你
would be like this, you it gives you
就像这样，它会给你
support all the way down. Now, you don't
一路支撑到底。现在，你不需要了。
like the foam of it all, but you do like
就像这一切的泡沫一样，但你确实喜欢
the the gusset, right?
是侧缝，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Here's one that's got the gusset without
这里有一款没有侧缝的款式。
the foam. So, it's squishy and has the
泡沫。所以，它软软的，而且有……
gusset. So, if you were going to use
侧缝。所以，如果你打算使用
this,
这，
&gt;&gt; that's good.
那挺好的。
&gt;&gt; So, now we've been able to fit you for
所以，现在我们已经能够为您量身定制了
the pillow. Now, the next question we
枕头。现在，下一个问题是……
have, uh, well, the last one is there
嗯，最后一个在那里。
are some special types of pillows.
有一些特殊类型的枕头。
Actually, this one has got a cutout. So,
实际上，这个是有镂空设计的。所以，
you notice how that's got like a moon
你注意到它像个月亮吗？
here. It fits perfectly here. here. And
这里。它放在这里正合适。这里。和
notice, right, this is this is my
注意，对了，这是我的
personal pillow.
个人枕头。
&gt;&gt; Oh, okay. I can So,
哦好的。我可以。所以，
&gt;&gt; you have to shift.
你必须改变策略。
&gt;&gt; I know. Sorry. Um, and so you can see it
我知道。对不起。嗯，所以你可以看到
really comes all the way down to your
归根结底，这完全取决于你
neck and it gives you support all the
它能支撑颈部，并提供全方位的支撑。
way from the base of your neck all the
从你的脖子底部一直到……
way up through. And that's one of the
一路向上。这是其中之一
reasons that I like it cuz I can cut it
我喜欢它的原因在于我可以把它切开。
out and put it right there on me.
拿出来，直接放在我身上。
&gt;&gt; For the average person, if if they had
对于普通人来说，如果他们有
to pick one pillow without you knowing
在你不知情的情况下挑选一个枕头
anything about them, which pillow would
关于它们的一切，哪个枕头会更好？
you pick of these six?
你从这六个中选一个？
&gt;&gt; So, of all of these six, well, if I had
所以，在这六个人中，嗯，如果我有
my choice, I'd pick this one because
如果让我选，我会选这个，因为
this is my favorite. By the way, there's
这是我最喜欢的。顺便说一下，还有
also another feature of this that I
此外，它还有另一个特点，那就是……
think is important to that people should
认为这一点对人们来说很重要
notice is it's got a zipper, which means
注意它有拉链，这意味着
I can change the stuffing and I can pull
我可以更换填充物，也可以拉动
it out or put it in. So, I can change
把它拿出来或放进去。所以，我可以改变
the height of my pillow.
我的枕头高度。
&gt;&gt; And what stuffing is that?
那是什么馅料？
&gt;&gt; This is actually a shredded latex.
这其实是碎乳胶。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; Which I really like to sleep on.
我很喜欢睡在上面。
&gt;&gt; So, what's this pillow called?
那么，这个枕头叫什么名字？
&gt;&gt; So, this is by a company called Coupe.
这是由一家名为 Coupe 的公司推出的。
Um, and um I like it because of the
嗯，我喜欢它是因为……
change in the in the shape as well as
形状的变化以及
the stuffing and the zipper on the side.
填充物和侧面的拉链。
It really makes it kind of what I would
这真的让我感觉有点像我理想中的样子。
argue to be probably the best pillow
可以说是最好的枕头
out.
出去。
&gt;&gt; And what's the worst pillow?
最糟糕的枕头是什么？
&gt;&gt; The worst pillow that we've got here,
这是我们这里最差的枕头。
this one. So, almost no support, right?
这个。所以几乎没有支持，对吧？
It's super squishy,
它超级软，
&gt;&gt; right? We don't we don't we have the
正确的？我们没有，我们没有，我们有
knife's edge here. There's not much to
这里如履薄冰。没什么可说的
it. Also, by the way, it feels like this
它。另外，顺便说一句，感觉就像这样
is made with polyester, which is a heat
它由聚酯纤维制成，聚酯纤维是一种耐热材料。
trapper. Now, let's lie you down on the
捕兽人。现在，我们让你躺下。
bed, get you in your starting sleep
上床，让你开始入睡
position, and I'm going to show you
位置，我这就给你展示。
exactly where the pillow should go and
枕头应该放在哪里就放在哪里。
what pillow should be for you. So, if
什么样的枕头最适合你？所以，如果
you can lie down for me. Now, what is
你可以躺下。那么，什么是
your starting sleep position? Are you a
你睡觉时的起始姿势是什么？你是
back sleeper? You a side sleeper? You a
仰卧？你是侧睡吗？你
stomach sleeper?
俯卧睡觉？
&gt;&gt; I start on my stomach and I roll to my
我先趴着，然后翻身到……
right.
正确的。
&gt;&gt; Got it. Okay, perfect. Go ahead and get
知道了。好的，完美。继续往下拿
on your stomach for
趴着
&gt;&gt; By the way, how weird is that?
话说回来，这难道不奇怪吗？
&gt;&gt; Roughly 75% of sleepers are side
大约75%的睡眠者是侧卧睡姿。
sleepers, either right or left. So,
睡觉的人，无论是向左还是向右。所以，
you're definitely not don't fall into
你绝对不是，不要陷入
that category. Another 20 or so percent
该类别。还有大约20%
are back sleepers. You're in the like 5%
他们是仰卧睡姿。你属于那5%左右。
category of stomach sleepers. The reason
俯卧睡眠者类别。原因
it's the worst position is when you're
最糟糕的情况就是当你……
lying on your stomach, right, and the
你趴着，对吧？
pillow is here. You're pushing on your
枕头在这里。你正在努力推进你的
back here and it causes what's called a
回到这里，它会导致所谓的
spllay, which is extra pressure on your
飞溅，这会给你带来额外的压力
lower back. And that can give you low
下背部。而这可能会让你感到沮丧
back pain over time.
长期背痛。
&gt;&gt; I only do it for the first like 10
我只在前十个左右这样做。
minutes
分钟
&gt;&gt; and then you rotate.
然后你旋转。
&gt;&gt; And then I rotate onto my side.
然后我翻身侧躺。
&gt;&gt; Which side? Right or left?
哪一边？向左还是向右？
&gt;&gt; My right. This side.
我的没错。这边。
&gt;&gt; Perfect. So in all actuality, you
完美的。所以实际上，你
actually want to be on your left side
实际上你想待在你的左侧
because when you lie on your right side,
因为当你侧卧在右侧时，
you're actually all of your organs push
实际上，你所有的器官都在推动。
down onto your stomach and it can leak
滴到肚子上，可能会漏出来
some of those gastric juices and you end
一些胃液，然后你就结束了
up with something called
想出了一个叫做
gastroosophageal reflux disease. So the
胃食管反流病。所以
way I teach people is right is wrong. So
我教别人的方式是把对当错。所以
you don't sleep on your right side, you
你睡觉时不侧卧，你
sleep on your left side if you can. If
如果可以的话，尽量左侧卧睡。如果
you can, but let's fit you anyway. Let's
你可以，但我们还是会帮你试穿。我们开始吧
go ahead and get you down on your what
来吧，把你的……
would be your right side and let's see
应该是你的右侧，我们来看看。
how you do. Lie down.
你好。躺。
&gt;&gt; How I normally lie down.
我通常的躺姿。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Okay. This is how I lie down when
好的。好的。我就是这样躺下的
I first get in bed for the first time. I
我第一次躺到床上。我
can't wait to see.
迫不及待想看。
&gt;&gt; I'm like this. I move the pillow out the
我就是这样。我把枕头移开。
way
方式
&gt;&gt; and I just learn lay like this for a
我刚刚学会了这样躺着。
while.
尽管。
&gt;&gt; Okay. And you have no pillow.
好的。而且你没有枕头。
&gt;&gt; No pillow.
没有枕头。
&gt;&gt; Perfect. And then when you rotate to get
完美的。然后当你旋转以获得
to your side.
在你身边。
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Show me that.
给我看看。
&gt;&gt; I sleep like this on my on my right
我睡觉时这样侧卧，我的右手边。
side.
边。
&gt;&gt; Like roughly like this.
大概就是这样。
&gt;&gt; So, what you'll notice is your shoulder
所以，你会注意到你的肩膀
is now up into this part here. So, it's
现在到了这一部分。所以，就是这样。
still being supported. Your head is
仍在提供支持。你的头是
fine. And what you'll notice is his head
美好的。你会注意到他的头
is in line with his sternum, right? His
与他的胸骨在一条直线上，对吗？他的
nose is in line there. It's not falling
鼻子在那里是直立的。它没有倒塌。
too far. It's not overextended.
太远了。它并没有过度扩张。
&gt;&gt; That's my sternum.
那是我的胸骨。
&gt;&gt; Your sternum is the direct center of
你的胸骨是正中心
your chest. It's the m like your breast
你的胸部。就像你的乳房一样
plate is what you would call it, right?
你会把它叫做盘子，对吧？
Right. Sort of in the center of So, you
正确的。有点像在中心，所以，你
want your nose to be in line with that,
希望你的鼻子与它成一条直线，
which it basically is. And when I look
事实的确如此。当我看着
at your head, your head is not tilted to
你的头部没有倾斜
one side or another. So, I know there's
要么是这一方，要么是另一方。所以，我知道有
no more neck strain. So, that would be
不再感到颈部酸痛。所以，那就是
the perfect pillow for you. But that
最适合你的枕头。但是……
happens to be my pillow. So, I'm not
碰巧是我的枕头。所以，我不是
going to give it to you, but I might get
我会把它给你，但我可能会收到
you one if you're nice to me.
如果你对我好，你就得一个。
&gt;&gt; Thank you. What about these other
谢谢。其他的呢？
pillow? So, the bad one was which one?
枕头？所以，到底是哪一个不好呢？
The bad one was this one. So now go
最糟糕的就是这个。现在走
ahead and put yourself on that one.
先下手为强，把自己放在那个位置上。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I'm going too far down.
是的，我下潜得太深了。
&gt;&gt; Right. And you're not even trying. Like
正确的。你甚至都没尝试。喜欢
you don't even have to push your head
你甚至不用推头
that far. And and you can see and your
到那个程度了。而且你可以看到你的
and look where do you put your arm? Your
你看看你把胳膊放在哪里？你的
arm's not supported. Like it's becomes
手臂没有支撑。就像它变成了
like people don't realize it but pillows
就像人们没有意识到的那样，枕头
matter. What I try to tell people is I
事情。我想告诉人们的是，
used to be a runner and when you're a
曾经是一名跑步运动员，当你是一名……
runner like equipment matters like your
跑步装备很重要，比如你的
shoes matter, your music matters, your
鞋子很重要，你的音乐很重要，你的
your dry fit wear matters. The same
你的速干服很重要。相同
holds true with sleep. If you don't have
睡眠也同样如此。如果你没有
good pillow, good mattress, good sheets,
好枕头、好床垫、好床单
you don't have the right equipment,
你没有合适的设备。
you're not going to get good sleep.
你肯定睡不好觉。
&gt;&gt; That is a terrible pillow.
那枕头太糟糕了。
&gt;&gt; I'm telling you,
我告诉你，
&gt;&gt; really, really bad pillow. Okay, so
非常非常糟糕的枕头。好的，所以
sleeping on my left side is the correct
左侧卧睡是正确的睡姿。
side
边
&gt;&gt; with a good pillow.
配个好枕头。
&gt;&gt; But now, let's talk about temperature.
但现在，我们来谈谈温度。
&gt;&gt; Y.
Y.
&gt;&gt; So, while you're lying here, you may
所以，当你躺在这里的时候，你可能会
have noticed that there's different
我注意到存在一些差异
temperature on either side of the bed.
床两侧的温度。
&gt;&gt; So, if you feel here
所以，如果你觉得这里
&gt;&gt; Oh, it's warm.
哦，好暖和。
&gt;&gt; It is.
这是。
That's correct. So when you're lying
没错。所以当你撒谎的时候
there, your body will naturally become
在那里，你的身体自然会变得
more warm. So remember how we were
更暖和些。所以，还记得我们以前的样子吗？
talking that sleep follows the core body
谈论睡眠与核心身体的关系
temperature cycle, right? And so as your
温度循环，对吧？所以，你的
core body temperature drops, you want
核心体温下降，你想要
your environment to drop with it because
你的环境也会随之下降，因为
if it doesn't and the environment is too
如果它不这样做，而环境又太……
hot, you can't fall asleep. So this is a
天气太热，睡不着觉。所以这是
product. It's called an Orion sleep
产品。它被称为猎户座睡眠
system, and it's a topper that's you're
系统，而且它是你的顶级配置
lying on top of. Has a thin tube that
躺在上面。它有一根细管，
goes through it. You can't feel the
经历它。你感觉不到
tube. should feel cool over there and
管子。那边应该会感觉凉爽一些。
warm over here.
这里很暖和。
&gt;&gt; It's cold here, it's warm here.
这里冷，这里暖。
&gt;&gt; Exactly. And we and you can rotate it
确切地。我们和你们都可以轮流使用它。
however you want. But what's so
随你喜欢。但究竟是什么呢？
fascinating about this is you can
这件事最吸引人的地方在于你可以
actually set it so that it follows your
实际上，请将其设置为跟随您的设置。
circadian rhythm and it actually can
昼夜节律，而且它实际上可以
help you stay asleep. The only thing
帮助你保持睡眠。唯一的事情
that you as a consumer can manipulate in
作为消费者，您可以操控这一点
your sleep. Like you can't write a
你的睡眠。就像你不能写一个
pharmaceutical right prescription. You
正确的处方用药。你
can't get a CPAT machine. But what you
买不到CPAT机器。但是你
can do is control the temperature. So
能做的就是控制温度。所以
you might say to yourself, when would I
你可能会问自己，我什么时候才能……
want to control the temperature for my
想控制我的温度
sleep? Well, if you were female and you
睡觉？嗯，如果你是女性，而且你
were 45 years old and you were going
当时我们都45岁了，你正准备离开。
through menopause, you really want to
更年期期间，你真的想要
control the temperature because hot
控制温度，因为太热
flashes might wake you up in the middle
闪光灯可能会在半夜把你吵醒。
of the night. Those types of things
夜幕降临。诸如此类的事情
become very, very important.
变得非常非常重要。
&gt;&gt; And how much does this cost?
这要多少钱？
&gt;&gt; So, this runs about a little over 2,000
所以，这大概要2000多美元。
US. Um, the nearest competitor is
我们。嗯，最接近的竞争对手是
significantly more expensive, almost a
价格明显更高，几乎是
third more expensive.
价格高出三分之一。
&gt;&gt; And are you affiliated with them in any
你是否与他们有任何关联？
way?
方式？
&gt;&gt; I am affiliated with these guys. I am
我和这些人有关系。我是
their chief sleep officer.
他们的首席睡眠官。
&gt;&gt; Oh, nice. Didn't know that was the job
哦，不错。我不知道那是份工作。
title.
标题。
&gt;&gt; I know. I didn't know. I made up the job
我知道。我不知道。我编造了这份工作
title myself. Thank you very much.
给自己起个名字。非常感谢。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Is there anything else I should
好的。还有其他需要注意的吗？
know about the broader room that is
了解更广泛的领域
pertinent?
相关吗？
&gt;&gt; So when I talk about broader room
所以，当我谈到更宽敞的空间时，
aspects, I think of the five senses. So
各个方面，我想到了五种感官。所以
sight, sound, touch, taste, and smell,
视觉、听觉、触觉、味觉和嗅觉
right? So sight is light, right? So
正确的？所以视觉就是光，对吗？所以
clearly you want the lights down as
显然你想把灯光调暗。
we're starting to get towards bed. Maybe
我们开始准备睡觉了。或许
having a dimmer switch or something like
装个调光开关之类的东西
that is a great thing to slowly start to
这是一件值得慢慢开始的好事情。
do that or kept the overhead lights and
这样做或者保留顶灯
just have the bedside table lamps about
床头柜上只要放几盏灯就行了。
30 minutes before bed. Again, setting
睡前30分钟。再次设置
the tone. The next one would be sound.
语气。下一个是声音。
So, it's always better to be quiet, but
所以，保持沉默总是更好的选择，但是
at the end of the day, sometimes you can
归根结底，有时候你可以
have that and sometimes you can't. It's
有时候可以，有时候不行。它是
really about the emotionality that you
真正关乎你的情感
attach to the sound itself. If you get
附着在声音本身上。如果你得到
annoyed by something, it's just going to
如果被某事惹恼了，那就只会……
get worse and worse. But if you can
情况越来越糟。但如果你能
think in your head, hey, this isn't so
心里想，嘿，事情并非如此。
annoying anymore, it becomes less
不再那么烦人了，就不那么烦人了。
problematic. But to be clear, certain
有问题。但需要明确的是，
volume sounds and certain decibel levels
音量和特定分贝级别
are going to wake you up. And so, you
他们会把你叫醒。所以，你
really, it's hard to sleep next to a big
真的，很难睡在大个子旁边。
highway, right? So, you want to have as
高速公路，对吧？所以，你想拥有……
much sound buffering as you possibly
尽可能多地使用声音缓冲
can. So, we did sight, we did sound.
能。所以，我们做了视觉测试，也做了听觉测试。
Let's do touch. Touch is temperature,
我们来做肢体接触吧。触感是温度。
right? We talked about that. You want
正确的？我们谈过这件事。你想
the bedroom to be cool. If you can get
卧室要凉爽。如果你能得到
the get the um air conditioning on, but
把空调打开，但是
let's say you've got the air
假设你已经有了空气
conditioning on, but it's super hot
正在开机，但是太热了
summer and you're not fortunate enough
夏天到了，而你却不够幸运。
to have an Orion sitting underneath your
让猎户座就摆在你下面
sheets. What do you do? Go out and buy a
床单。你做什么工作？出去买一个
plastic bottle of water, two of them.
两瓶塑料瓶装水。
Stick them in the freezer. Then put them
把它们放进冰箱冷冻室。然后把它们放进去
into socks and then put them on your
把袜子套在脚上，然后穿上你的
sides. Okay, so frozen water bottle
双方。好的，所以，冰冻水瓶
inside a pair of inside a sock that sits
一双袜子里面
on your side. It's like a mini air
站在你这边。它就像一个迷你空气
conditioner underneath the covers. It
在被窝里涂抹护发素。它
works like a charm. I use this when I
效果非常好。我使用这个的时候
travel because a lot of times, you know,
旅行是因为很多时候，你知道，
the room you can't necessarily change
房间你未必能改变
the thermostat or things like that and
恒温器之类的东西
it's a great way to be able to do that
这是实现这一目标的绝佳方法。
kind of stuff. Then the final one is
诸如此类的事情。最后一个是
smell. So, people always ask me, "Does
闻。所以，人们总是问我，“真的吗？”
aroma therapy really work?" Believe it
芳香疗法真的有效吗？相信我。
or not, there are at least two
或者，至少有两个
scientifically rigorous studies that
科学严谨的研究
show that aroma therapy can actually be
证明芳香疗法确实可以
helpful for you. But I want to be clear,
对你有帮助。但我想要明确一点，
candles are not the way to do aroma
蜡烛并不是营造香味的好方法。
therapy. Fire and sleep do not mix.
治疗。火和睡眠不能混为一谈。
Okay?
好的？
&gt;&gt; But a diffuser I'm fine with. Or a
但我可以用香薰机。或者
little sache or a pillow mist. All of
小香囊或枕头喷雾。全部
those can be quite helpful. And you just
这些都很有帮助。而你只是
put them, you spray it on your pillow,
把它们放进去，然后喷在枕头上。
or you have it right next to your
或者它就放在你旁边
pillow. And as you breathe in the aroma,
枕头。当你吸入这香气时，
two aromomas have been shown to be
已证实有两种香气
helpful for sleep. One is lavender.
有助于睡眠。其中一种是薰衣草。
Surprise, surprise. The other is called
真是意料之外。另一个叫做
elang elang. Um, that's one that's
elang elang。嗯，那是其中之一。
actually got some data on it. And I
实际上我掌握了一些相关数据。我
actually think I saw a study on vanilla.
我好像看过一篇关于香草的研究报告。
&gt;&gt; And should I be sleeping naked?
那我应该裸睡吗？
&gt;&gt; Such a good question. So, here's what
问得好。所以，情况是这样的：
I'll tell you is you thermorreulate
我告诉你，你热反应
better with less clothing on. So, less
穿得越少越好。所以，更少
barriers allow your body to do exactly
屏障使你的身体能够准确地完成以下动作：
what it should do. So, I would argue you
它应该做什么。所以我认为你
definitely could sleep naked. And I I
绝对可以裸睡。而我
think there's an argument for sleeping
我觉得有必要睡觉。
naked will allow you to sleep better and
裸体能让你睡得更好。
thermorreulate better. However, be
更好地进行热修复。然而，
careful because if you have animals in
小心，因为如果你养了动物的话
the bed and you're sleeping naked, what
你躺在床上，裸睡，这是什么情况？
looks like a chew toy to them might be
看起来像个磨牙玩具，对他们来说可能是
important for you.
对你来说很重要。
&gt;&gt; You're speaking from experience.
你这是以亲身经历来说的。
&gt;&gt; I'm just letting you know there's
我只是想告诉你，有……
problems out there. I'm not saying that
外面有很多问题。我不是那个意思。
I had one of those problems myself.
我自己也遇到过类似的问题。
&gt;&gt; Okay. I I think we've covered it, right?
好的。我想我们已经讨论过了，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Last one. Yeah.
最后一个。是的。
&gt;&gt; Socks.
袜子。
&gt;&gt; Oh, socks. Everybody wants to know,
哦，袜子。每个人都想知道，
should I wear socks to bed? So, here's
睡觉时应该穿袜子吗？所以，这就是……
what's interesting is you dissipate heat
有趣的是，你可以散发热量。
faster wearing uh with uh unsocked foot
穿得更快，呃，光脚穿
because there's no hair on the bottom of
因为屁股底部没有毛
your feet. You ever notice when you're
你的脚。你有没有注意到，当你
hot at night and you stick your foot out
夜里很热，你把脚伸出去
from under the covers, you instantly
从被窝里，你瞬间
cool down and everything's okay. So,
冷静下来，一切都会好起来的。所以，
what I do for some of my patients who
我为一些病人做的事情
have thermmorreulation issues, I have
我有热变形问题。
them start with socks but no clothes and
他们一开始只有袜子，没有衣服。
then they can remove their socks
然后他们就可以脱掉袜子了。
afterwards as they start to get too
之后，当他们开始变得太……
warm.
温暖的。
&gt;&gt; Okay, let's go back upstairs and finish
好了，我们回楼上继续吧。
this conversation.
这段对话。
important question to ask you.
这个问题很重要，我想问你。
&gt;&gt; So, I want to go back upstairs. Thank
所以，我想回楼上去。感谢
you so much for that. Super, super
非常感谢你。太棒了，太棒了
useful.
有用。
&gt;&gt; Sure.
当然。
&gt;&gt; Dr. Michael Bruce, we have a closing
迈克尔·布鲁斯博士，我们即将结束
tradition on this podcast where the last
这个播客的传统是……
guest leaves a question for the next
一位客人给下一位客人留下了一个问题。
guest, not knowing who they're leaving
客人，不知道他们要离开的是谁。
it for.
它是为了。
&gt;&gt; Oh, I didn't know this. This is awesome.
哦，我不知道这件事。太棒了。
&gt;&gt; And the question that's been left for
而留给大家的问题是……
you is, if you could have the power to
你，如果你拥有这种力量……
change one thing in the US healthare
改变美国医疗保健中的一件事
system, what would it be and why?
系统会是什么样的？为什么？
&gt;&gt; What I would like to see happen, well,
我希望看到的情况是，嗯，
there's two things. One is a wish and
有两件事。一个是愿望，
one is I think a possible reality. So
我认为其中一个是有可能实现的。所以
the possible reality is I'd like to see
可能的现实是，我希望看到
everybody in the United States get
美国每个人都会得到
tested for sleep apnnea. It's so
接受了睡眠呼吸暂停测试。真是太
underdiagnosed. There's so many people
诊断不足。人太多了
that are suffering from it. You saw the
那些正在遭受这种疾病折磨的人。你看到了
statistics. I mean it's it's an
统计数据。我的意思是，这是一个
epidemic. So if I could have one thing
流行性。所以如果我能拥有一样东西的话
that happens in the US health care
这种情况发生在美国医疗保健领域。
system, it would be that somehow or
系统，不知何故或
another somebody the powers that be say,
另一个掌权者说，
"Hey, you know what? We need to test
“嘿，你知道吗？我们需要测试
everybody for sleep disorders,
所有人都患有睡眠障碍，
specifically sleep apnea." I think that
具体来说，就是睡眠呼吸暂停。”我认为
would be a great big wish that I would
这将是我最大的愿望。
have. The second wish, which I don't
有。第二个愿望，我没有
know would would ever happen, but I'm
我知道这永远不会发生，但我
going to take my second wish anyway,
无论如何，我都要许第二个愿望。
even though you didn't offer it, is I
即使你没有主动提出，我也是。
want everybody to get a great night's
希望大家都能度过一个美好的夜晚
sleep, but I wanted to all be on the
睡觉，但我希望所有人都在……
same night.
当晚。
I want everybody in the world to get a
我希望全世界每个人都能得到一个
really good night's sleep on the Can you
在 Can You 上睡了个好觉
imagine what would happen the next day?
想象一下第二天会发生什么？
What if what if what if people actually
如果……如果……如果人们真的
found peace in the waring nations
在交战国中找到了和平
because they actually got a good night's
因为他们确实睡了个好觉
sleep? What do you think innovations
睡觉？你认为创新是什么？
would happen with if we get some of the
如果我们得到一些……就会发生这种情况
smartest people in the world to just get
世界上最聪明的人竟然都……
a good night's sleep? Like what about
睡个好觉？比如……
charities? What about philanthropy? Like
慈善机构？慈善事业方面呢？喜欢
every single thing that you do, you do
你做的每一件事，你都会做
better with a good night's sleep.
睡个好觉会感觉好些。
Wouldn't it be cool if everybody got one
如果人人都能拥有一个，那该多酷啊！
just for one night and see what happens?
就一晚，看看会发生什么？
&gt;&gt; Nine months later, there'd be a lot of
九个月后，将会有很多
kids. There would be a lot of kids born
孩子们。会有很多孩子出生。
for sure.
一定。
&gt;&gt; That's so beautiful. Michael, thank you
真漂亮。迈克尔，谢谢你。
so much for the work that you do. It's
你所做的工作就这么结束了吗？它是
so incredibly important because as the
非常重要，因为
numbers and the stats have shown, people
数字和统计数据表明，人们
are struggling increasingly in the world
在世界上，他们正面临越来越大的困境。
that we live. But through lifestyle
我们生活的地方。但通过生活方式
factors and the way that we work and all
各种因素、我们的工作方式以及所有
these other factors we talked about with
我们讨论过的这些其他因素
this more than anything and for so many
这一点比其他任何事情都重要，对很多人来说也是如此。
people, it's the cause of so much
人们啊，这是很多问题的根源。
frustration. It is the thing furthest
挫折。它是最远的事物。
upstream from a lot of the problems that
很多问题的根源在于上游
they struggle with in relationships, in
他们在人际关系中遇到困难
their work, in their sex life, and
他们的工作、他们的性生活，以及
everything in between. So having great
介于两者之间的一切。所以拥有美好的
educators out in the world that help to
世界各地帮助教育的人们
demystify this black box is so critical
揭开这个黑箱的神秘面纱至关重要。
and you're one of the very very best
你是最非常优秀的人之一。
I've ever met and in part because you're
我遇到过的最棒的人，部分原因就是因为你
so unbelievably engaging. You're a great
太引人入胜了。你很棒
storyteller. You've you've been in the
讲故事的人。你已经……
field doing this with patients of wide
在该领域，我们正在对各种各样的患者进行这项研究。
varieties but also you bring that
种类繁多，但你也带来了这些
psychology element which is of quite
心理因素相当重要。
rare to people that talk about
很少有人谈论
&gt;&gt; the clinical side of sleep. You have
睡眠的临床方面。你有
several great resources if people want
如果人们想要的话，这里有几个很棒的资源。
to continue to um learn more. I would
继续学习更多知识。我会
highly recommend um people if you've
强烈推荐给各位，如果你有
gotten to this point in the
已经到了这一步
conversation, I would highly recommend
对话，我强烈推荐
going over to your YouTube channel now
现在去你的YouTube频道看看
and watching some of your top videos
并观看您的一些热门视频
because I found them to be fascinating
因为我觉得它们很迷人。
and I learned so much more. We we
我还学到了很多东西。我们
weren't able to go through everything
没能全部看完。
today, but if there's specific things
今天，但如果有一些具体的事情……
like waking up in the middle of the
就像在半夜醒来一样
night, um your videos about that have
晚上好，嗯，你关于那方面的视频有
six or seven million views over on your
你的视频获得了六七百万次的观看量
channel and they're very very focused on
频道，他们非常非常专注于
that subject. So, if there's specific
那个话题。所以，如果有具体情况的话。
things that you felt weren't covered in
你觉得没有涵盖的内容
this conversation, right now go over to
现在，让我们把这个对话转移到
Michael's channel. Um, it'll be linked
迈克尔的频道。嗯，它会链接起来。
below and um, watch more there. But
下面还有更多内容，请观看那里。但
also, if you're a reader and you love to
另外，如果你是一名读者，并且热爱阅读
read and that's your thing, which I know
读书是你的爱好，我知道。
is great for sleep, two great books here
非常适合睡眠，这里有两本很棒的书。
in front of me. The power of when,
在我面前。时机的力量
discover your chronotype, and the best
发现你的睡眠类型，以及最佳睡眠模式
time to eat, lunch, ask for a raise,
该吃饭了，午饭时间到了，该要求加薪了。
have sex, write a novel, take your meds,
做爱、写小说、吃药，
and more. And also this book here,
还有更多。还有这本书，
Sleep, Drink, Breathe, which talks
睡觉、喝水、呼吸，这句台词
broadly about the simple daily habits
大致来说，是关于简单的日常习惯。
for profound long-term health. Michael,
为了深远的长期健康。迈克尔，
thank you.
谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Thank you. This has been so much fun. I
谢谢。这真的太有趣了。我
wasn't exactly sure what to expect, but
不太确定会发生什么，但是
it was lovely. I really enjoyed it.
太棒了。我非常喜欢。
Everybody here is fantastic, and uh I
这里每个人都很棒，呃，我
just want to wish everybody sweet
祝大家甜蜜
dreams. YouTube have this new crazy
梦想。 YouTube 上出现了这种疯狂的新玩意儿
algorithm where they know exactly what
他们使用某种算法，确切地知道什么
video you would like to watch next based
您接下来想观看的视频
on AI and all of your viewing behavior.
关于人工智能和你的所有观看行为。
And the algorithm says that this video
算法显示这段视频
is the perfect video for you. It's
这段视频非常适合你。它是
different for everybody looking right
对于每个向右看的人来说，结果都不一样。
now. Check this video out and I bet you
现在。看看这个视频，我敢打赌你
you might love it.
你或许会喜欢它。